Chapter 278

Beatrice flopped on her dorm bed while rubbing her eyes. It was time to rest, tomorrow was her big day. She and the other students would be taking various aptitude quests with their summons. This was something everyone was preparing for years during basic classes so she wasn’t the only person that was nervous.

A lot depended on this aptitude test. The biggest reason a person wanted to get a good result was status and power. By being rated higher a student would get access to better books, better teachers and would be prioritized.

Even though Beatrice didn’t want to stand out she wanted all those things. Power was something she very much strived for only with that would she be able to avenge her late grandfather.

“So you want me to help you get better results? Didn’t you promise your parents that you wouldn’t stand out?”

Beatrice was now juggling three balls around while balancing on a log. This was inside the soul world that Zhang Dong created. The scenery had changed from a sunny beach to a river in a forest. The log the girl was balancing on was wiggling around in the stream while she practiced her concentration.

“Yes I understand but…”

“But you want to get stronger and to get stronger you require your academy's knowledge?”

Zhang Dong that was sitting on a large branch answered before flinging a pebble towards the log that Beatrice was standing on. This tiny rock traveled as fast as a bullet and caused the large log to shake around violently. What followed was a drenched Beatrice that landed in the shallow stream below, the balls that she was juggling landing on her head.

“You’ll never get stronger if you lose your concentration like that…”

He looked at the wet girl that was shivering in the cold water. Normally he would be all for the slow approach. It was best to keep a low profile while slowly building up the power base. The girl wasn’t really in a position where she could stand out too much. Even less with that crazy main house of hers looking over their shoulders. But he didn’t have much time on his side, he needed to get back to his own family.

But still, he wasn’t sure if risking the child's life would be such a great idea. If he was her summoned spirit, he could probably defend her from everything, but he didn’t plan on staying that long. He had made some plans towards that, all this mana that this young girl was building wouldn’t be just for show. Even if he left her she would easily be able to form a proper contract with another spirit or be a regular mage.

Due to this, he was on the fence on how to continue, the girl was probably willing to get herself in harm's way if it was necessary. It was still only an academy for kids, it shouldn’t be that dangerous if she stood out a bit.

“Everything will be fine great spirit… if I make it to the special class, I’ll be able to visit the higher levels of the library… you’ll be able to get more books…”

Zhang Dong listened closely, apparently, a higher tier student had more privileges. The locked away library building would hand him the knowledge that he needed. What he now wanted was the location of a cube, with it his chances of getting back home would skyrocket.

‘I guess it should be fine…’

In the end, the feelings for his own family won over. If this girl was willing to put herself in harm's way, then he wouldn’t stop her. At least she had him if something happened. The girl was already 15 years old, in his world, this was already the age of an adult. Most all the disciples in his sect were already battling ferocious beasts and putting themselves in danger. This all in the pursuit of power and prestige.

“Trying to barter with this Lightning Emperor are you?”

Beatrice shook her head in fright a bit but instead of rage, she could see a somewhat grin on Zhang Dong’s face.

“Good, I will help you but only if you can perform this next task!”

He wiggled his finger and the log that the girl was standing on started spinning in one direction. Beatrice was tasked to balance on it while he randomly pelted her with small rocks.

On the dawn of the next day, Beatrice felt tired. Not physically but mentally, the small dream training sessions did put a tiny strain on her spirit. With the increase of her soul energy though the effect was minimized.

Zhang Dong started thinking of how to get his eager summoner through these tests without making the other kids look bad. Even now Beatrice’s mana pool had risen tremendously, she was already surpassing most of the kids her age. The only ones that were still ahead of her would be the young master types that he loved so much. He hoped that those types of people wouldn’t get as easily offended as the ones from his old world.

“We have gathered here to perform the annual aptitude test for all you young summoners, please remember to…”

Beatrice had now moved to the gathering place with everyone that had passed the test. She was standing to the side with all the other black-uniformed youths. They were still segregated by status here. Zhang Dong had a feeling that even if those lower status youths were elevated by their test results, the original ones in power wouldn’t take kindly to it.

‘I hope this goes well… don’t really want Beatrice to be involved in the good old step ladder of generic baddies.’

In a cultivation world what would mostly happen in this situation was one thing. A young master would not take kindly to an upstart getting similar or better results. He or she would then begin hazing and making trouble for this individual which would then result in this prideful person getting defeated in some way. Then the real problem would begin, probably starting with the young master’s older cousin or uncle.

‘Okay, let’s go over it again. We will be aiming to get you into the top class but you must place lower than the top students.’

Zhang Dong spoke out from his soul dimension. He had decided to help the girl get a better placement in the test but that didn’t mean that he wanted her to smoke the competition either. He wanted to have her place below the current top students like the prince or Isabella Hohenberg of Dragonridge.

Isabella posed the biggest danger as she was from the main house that Beatrice wanted to go against. It would be a direct slap to Isabella’s prestige if someone like Beatrice did better at an aptitude test. It would probably bring various problems with it, he knew how those passionate youths operated.

‘I understand great spirit…’

‘Also you can stop calling me great spirit, it was funny at first...just call me Leigong.’

‘But great spiri…’

Beatrice was a bit surprised by the sudden request to drop the honorifics. This was a world based on strength, so being respectful to a strong summoned spirit like she had was a must.

‘It’s fine, we are partners and partners need to be on a first-name basis!’

‘I could never be foolish enough to refer to a heroic spirit in such a way…’

‘Well, you will have to. Otherwise, I’m not going to answer your calls.’

This revelation caused Beatrice to sweat slightly. If her summon refused to be called during the test then she would end up in the lower class for sure. It could be even worse and they could call her even being a spirit summoner in question.

Beatrice had to begrudgingly accept Zhang Dong’s request.

‘Great Leigong… Mr. Leigong?’

Though it appeared that it would take some time for her to drop some of those honorifics. The place the test would be taking place was a large hall. With them were about two hundred other students. If Zhang Dong compared it to his previous world the numbers were quite small. When it came to sect testing the disciple number was always in the thousands of people.

The teacher continued the long-winded explanation of the tests that they would be going through. The first one was quite identical to what his own sect was doing just on a lesser scale. They would bring out some kind of measuring device that would show them how much mana each student had.

After that, they would test the elemental affinities of the spirit by having the summoner channel their energies into another device. The user of the spirit would have their mana be altered depending on their summon. Beatrice here would probably be shown as a lightning user.

The first ones that took the test were the students in white robes with the prince being first. It was clear that they didn’t want the high nobles to be stuck standing around and waiting for others. The device that was measuring the mana pool looked like a regular round crystal ball. It was placed in the center of some kind of magic circle and a number would light up above it. This number was the person’s level of mana.

Zhang Dong looked through Beatrice’s eyes as a green-haired youth walked over to take the first test. He even noticed the shouts of praise from the noble ladies at the side, this guy was clearly the biggest young master here. The hand was placed and after a moment a number appeared above it.

“489 points for prince Ludwig…”

The people from the side started cheering out, in Zhang Dong’s eyes this youth wasn’t really anything special. After training Beatrice for a few days her mana pool had reached a certain threshold that wasn’t that far off from this so called prodigy.

‘She’ll probably surpass him in a month or two… for now it's fine for her to be slightly weaker…’

The people started going through the test and he took note. It was important for Beatrice to be slightly below the top students. It would be best if she made it in at the last spot but that would be a big gamble.

This green-haired prince was somehow able to keep the top spot, the person from the main family that Beatrice was cautious of achieved a result of 411 and she was the third-best from the bunch. There was another youth from a ducal house that received 443 points.

Most of the students in white uniforms had results between a 100 and 300 with the top reaching slightly over that. From his discussion with Beatrice, they would need to get from 150 to 200 to be sure. A person of lower status had to show more talent than a family that could buy their way in.

The students in the black robes mostly hovered below the one hundred mark with a handful going beyond it. In time Beatrice was in front of the measuring device by Zhang Dong’s calculations if he didn’t interfere she would get slightly more than a 100 points. There was a way to boost that result with the help of a certain technique he developed thanks to the books. The problem with this was that he didn’t have much time to test it out and this would cause the first blunder to occur.

“Beatrice Hohenberg.... 7…. 798 points…”

The whole chamber got quiet after seeing the number above the device. No one could believe that a lowly daughter of a baron had more mana than a member of the royal family or from a ducal hose.

On the inside of this here blond girl, there was a certain Patriarch scratching his head, not sure about what went wrong.

‘Well… uh if you do bad at the other test your rating should go down… probably…’

He called out while shrugging, Beatrice on the other hand dropped her head down as she was feeling too many gazes on her face. She clearly didn’t expect her super glorious summon to make a mistake like this.

Chapter 279

‘Mr. Leigong… weren’t we not supposed to stick out this much?’

Beatrice asked after moving away from the testing orb. The other students were looking at her with much interest after she had soundly beaten the crown prince's score.

‘Ah don’t worry everything is going according to plan… you’ll just do worse in the other tests. They’ll just think you have a large mana pool but are behind in skills…’

Zhang Dong quickly thought about something to salvage the situation. There were other tests ahead of them, if she only stuck out in one then it would probably be fine. They would just attribute her to having potential in mana and nothing else.

The testing continued but the stares didn’t stop. He wasn’t sure what went wrong but he must have misjudged the effect that his spiritual energy would have here. It was that energy that he was using and not this world's mana that was slightly on a different wavelength.

‘I need to be ready for the next aptitude test and not make any more mistakes…’

The first test only measured the summoner's mana reserves. The second one would be testing another part, which would be the elemental affinity of the summon. For instance, if a person made a contract with a fire-based spirit like an Ifrit their affinity for fire would be high. Some spirits could have more than one affinity which he was expecting to get.

Prince Ludwig was the first one to go as well. Zhang Dong wasn’t sure if it was due to the green hair but the youth’s main affinity was wind with a surprising holy element as well.

“The prince managed to make a contract with a pegasus, as expected from a member of the royalty!”

Zhang Dong listened to some of the students with interest. The youth's summon was a flying horse and it was apparently also rare. He wasn’t so sure about such a creature’s strength in combat as it was just a horse with wings. But summoners could use certain summon specific spells depending on their spirit. Perhaps this was such a summon that boosted a person’s magical capabilities instead of being a minion that fought in their master's stead.

Isabella on the other hand looked to be the owner of a water-based spirit. From the conversations that some girls were having it looked to be some kind of water nymph. Just as the pegasus this was a higher form of spirit that was also somewhat intelligent. It was clear that the top students had attracted the rare spirits.

Some with their own capabilities but most by offering better treasures for the contracts. Regular students were left with generic summon spirits like the snake that Beatrice’s classmate Adabelle possessed.

After some time passed it was time for Beatrice to take the test. Previously no one had paid attention to her but now people were looking in. Some had expressions of disdain while others of curiosity.

‘Okay… this should work…’

Zhang Dong tried to relax, the test should show the spirit's elemental affinities. He was a cultivator that studied the Dao of lightning and of the holy element. His lightning should be the primary one while the latter the secondary.

The magical device that measured this looked like a mirror. The student was tasked to concentrate on their summoning mark that was on their right hand. When they performed this task right the elements would appear on the surface of the mirror. They would look like small balls of energy, depending on the size it would be clear what the summoned spirit was best at.

Beatrice placed her hand on the mirror and concentrated. The sign on her hand appeared and the surface of the mirror started to react. The tests here were open to anyone to see, the students were sure to look at the results of this dark horse.

The mirror started to shine and soon a blob of electricity appeared in the middle of it. It was quite big compared to what the other student received and implied that Beatrice possessed the rare lightning elemental affinity, which was also quite high.

But then something odd happened, soon after the electrical bubble in the middle appeared a second one also materialized. This one was bright gold, similar to the color the prince had with his pegasus but much larger and clear.

“Lightning and holy?... wait… there is more?”

The students and teachers started murmuring again as multiple elemental bubbles started to appear. They circled around the two large ones in the middle as little planets. Green for wind, red for fire, brown for earth, blue for water. There were all there, the four main elements had shown themselves. There were even some colors that the teachers didn’t recognize.

‘...is it because of all the various Daos that I picked up through the years?’

Zhang Dong scratched his head again. He was a cultivator that had mastered a lot of techniques through the years. The Zhang Clan was versed in water techniques so he had picked up a few along the way. Huo Clans fire, Feng clans wind, and even some earth techniques from some side schools.

He didn’t focus much on them but considering that he was a nascent soul master he could master them to a certain degree in a couple of days or weeks. Thus the mirror showed a reflection of the Daos that he was proficient in, which was quite many.

This was something unprecedented as most spirits were only good at one thing. Rare ones had a secondary element to go with their main one. Then the legendary creatures had three of them. But he was already showing twice that number.

Thus the eyes were again on Beatrice for showing something never seen before. Where the first test might have been attributed to luck or one rare skill, this showed something more. Now she was far ahead of her competition and only two more tests remained.

‘G-great spirit…?’

‘A-all according to plan…’

Zhang Dong wasn’t sure what he could say, it looked like things were working against him. The girl had already aced two of the four main tests. She was already sticking out like a sore thumb and he wasn’t sure if he could do anything about it at this point. Even if she failed the other two quests she already positioned herself miles away from the competition.

He had tried to lower his elemental affinities during this test but even then the mirror showed all of his inner workings.It was as if something was working in the background to expose his secrets.

The teachers and the students were now paying attention to her. Through Beatrice’s eyes, he could see everyone whispering. The teachers were taking notes and he could even see some of them going elsewhere. In time he would know that they went to get some higher profile, people, to come. This whole thing was getting out of hand quite quickly.

‘Beatrice, the next test is to measure how much magical pressure a summoner can handle, right?’

‘Yes Leigong…’

‘How about you just pretend to pass out before the other students, just wait enough for it to not be too obvious…’

The master plan had been made, it was more or less the last hope. The next test would put the casters under pressure. From what Zhang Dong could tell it was similar to a popular test that cultivators liked to do. One of the stronger cultivators would release killing intent or their aura on the disciples. If the student didn’t pass out and held on through a test like that they would pass.

This would be the same thing here. One of the mages would deliver magical pressure onto the young spell casters. They would feel strain to their souls and would have to last through it. He wasn’t sure anymore but he felt like with him around Beatrice wouldn’t really be affected by something like that. She would need to play dead otherwise she would probably outlast everyone else while yawning.

…...

Unbeknownst to Zhang Dong and Beatrice, there was some movement in the background. The two tests that the young girl aced brought unwanted attention.

“Is that the girl?”

“Yes… her results have been astonishing. Not since the Arch-mage has someone been able to get such results…”

An old man with a long beard and a classical wizard hat was talking to some teachers. They were looking at Beatrice through a hidden side window. This man here was the vice principal and he was called overdue to the troubling results.

“Could it have been a mistake?”

“Not likely sir, we have checked the devices and they haven’t been tampered with. The girl also isn’t someone with such resources to fool our teachers.”

The man started rubbing his long beard with one hand while looking through the window. After some squinting, he spoke out.

“There is something peculiar about that mana… I will test her myself.”

The man hit the ground with his long staff that looked like a large tree branch with a big green gem at the top. He was surrounded by a magical glow before his appearance changed to that of one of the teachers in this room.

“Could she be one of them? Wouldn’t they try to not stand out this much?”

“It could be a possibility… those results do look troubling.”

The vice principal placed his staff to the side and exchanged it for the one that the teacher was using. He then headed towards the testing room where a smaller group of students was waiting for him.

They were standing in a circle and ready to take the test. They were about ten meters away from the teacher that would be standing in the middle. The disguised vice principal moved to the designated spot and prepared himself for the test.

He was now looking in Beatrice’s direction. He could feel that there was something off about there but he couldn’t put a finger on it. There had been some troublesome things happening around this academy and this girl was being suspicious.

‘I need to test her… I will need to take a peek inside to be sure…’

The students were preparing themselves, all of them had closed their eyes to concentrate so no one was able to see him staring at Beatrice with deep interest. His staff connected with the ground and the mana pressure was released.

‘Interesting…’

A normal mage would have not noticed something like this but the vice principal was someone very experienced. He could tell that the pressure he used for the first test was just bouncing off the girl in front of him. He also noticed that she was pretending to be affected by it, this of course sparked some concerns.

‘Is she putting on an act?’

Due to this whole thing looking fishy the man decided to probe her more. He sent a direct mana probe towards this young girl. If she was a normal human being then she would at most pass out instantly but if she was one of the enemies they were looking for then the reaction would be more adverse.

“W-what is this?”

“Why hello there… I didn’t think I’d be having guests today.”

The man was surprised by a third result. The moment he tried probing the girl he felt something powerful pulling him inside. He found himself in some strange place face to face with someone powerful. This someone had clearly trapped him here as he felt that his connection to his own body was being blocked off and he couldn’t leave.

What he was looking at was some kind of man sitting on a golden throne. He looked like some kind of otherworldly being. There was also another problem, right next to this man was a giant golden dragon that looked quite fierce.

“You’ll have to give me a good reason about why you tried to do that to my little Beatrice.”

“Y-your little Beatrice?”

“Yes, the girl I’m contracted with, why did you try to damage her soul?”

The man started to sweat as he realized what this was. The person standing in front of him was clearly not the enemy that he was looking for. He was some kind of heroic spirit that made a contract with that student. The situation was dire as the vice principal knew well that the contracted spirits were very protective of their contractors. If he made a mistake he could very well have his soul erased by this powerful being…

Chapter 280

Zhang Dong was a bit maddened. He had made many blunders through these aptitude tests which caused Beatrice to stand out. The plan of getting into the special class with somewhat lowered scores had fallen through. Beatrice was looking like some kind of gifted child now, far above the other powerful noble houses. He knew well how those types of people reacted to upstarts, his only hope was that they wouldn’t go all out against a child till she grows.

Then there was this guy that was trying to pull a fast one. He felt the magic instructor attempt some underhanded attack during the third test. To him, it looked like he was out for no good as this attack would damage Beatrice’s soul. The two were connected with each other so he was quickly made aware of this intrusion.

The purpose of this underhanded attack was unknown to him. It certainly had a different purpose than the mana pressure test. He reacted fast by intercepting the attacker, he was injecting a soul fragment for some reason so it was easy to pull it into his own soul dimension. Through this, he was able to make contact with the old man’s own soul and trap him here for now.

The place looked like a giant castle with him sitting on a throne. He had played around during the last training session with Beatrice and had left it like this. The old man he pulled in was now trembling before him and down on his knees.

“I apologize for my transgression, great spirit.”

‘I guess he thinks I’m a spirit like Beatrice does… Did he want to harm her? Maybe some jealous young noble ordered him to damage her future prospects?’

Zhang Dong was thinking in line with what cultivators from his own world would do. It was normal for them to try to cripple the competition. If this was true then he was kind of at fault for getting Beatrice noticed by the other students.

‘It could also be a big misunderstanding as always…’

He also had enough sense and life experience to know that things weren’t always how they seemed. The old guy could very well be doing something else entirely. He wasn’t versed in these magic world’s techniques, he could only distinguish them on a basic level. A prodding towards the girl's soul was done, if it would leave long-lasting effects or harm her, he wasn’t sure.

That is also why he didn’t try to trash him the moment he got here. His own soul energy was far greater than this old man. Though the old fart was the strongest person that he came across here. His energy levels were akin to someone at the very early onset of core formation. For someone at the middle stage of the nascent soul, this was nothing.

“Explain to me… what was your reason? Who put you up to this? Are there people aiming for Beatrice’s life?”

“Aiming for her life? N-no great spirit, you have it all wrong! This has nothing to do with the student that you made a contract with!”
The man became quite chatty, this was probably because his soul beast was right next to him. The size difference between the small old man and the giant golden dragon was immense.

Zhang Dong was painted a picture during this explanation. There were supposed ‘demons’ in this world, ones that liked to infiltrate human locations like this magical academy. Due to Beatrice’s strange boost in power during the test, he was called to check up on her. The attack that he intercepted was there to see if she was one of this form shifting monsters.

“So, these demons infiltrate schools like this to steal knowledge or to kill potential strong magicians?”

‘Great now I have to contend with body snatchers…’

“Is there a way to detect these demons?”

“Yes great spirit, they are susceptible to certain magical spells. The same one that I performed on your summoner…”

It was strange to look at an old man that was kneeling down and looking up to him with glistening eyes. He was like a really old wrinkled up puppy that looked at his master after peeing on the carpet. It did seem like he was telling the truth, he had certain techniques to measure things like that.

“Very well… you may leave…”

“Thank you, great spirit! I will never forget your generosity”

The man’s eyes opened up wide and he was all smiles but that turned upside down the moment Zhang Dong spoke out again.

“But to be sure, I’ll have to leave you with a small present.”

“A present, great spirit?”

Zhang Dong flicked his finger forward and a small golden bolt of lightning flew out. It connected with the soul version of the old man, the moment it did he could hear him scream out in pain.

“I will leave my mark on you, if you ever go against Beatrice in any way, your life will be forfeit! You don’t have to worry, if you do a simple task for me your life will be spared.”

The vice-principal opened up his eyes to find himself on the ground. The students that were taking the test were around him. It looked like he had passed out and dropped dead during the test. Even some teachers were coming from the side.

“Is everything okay?”

He shot up to his feet and checked for something. There was a certain seal placed in his body now, it wasn’t something that he was capable of removing with his current power. The contracted spirit that lived in the girl had placed some kind of kill switch on him, of this he was certain.

“Y-yes… the test is over… now if you’ll excuse me…”

The old man that was still disguised as the teacher quickly ran back into the back room where his associates were.

“Vice-principal what happened? You suddenly collapsed?”

“How long was I unconscious?”

“For about ten seconds…”

“Is that so…”

“What about the student? Is she a demon?”

“The student?”

The old man looked to the instructor that was asking him questions. Sweat was visible on his forehead the moment he thought about the person living inside of that young girl.

“No she is not… give her full marks for the test! Now… I need to talk to the principal! Stall a bit with the next test, don’t let student Beatrice contend before I return! ”

The other instructors were surprised by the vice principal’s exit. He looked like he had seen a ghost and was clearly afraid of the girl. This left everyone here with only more questions and even fear towards this young lady.

Beatrice was again the focal point of this test. Even the students that were together with her could see that for some reason the teacher was afraid of her. Zhang dong that was on the inside was slowly tearing out his hair. The vice-principal ruined his plans and Beatrice ended up with the highest marks again.

Now it was already too late to go back, it didn’t really matter what would happen at the last test. From Zhang Dong’s perspective, the students and teachers were already looking at Beatrice as some strange rare animal.

He placed a little soul binding technique on the old man so that he could listen in to what he would do. Through it, he could see the old man running towards some large tower that was further away in the magical academy.

‘Good he is following the instructions, hope the person in charge will listen...’

He rubbed his chin while Beatrice pestered him about what was happening.

‘Listen up Beatrice, it’s probably not going to be possible to hide my presence anymore. We will have to change our plan… slightly. ’

‘Um…’

He felt like the image of the glorious all-knowing spirit was dropping by the minute in Beatrice’s eyes. Nothing seemed to be working out so he decided to go out with a bang. The last test was going to be a practical one. The new summoners were supposed to call out their spirits and have them battle.

Their opponents would be the instructors and their summoned monsters. The only thing he could do now was to leave an impression on others. He needed to show off that he wasn’t someone that anyone could mess with. People were already aware that Beatrice had gotten a special spirit.

The only way to protect her now was to show that he was powerful enough to even go against the top experts of this world. This could be only achieved by facing off against the right opponent and that vice principal character would help him with that.

‘If you say so Leigong…’

He could tell that the young girl was starting to doubt his advice but for now, she was going along with it. Explaining the whole ordeal would take too long so for now he decided to remain mysterious.

After some time every student had gone through the third test. The results were posted on a large board outside of the testing chamber. The person that was first again was Beatrice, the girl had to contend with more surprised gazes.

Tests like this didn’t take that long and there weren’t that many people. The final test would be the longest as it required the young summoners to let their spirits clash. Before that, it was time for some arguing though as some of the young nobles weren’t having it.

“How did you do it, how can someone like you score this high!?”

A girl in a white uniform was now confronting Beatrice in front of the result board. Zhang Dong’s host was way ahead of the competition, the second place belonged to the young prince but it wasn’t even a close call.

“How would I even do that? Bring some proof before you accuse someone!”

Beatrice retaliated by glaring at the other female student. It was surprising to see someone from the less established students to shout back at someone in a higher position.

“You dare!?”

Zhang Dong perked up at the muttered words, it looked like this world wasn’t that much different than his. Now if the opposing side just continued with a ‘courting death’ line it would have been perfect. Before things could escalate another blond lady appeared. She was quite the beauty and known by everyone here, she was Isabella Hohenberg a duke’s daughter.

“Lady Godford, you should calm down and prepare for the last test... “

The girl looked at Isabella and instantly shrunk back. It was like looking at a small mouse that was confronted by a ferocious cat.

“I… if Lady Isabella says so… I’ll excuse myself…”

She was soon gone along with her own entourage of students.

“Thank you for helping, Lady Isabella.”

Zhang Dong could feel that Beatrice was surprised by the sudden aid. He could also see that it wasn’t done out of good will. That look that Isabella was giving Beatrice was filled with malice. It was unknown what she was plotting but he didn’t like where this was going. Luckily a green-haired young man appeared to diffuse the situation.

“That’s quite the achievement, Lady Beatrice was it? I’ll be looking forward to your next test.”

The youth looked quite friendly and he wasn’t even jealous of losing out to Beatrice. There was a certain shiver that ran through Beatrice the moment the prince talked to her. It was followed by a snapping sound from the direction that Isabella was standing in. The fan in the girl's hand that she was holding had been cleanly snapped in two.

“Oh my, it must have been old, I will have to order a new one.”

She played it off with a laugh before walking away.

‘I don’t think that girl likes you too much.’

‘I can see that Mr. Leigong…’

The gathering soon dispersed as it was time to get ready for the final test of the day.

Chapter 281

A loud knock on a white ornate door was heard. Behind that exquisite looking entrance there was a spacious room. On the sides, there were blue crystals that illuminated it from all sides while the windows seemed to be not letting much sunlight in.

Inside there, various bookcases with various grimoires could be spotted. But the most characteristic item that was there looked to be a large white desk. Behind it there was a person looking over some scrolls, this person seemed quite annoyed at the loud knocking at the door.

“Who is it? I said that I didn’t want to be disturbed!”

“Excuse me Principal, it’s me…”

“Vice Principal?...”

The person behind the desk grumbled while putting the scrolls back onto the desk. Within a few moments, a feminine voice replied.

“You can enter.”

The Principal that was sitting behind the desk was wearing a baggy wizard robe but her head was visible. She had long snow-white hair very akin to a certain Lightning Emperor. Her skin was much darker though but the most characteristic thing about this person were the thin long ears.

“Thank you Principal, you have to help me!”

The woman that looked like your typical dark elf from a fantasy book narrowed her crimson eyes at the old man that came crashing through her door. He even tripped on the carpet and face planted onto the ground. It was clear that something had to have happened as she never saw him lose his composure like this.

“Vice Principal Elobarin, control yourself!”

The dark-skinned woman wiggled her finger around and some sparkles appeared in front of it. A torrent of wind surrounded the fallen man and brought him to his two feet.

“I apologize Principal, but the situation is dire… I have been marked!”

“You have been marked? By who? Who would be powerful enough to put a mark on a mage of your caliber?”

The woman frowned while standing up. She was the principal of this whole academy and also the most powerful mage in it. After her came the vice principals, there were more than one of them around. They were weaker than her but still should be amongst the best in this academy and even this world.

“Was it one of the demons? Did it infiltrate our academy!?”

“No.. it wasn’t a demon…”

The man grasped his chest as he tried to calm himself down. In a few moments, he looked at the woman and started explaining. He told her about the strange boost in Beatrice’s stats during the assessment test. How he tried testing her himself to see if she was one of the demons in disguise and then how he was confronted by a mighty spirit that left a mark on his soul with an ultimatum.

“A spirit you say? How powerful could it have been to do such a thing, a Spirit King?”

The man was finished with his explanation but was still sweating. In a moment he spoke up to correct the person he was working for.

“A spirit king… I don’t think so… I think that spirit was much greater than that…”

“You don’t mean?”

The man nodded while looking at the dark elven lady with a sweaty forehead.

“A Spirit Emperor? Why would a Spirit Emperor form a contract with that student, is there something special about her?”

“I don’t know… but he gave me a message to pass on to you before he let me go…”

“A message? To me?”

The woman raised her brow, not really sure why a powerful spirit like that would even be in the picture. Though magical spirits had their own ways of doing things so this situation wasn’t all that inconceivable.

“Well, not specifically to the Principal. The spirit wanted me to procure a strong summoner for the last test.”

The old man started explaining some more. The spirit left a mark on his soul that could be triggered to kill him. Only if he brought over a strong summoner to face off against Beatrice in the coming test would he be able to get rid of it.

“I’m not sure what its purpose is… maybe it wants to fight a strong opponent?... He did look very ferocious and powerful…”

The elven woman started rubbing her chin while moving over to the old man. She touched his shoulder while concentrating. While using her knowledge she looked at the Vice Principal’s condition. She could see some kind of strange spell being attached to his soul.

She wouldn’t just let someone under her be exposed to something like this so she started casting some spells to get rid of this mark. Though the moment she attempted a removal there was an unwanted reaction in the form of electrocution.

A large explosion was heard from the office of the academy's Principal. This alerted the secretary that was working outside. The young woman quickly ran into the room to see what was going on.

“Principal are you okay! W-What happened!”

The woman was greeted by a partially destroyed room. Many torn up books pages were still floating around and falling down on two people that were down on the ground. Both the Principal and Vice-Principal were twitching around their hair had been electrocuted which made the two look like they had afros.

“Elobarin… get Isilin to test that spirit…”

“Y-yes Principal…”

It took some time for the two to gather themselves but it was enough to prepare the stage for Zhang Dong and Beatrice. The other students were now going through the last test in the same order as previously.

Beatrice was in a side room with some other students. She was clearly getting strange looks from others, no one expected her to be at the top of the class after most of the tests were over. It didn’t even matter how well she did in the last test, she would be getting into the prestigious class with the other high nobles.

‘Don’t mind them, they are just surprised that’s all.’

Zhang Dong spoke to Beatrice that was just sitting there. He had noticed that this young girl didn’t really have any friends here. Even before she started these trials there wasn’t anyone that she spoke to. The only person that interacted with her was that strange roommate but even that one didn’t converse much with her.

She was truly the lonely heroine of this story, and now with him forcing the attention towards her, the other people were aware of her existence. He already knew where this was going and he didn’t like it.

‘It’s okay Mr. Leigong I’m used to it.’

Due to the soul connection that he had with the girl he could see some flashes of old memories. Even in those, she was the odd girl out, mostly hanging out in the back while the high noble ladies like Isabella chatted.

‘Look on the bright side, now no one will be able to ignore you, you’ll be a hot topic in the noble circles!’

He tried shifting the conversation to a better place but the girl just gave out a sigh while grumbling. It was clear that the attention that she was getting was troubling her.

‘I thought we weren’t supposed to stand out so much, Mr. Leigong.’

Beatrice replied in a somewhat cold tone, it was clear that she was on to his hogwash. He couldn’t do much about it, the all-knowing spirit act wasn’t something he was used to. There were too many variables so he made her rate above all the other students by a mile. What was done was done though, the only way to salvage the situation now was to make people fear her.

If not, any two-bit schmuck would try to test her true power. This was the biggest fault with people that liked to hide their true strength. They would be approached by anyone and everyone for any small discretion. He could already imagine Beatrice getting hazed by the higher nobles if they thought they could take her. On the other hand, if they knew that she was able to easily take them out, they would remain in their lane.

“Beatrice Hohenberg please get ready.”

Zhang Dong’s train of thought was broken by one of the teachers that entered the waiting room. The other students looked to Beatrice with interest as she stood up, quite a bit of people were interested in this spirit that could make this average noble girl progress this fast.

‘Don’t worry Beatrice, just summon me and I’ll take care of the rest!’

He called out to her while she got ready. The last test would be a practical one where summons would be pitted up against each other. This was also why he used the vice principal to his advantage. He gave him one order, to get a strong summoner to face off against Beatrice here. If not, he would be fighting a lesser spirit that wouldn’t really be very impactful for his show.

To show off his power he needed the right opponent. If he faced off against a weak spirit like that one snake there wouldn’t really be much impact on it. Only when the hero had the right villain could he shine.

‘Calm down, I’m with you.’

Zhang Dong could feel that the young girl was getting nervous. After walking through a long corridor she arrived at something that looked like an arena. There were other students and teachers to the sides watching them.

‘I’m fine… but why are there so many people here…’

‘Oh? Are there usually fewer people at these events?’

‘Yes…’

A smile appeared on his face as he heard that. This meant that the attention was on him and the girl. He would need to perform well now, from what he knew people were thinking that he was some kind of super-rare spirit. If they thought he was a rarity they wouldn’t hurt the girl that managed to summon a legendary creature.

They would probably try to somehow profit from this event, try to control her first before any kind of violent act would be attempted. He would need to use the time given to progress the young girl further down her path of power. At a certain point even if someone tried something drastic she would be ready.

“Student, Beatrice Hohenberg. Are you ready to be rated?”

“I am!”

She nodded while looking up to the person that spoke out. Zhang Dong looked with her and noticed a peculiar looking woman with dark skin and long ears.

‘Is that an elf? and a dark elf to boot?’

After Beatrice confirmed that she was ready a certain person walked out from behind from where that dark elven woman was standing. There was a spell cast to propel this person forward all the way into the ring.

“Isn’t that Instructor Isilin?... isn’t he a five-star summoner?”

“Why would someone like that…”

People started murmuring amongst themselves after the person performing the test was revealed. It was clear that his little blackmailing attempt worked and they were now facing a more powerful summoner.

With Beatrice on one side and the instructor in a dark robe on the other, the test was going to start. Instructor Isilin was a lanky looking man with glasses and a magic book in his left hand. He waved his right hand on which he had a summoning circle that began to glow. A myriad of magical circles started appearing before the spirit summoning started.

Soon the creature that Zhang Dong would need to face would appear. By the size of the magical circle it appeared that this creature would be quite large. The people moved closer, none of them believed that someone like Beatrice would be able to summon something that could stand against a five star ranked summoner. But soon they would be astonished by the being called the Lightning Emperor Leigong!

Chapter 282

More and more people poured into the training arena where the summoner test was taking place. Word had spread that a new top student had appeared that belonged to a lower noble house. This caused all of the black-uniformed students to be interested in seeing one of their own move up in social status. Also, the white uniforms were interesting in the new upstart.

Everyone murmured while they saw her walking out even more after they all realized that both the Vice Principal and the Principal were watching this test. This caused quite the uproar while also filling up the whole place with people. All eyes were on Beatrice, the young girl wasn’t taking the attention too well as she dropped her head so that others wouldn’t see her face.

‘This test is between summoned spirits, so just leave everything to me.’

There was more than summoning a battle spirit to a fight between Summoners. Each of these mages could also support their creature with attacking and buffing spells. They could lend more mana to the spirit that could then perform some specialized attacks. Also with time as a summoner’s mana capacity grew they could support more spirits.

Beatrice was facing a five-star summoner, this was someone at a quite advanced level. She on the other hand would be considered a one-star summoner after passing this test. So someone that wasn’t even a proper summoner was facing off against a master. Most instructors in this school were at the three-star level. Thus this was quite the event, it was obvious for the people in the stands that there had to be something special about this Beatrice Hohenberg.

‘Why is instructor Isilin here…’

Beatrice asked while her eyes went wide. She only now realized that the Principal and some high profile people from the academy were all here. Zhang Dong on the other hand knew that he was the reason that they were here. He had left a little shocking present in that Vice Principal’s soul that would be impossible to remove for anyone below the nascent soul level.

When that person invaded his realm he was able to exert the maximum of his cultivation realm on him. He expected the old fart to go to one of the powerful mages to remove this mark that he placed. He also was sure to make it jolt people with some lightning if it was prodded too much. It looked quite dangerous but the man wasn’t really in any danger of his soul being damaged. Zhang Dong just wasn’t that type of person but the people here didn’t know that. So this allowed him to play as an eccentric spirit.

‘They must be aware of my existence, probably just want to test the extent of my power.’

He replied while Beatrice bowed before the instructor. Zhang Dong was a bit worried about his summoner’s mana reserves but she should have enough for him to show himself and defeat a higher caliber of summon.

If he actually failed to defeat his opponent then Beatrice’s life could be in danger. Those people that were from the main house could get some stupid ideas. Which was also why he needed to make them at least think that he was more than even their strongest mage could handle.

“Begin.”

It was time to start, the Principal gave the okay for the bout to start and everyone looked into the ring. Instructor Isilin started to perform his summoning spell by reaching out with his hand forward. A large round magical circle appeared in front of him and after a moment a creature started rising from within it.

Beatrice noticed that this already looked a bit different from what she did when summoning her spirit. When she performed the summoning her hand only flashed slightly and then Leigong’s body parts appeared at a random location. There was no magic circle or anything he just popped out of nowhere instead.

Before she could think about it more, her gaze was drawn to the spirit that was emerging from the large magical circle. The first thing that she noticed was its face, it looked similar to what a toad or frog would look like. The toad-like mouth wasn’t without teeth, there were omnivore-like chompers stacked nicely together.

This creature was quite large, many times larger than a human. The body was prolonged and there were more than two sets of legs. It had three legs on each side, the feet had large claws that dug into the hard ground beneath. If Zhang Dong had to chime in, he would tell her that this creature looked like a cross between an alligator and a frog with a bonus set of legs to probably keep that large body moving.

“It’s Instructor Isilin’s Land Dragon! Didn’t think we'd get to see such a powerful summon spirit!”

“Isn’t that spirit a king class summon? Why would they use it on someone that isn’t even a one-star summoner?”

People started chatting with each other while the large monster emerged. Its tail started wiggling about and smacking the ground that caused some tremors to go through this arena.

“Student Beatrice, please summon your spirit.”

It was finally time for the young girl to perform her summoning but with so many people watching her the only thing that she wanted to do was to run away. People started whispering some more after seeing her hesitate, some even started to laugh.

“Are you sure that girl can summon a spirit?”

“Maybe it's a tiny slime and she is ashamed to bring it out?”

The mocking voices filled the arena building while Beatrice started shrinking back, the only thing that brought her back into reality was the voice of her contracted spirit.

‘Beatrice, ignore those kids, they don’t know you. Just perform your summoning like you practiced and leave everything to me!’

The confident voice of Leigong made her finally snap back to reality. She soon moved her hand forward while concentrating. The mark on her hand started to glow in golden color while everyone quieted down.

People that were the most interested in the girl’s spirit were the Principal and the instructors. They all could already see that something was off, this spirit was unique. They could feel the mana energy around that summoning mark and it had a somewhat different quality than what a regular spirit should have.

This summoning was a bit different as Beatrice saw a golden ball of light appearing in front of her instead of the usual foot or hand. The audience started at the ball of light while narrowing their eyes while calling out loudly.

“Is that a Will-o'-Wisp? ...isn’t that at the same level as a slime?”

Before they could laugh out through something different happened, the ball of light exploded causing a massive burst of bright light to blind everyone in the vicinity. There was also a loud explosion-like sound akin to a thunderbolt connecting with a tree. Everyone covered their eyes and ears that were in a world of hurt.

“W-what happened...wait who is that there…”

The people started shouting in pain at first but after recovering everyone started pointing down to the arena. There before Beatrice stood a man. He was quite handsome with a chiseled jaw, rippling pecs, and shoulder long snow-white hair.

“W-why is he like that?”

“Cover your eyes!”

There he was, Zhang Dong in all of his glory and in a white loincloth. The people that were facking his backside could behold those stunning rear cheeks that were only partially hidden by a thin white material.

‘Mr. Leigong… where are your clothes…’

Beatrice blushed as she was the closest person to Zhang Dong. The only thing hiding that package was a tightly placed loincloth but the spirit that was summoned didn’t seem to mind, it was as if this was all going according to plan.

‘Well my little Beatrice, let me explain. You see, my godly clothes are made from very rare materials. When you summon me with them you use up too much mana, so if I want to appear fully I have to show up like this. But don’t worry, I don’t mind.”

Zhang Dong’s gear was all above the heavenly grade. When he tried to materialize in this world mana would be used up for those clothes to manifest. Thus the easiest way was to remove this problem and just use the smallest amount of fabric possible. He was mostly bare like this but with his enhanced body he didn’t really need armor.

This of course caused the young ladies in the audience to squeal. He was quite the handsome man and looked to be in his early twenties and in the prime of his life. The other people here could not contend with all this manliness before them.

“How did that girl summon such a vulgar looking spirit…”

“Yes… look at that jawline and all those muscles…”

“And look at that indecent appendage down there… it's grotesquely large!”

“Do you think I could form a contract with a similar spirit? Is it some kind of new summon creature?”

The men in the arena started looking at the women that were talking loudly. At first, it looked like they were angered by this human-looking spirit’s appearance but when continuing their true intentions shine through.

“Is that the spirit that put the mark on you?”

The dark elven woman asked the Vice Principal that was staring with eyes bulging at the half-naked man down in the arena.

“What? Ah yes, that was him… but he was wearing clothes… why is he almost naked?”

“I see...Instructor Isilin, please continue with the test!”

The Principal called out from the stands to the man performing the test. He was also stunned by the humanoid spirit that was before him as they were a rare breed. With a wave of his hand, he gave an order to his Land Dragon. The creature gave out a loud howl before charging towards this peculiar looking summon.

Zhang Dong squatted down while not really paying attention to the charging monster. He scooped up some sand from the ground and let it fall through his fingertips.

“Finally, I can interact with this world normally…”

After removing most of his clothes he was finally able to bring his entire body into this world. If he didn’t use up too much of his spiritual energy he would be even able to walk around without Beatrice’s mana running out too fast.

‘Great Spirit… t-the Land Dragon…’

Beatrice sent him a massage while he was spacing out. He looked forward and could see a huge alligator-frog bolting toward his position. The monster’s head was larger than his whole body, it could swallow him whole if it wanted to.

“Don’t need to worry, it’s but a tiny amphibian reptile.”

He replied while slamming his arms into the ground before him. Zhang Dong remained in place with both his hands stuck in the dirt. Before the creature could get into biting distance he made his move.

Zhang Dong stood up while pulling the ground in front of him upwards. It looked as if he was flipping a table but instead of a table, it was a big chunk of the arena that the creature was standing on.

The people in the audience went slack-jawed as they saw the smaller humanoid spirit flip half of the arena with the Land Dragon standing on that part. The creature was tossed back with the huge chunk of ground and rock falling on top of it, burying it in the process.

“See? Nothing to worry about!”

Zhang Dong laughed out loud while looking back at Beatrice that also had a strange expression of astonishment on her face.

“I… I see…”

Chapter 283

After a moment of silence, the audience in the arena started to shout out. They just witnessed a half-naked man lifting up half of the arena’s ground and flipping it with the large dragon on it. It just looked like he dug his hands into the ground and pulled out a large part of the ground from underneath.

The Summoned Land Dragon roared loudly before all the noises stopped. Now everyone was looking at a big pile of rubble and with only the half-naked man before it. His long white hair was waving around from the wind pressure and he looked quite happy for some reason.

‘See Beatrice, what did I say? No problem!’

Zhang Dong looked at the rubble before him that he just flipped on his opponent. After being able to come out he started performing some tests. For one thing, he was quite a lot weaker than he would like to be.

At this moment he wasn’t even able to reach the core formation level if he wanted to remain in his full-bodied form. The monster that he was fighting was about at the strength level of a late stage foundation establishment beast.

He himself was a bit stronger while only utilizing his body refining technique instead of his Qi cultivation. There was enough mana for him to use from Beatrice to maybe perform one stronger Qi attack but that would probably tire his summoner out. He was already minimizing the strain on her by not wearing most of his clothes. The usual boxers he used were also replaced by a loincloth to lower the expenditure even further.

Before he could raise his fist high in victory he heard something. There was a rumble in all that rubble that he created. This made him also notice the instructor that Beatrice was up against. He could see the man injecting mana down where his opponent would be. In a few moments, he knew why as the Land Dragon showed his frog-like face to him.

‘The books did say that summoners have that utility as well.’

Zhang Dong had gone through the library books so he had more than the basic knowledge about magic and this world. What this summoner was doing was healing his creature with the help of his mana.

From what he could tell, summoners could be divided into a few categories. This man here was from one that specialized in high mana capacity. They mostly just used their summoned spirits for fighting while hanging back in the background. With more mana, the spirits could perform more spells or have a boost to their strength.

There was also a category that didn’t rely on summoned spirits to fight for them. They just used their elemental affinities to produce their own spells and fight closer to what a normal mage would. Those types had some subcategories depending on their way of fighting. Some did it form close range while others from far away.

The students went quiet as they felt the whole place rumble. In a matter of seconds, the creature that looked like a mix between a frog and an alligator started crawling out from beneath that rubble.

“Hah, I guess it's time for round two! This Lightning Emperor Leigong will put you in your place!”

Zhang Dong shouted out, his words were clearly heard by the people around this large room. This brought everyone’s attention to him instead of the Land Dragon that was crawling out from within the pile of rocks and dirt. He kind of knew why they were surprised as he wasn’t acting like a normal summon.

Normal summoned spirits like him wouldn’t be able to converse with other people than their summoners. He had a connection with Beatrice through her soul so learning the language was easy. The books that he absorbed through the days helped to fill in some holes and now he was more than able to speak in this world's language.

“Leigong? Was there someone like that?”

“Lightning Emperor? Did such a spirit exist? Is it some kind of new spirit?”

“That spirit hasn’t used any lightning magic, is he really a lightning type? Why can it speak our tongue? ”

The teachers that were gathered besides the Principal started talking with each other. Zhang Dong had thrown out his name on purpose. His intent was to make a big impression and he needed to have a grand name to go with it. Calling himself an Emperor was also on purpose.

He knew how the spirits were rated in this world and a spirit Emperor was a legendary type. His intention was to make himself look stronger than he actually was. With the label of a legendary spirit, Beatrice’s life would be better protected. At least till he got enough time to get her to a high enough level where she could let him access his nascent soul level powers.

The lanky instructor named Isilin looked at the strange half-naked man before him. After hearing him speak out he became even more interested. This spirit that was being used by a young girl with zero fighting experience managed to deliver a devastating blow to his own summon.

This instructor was an experienced summoner though. He knew that defeating a single summoned creature from someone like him wouldn’t bring victory. There was much more mana that he could spend to resurrect his creature along with summoning others to aid it in battle.

Before he did that he looked back to the Principal that ordered him to do this unique test. In his mind this test was already over, there was no reason to continue the newbie summoner had already proved herself. This test was just here to measure the spirits might and this one seemed to be enough to contend with the best spirit that he could offer. But, it looked like the Principal had other plans.

“Continue Instructor Isilin.”

This man wasn’t very outspoken so he just nodded while looking back into the ring. His opponent that was wearing the silky white loincloth didn’t seem all that afraid. He was just standing there with his hands crossed over one another, his chest puffed out as if he owned the place.

The second round was going to start, with the ground already destroyed Zhang Dong would have to take another approach. The dragon roared out like a maddened beast while opening his mouth wide.

He noticed that a lot of magical energy started flowing towards that opened mouth. It appeared that this monster wasn’t called a dragon just for show. Even though it looked like a mix between a lizard and a frog it apparently also possessed the fabled dragon breath attack.

Normally an opponent would run away and try to hide, other times they would produce some kind of defensive magic to block. On the other hand, the one that called himself the Lightning Emperor remained in place without moving. Even Beatrice that was standing behind him looked worried but her spirit didn’t seem that he was thinking about dodging.

The large mouth opened up wide and a torrent of energy escaped. It was a burst of orange flame that submerged Beatrice’s spirit in fire. Beatrice was a bit to the side but she had to jump back a bit to not get affected by the residual heat. Even while being at a distance she had to look away while covering her face as the hot air was pushed towards her location.

“It’s the fabled Dragon fire breath, is that person alright?”

“That wasn’t a person, it was a spirit! But it probably had to retreat back to the spirit realm, there is no way it survived something like that!”

The young students started chiming in from the side. All of the people that were interested in Beatrice’s progress were here. Both the prince and Isabella were together, the blond lady was looking between the arena and the prince. Her eyebrows were twitching around as she noticed that Ludwig was focusing his attention not on the battlefield but on Beatrice instead.

Soon the whole arena was filled with a cloud of smoke. The dragon continued to spit out fire which caused the ground underneath to melt with some polishing it could certainly look like a mirror. With the breath attack now halted the creature stood with head raised as if proud after defeating an enemy that shamed it.

Before it could relax though it noticed something odd. Someone was chuckling and that someone was the man that called himself Leigong. His form appeared out of the smoke as he took off in a sprint. When his foot made contact with that molten ground that turned into glass, it shattered in a fraction of a second.

The people here had trouble following Zhang Dong’s speed but some of the more experienced masters could see it all. He just zoomed toward the large Land Dragon summon and delivered a swift kick to its chin. Normally no human would even try that, even though this creature looked peculiar it was still a dragon.

It had rock hard scales that covered its entire body. It could repel swords, arrows, and even regular spells without flinching at all. But what they saw here defied logic, the kick went right through these scales and shattered them into small pieces. The huge dragon was propelled upwards by the force of this kick, its front legs clearly shot up as it started to perform a backward flip.

It performed a reverse somersault while causing its summoner to panic. This creature was huge and it was close to falling on him. Isilin was quick to jump back with the assistance of some lesser wind spirits that carried him into safety.

Everyone was baffled by how easy it was for this man to kick the huge dragon back. The teachers and the Principal started wondering what this heroic spirit’s body was made of to perform such a feat. The dark elven lady, in particular, noticed a strange golden sheen that appeared on the man’s foot right before the kick connected.

This wasn’t quite over yet, after the Land Dragon was on its back Zhang Dong jumped up into the air. It was time to deliver the final blow and he had to make it count. He knew that he would need to borrow most of Beatrice’s mana for this but it had to be done. Only if the people saw his true might would they begin to take him seriously.

A rumbling sound of thunder was heard as he rose into the air. Everyone watched with astonishment as the half-naked man turned into golden energy. Lightning and holy energies started gathering into one place before a massive flash of light blinded the audience members.

They opened their eyes to another strange scene, instead of the white-haired man there now was a dragon. It was a disembodied head of a massive beast with scales and horns. Even though it was only the head of Zhang Dong’s soul beast it was many times larger than the Land Dragon below.

This golden dragon opened up his mouth and the people that were keeping watch of this fight started sweating. The Principal quickly rose from her seat while letting her magic power fly towards the arena.

“Quick, reinforce the barrier!”

Every able-bodied wizard in the vicinity lent a hand in reinforcing the protective barrier that kept the audience members safe. Soon a golden beam of plasma descended from the dragon head’s mouth. It connected with the flipped over Land Dragon and caused another massive flash of light.

Everything turned white and the whole place began to shake. The loud noise of crackling thunder and lightning was the only thing that anyone could hear. This last attack signaled the end of this bout, the only thing left after was a massive deep hole in the ground, anything that was in it had vanished into the ether while leaving everyone here with a shocked expression. No one would be able to forget what they witnessed today and the name Leigong would be etched into their hearts for times to come.

Chapter 284

Beatrice covered her eyes along with all the other people as Zhang Dong was performing his attack. She felt rather small and weak the moment the giant dragon head popped out into the outside world. She recognized this as the golden dragon that she saw in her spirit’s soul dimension.

It was unknown to her what this dragon was as it behaved like a dog. The dragon didn’t really behave as the legendary beings that she read about in the books. These giant scaly lizards were supposed to be very prideful, wise, and domineering. This one on the other hand always acted like a big puppy whenever she was over for a training session.

This time around it was clear that this puppy had some sharp chompers. The moment it opened its mouth a giant torrent of golden light connected with the ground below. A massive explosion followed suit but for some reason, she didn’t really feel the impact. A barrier of golden light surrounded her and gave her protection.

The moment the attack landed on its target Beatrice felt weakness taking over her. She could feel most of her mana leaving her along with another migraine coming alone. At this point in time, she was a bit used to this feeling of mana deprivation but she still had to focus, otherwise, she would surely pass out.

After the flash of light subsided everyone could finally see the aftermath. There was no Land Dragon in sight, instead there was a giant hole that filled out two-thirds of this training arena. The instructor named Isilin was passed out in the corner with part of his robe missing due to the blast. He was alive but just out cold.

The people outside the blast radius were protected by the magical barriers that barely survived this attack. This was mostly the case due to the dragon head aiming a concentrated breath attack straight down. The beam of light left a huge pit behind that stretched for an unknown number of meters, the bottom nowhere in sight.

“H-how is this possible?”

“W-was that a d-dragon? A g-golden dragon?”

“Why was it only a head? Why was it so big?”

The students and adults that were gathered here started reacting to what they saw. Zhang Dong used the rest of his energy to summon his soul beast to deliver its breath attack to finish the job. It was all done to be flashy, he knew that dragons were legendary beings in this world. They could also apparently change their appearance to humans, thus now everyone would think that the girl had made a contract with such a being.

‘Beatrice are you all right? I’m sorry I had to use more mana than I previously anticipated. Maybe next time I’ll put on a smaller loincloth.’

‘W-what? Please don’t do that Mr. Leigong…’

Beatrice held her forehead for a moment while taking in a deep breath. She could now see everyone looking in her direction. It was clear that everyone here had shocked expressions. From this point on it would probably be hard for her to be seen as one of the regular students.

‘Don’t worry, he is alive, I was sure not to hit him and just his summoned spirit.’

Zhang Dong said as Beatrice was looking at the passed out instructor. He was thrown to the side and his underwear was visible to anyone that was there. The man was wearing something similar to regular boxers but the coloring was a bit off with all the pink hearts there.

‘Should we head back, or do we need for the instructor to wake up?’

Zhang Dong asked as he wasn’t sure. From what he knew the teacher needed to announce the end of the testing battle. They would then give the young summoner a grade. Regretfully the man that was supposed to do that was out cold.

‘I think we need to wait…’

‘How about we asked that old guy?’

‘Old guy?’

‘Yeah, that Vice-Principal, I bet he could just give you the grade.’

‘T-the Vice-Principal?’

Beatrice responded in fright as asking someone like a Vice-Principal was something a student in her position couldn’t just do. She didn’t know that the old man had met Zhang Dong and was now bound to him.

‘Think they were sitting up in that booth, he should be right next to that dark-skinned elf lady.’

Beatrice looked up to where the Principal was sitting, both she and the old man were there. They were all looking at her as if she was some kind of rare animal. It was clear that Zhang Dong’s little performance left quite the impact.

Still, she wasn’t someone in a position to speak out, the Principal was also a noble and the strongest mage in the whole academy. Her noble rank might not have been of a Duchess but strength-wise she wasn’t far behind.

‘See they are looking at you, just wave them over but if you want I could talk to them.’

Zhang Dong called out while Beatrice started panicking. Coming into this she was already worried about what might have happened. Now she was looking at one of the most influential figures in the whole empire. She wasn’t sure what her summoned spirit was planning but at this point, she felt like he might make things worse.
‘I don’t think I have enough mana for that…’

Beatrice replied while trying to talk Zhang Dong out of it.

‘You don’t need to worry about that, I can take on a less strenuous form, you won’t even feel a thing.’

‘Ah...t-that’s reassuring Mr. Leigong…’

She slumped her shoulders forward after he replied.

“Silence!”

A loud booming voice filled the whole arena and everyone went quiet. It was clearly backed by some magic as it traveled through the whole place.

“Student Beatrice, report to my office immediately!”

The one shouting was the dark elven girl which was also the Principal. Beatrice wasn’t in a position to refuse. Even though she just wanted to go back to her dorm room and lay down, she needed to follow the order.

“Y-yes Principal…”

She replied while nodding as she wasn’t sure if the Principal heard her.

“Please clear this training arena out and someone get instructor Isilin to the priest. The other tests will be moved to another location!”

The announcement continued as the Principal started shouting out orders for the other teachers. The test wasn’t over for the other students but Beatrice was now obliged to follow the order.

After the announcement, the students started leaving this place. Beatrice returned to the room she was previously waiting in. The students that were there were now looking at her with even more astonishment. It was clear that they were acting sheepish, clearly, her show of might was making them more submissive.

“Beatrice Hohenberg of Dawn Lake?”

“Yes?”

A man with a large white beard and of older age was waiting outside. Beatrice knew him as he sometimes made some long-winded speeches. He went by the name Elobarin and was one of the Vice-Principals from this academy. If they went by noble ranks this man would be akin to a Count.

‘Don’t worry, he is on our side, you can go with him. Tell him that the Lightning Emperor sends his regards.’

‘W-why?’

‘Don’t worry, just do it.’

Elobarin looked at Beatrice that came out of the room. She bowed her head before him as a proper lady which caused him to wonder how someone like her was able to possess a special spirit.

“I’ll escort you to the Principal’s office, follow me.”

“Ah yes Sir, also… uh…”

“What is it, young lady?”

Elobarin asked while the two were slowly moving away from the other students.

“Um,... The Lightning Emperor sends his regards?”

She said in a weak voice while trying not to offend the old man. She was having trouble with so many powerful people and beings around her. She didn’t want to offend the Vice Principal but her summoned spirit was scarier. After the training fight she had with the instructor, this fact was cemented in her mind. Even she knew that what Zhang Dong did there was unprecedented.

The moment she uttered the words she could see the old man’s face contorting in a weird way. He looked like he had seen a ghost, the old man almost tripped and fell as well.

“H-he does? D-did he say anything else?”

“Um… please wait a moment…”

The two started walking slowly towards the Principal’s office. It looked as if Beatrice was looking up into the air but in reality, she was talking with her summoned spirit.

“Ah… he said that when we arrive at the Principal’s office he will talk with you both…”

Beatrice and Elobarin both didn’t like this reply. None of them knew what Zhang Dong was thinking and what his true goal here was.

“Is that so… let us continue.”

“Yes, I’ll be in your care…”

Both of them started laughing nervously while moving on. The people continued to whisper each time they saw the cute blond summoner, it was clear that her infamy was slowly starting to spread through the whole academy.

“The Principal is waiting for you.”

A lady was sitting by the desk. She had glasses on and looked very professional. They were finally at the Principal’s office after walking mostly in silence. The Vice Principal knocked on the closed door before going inside.

Beatrice and Zhang Dong could see more than one person inside. Besides the dark elf that was sitting behind the desk, there was a woman in a maid uniform. Beatrice looked out of the corner of her eyes at this person but then turned back to the dark-skinned lady. Zhang Dong on the other hand focused on this person’s ears which were quite large.

‘Is that a cat girl?’

He thought to himself while examining the whole place further. He could also feel that some of his own spiritual energy was still floating around in this room. It was clear that the little safety measure that he attached to the Vice Principal’s mark had gone off here. Some books were still on the ground and the made was in the process of cleaning up.

“Welcome Student Beatrice.”

The elf lady called out in quite the seductive voice while looking at Beatrice. Zhang Dong took note that this woman was quite seductive looking but not quite on the level as his own wife in the curves department. Beatrice performed a proper curtsy before the woman of status while the Vice Principal remained in the back.

“You wished to speak to me, Principal?”

“Yes, you probably know why.”

“It’s about the honorable Lightning Emperor Leigong… he also wanted to talk with you…”

Before the elf could reply or agree to Leigong’s arrival something happened. The mark on Beatrice’s right hand started glowing. The two mages in the room backed away while putting up some magic defenses at this sudden surge of magic.

“No need to worry, This Leigong won’t hurt anyone, unless they wish to do injustice against my contractor!”

A small golden orb of light appeared before Beatrice, the strange thing about this was that this summoned spirit was showing itself without its summoner’s chant.

“Is that…”

“Yes, I am the great Lightning Emperor Leigong!”

Zhang Dong pronounced his name with a thunderclap going off in the distance. Everyone in this room looked at the form that he took on. He wasn’t full-sized or naked, nor was he a body part either. Instead, he looked like a tiny cute action figure of his original self in a white robe, standing at a very imposing ten inches of height.

Chapter 285

A chibi version of Zhang Dong with a somewhat bobble head was floating around the room. This form used up almost no mana as it was small and without much density. The design he went with was one that would make him seem cuter. His face looked quite cartoonish with enlarged eyes but still had some of his old face structure.

The people in the room looked at this ‘Lightning Emperor’ with mixed expressions. Most of them were baffled by the strange look that was inspired by animated movies from his old world. He wasn’t sure if this was the right choice for the occasion but at least he was garnering some attention.

“Honorable Lightning Emperor Leigong?”

After a moment of silence, the dark elf Principal decided to speak up first. Her words were preceded by a cough that caused the Vice Principal to also straighten up.

“I see that your associate has mentioned our encounter.”

Zhang Dong looked at the old man that was standing to the side. The moment he did he could see the Vice Principal’s face twitching a bit.

“Yes, he did inform me about it. I would like to apologize on his behalf.”

The dark elf looked to the side, where the old man was standing. She started wiggling her eyebrows a bit to make him aware of something. This made the Vice Principal move forward and perform a small bow before Zhang Dong and Beatrice that was behind him.

The young girl started flailing her hands awkwardly as she didn’t know how to react to something like this. This was quite the normal response by someone on the lower end of the social ladder like a Baron’s daughter. The person in front of her was akin to a Count and far above her status. Her summoned spirit on the other handheld his nose up high while nodding.

“I’m glad that you understand, I will let this transgression slide but only this once!”

Zhang Dong replied while slowly floating toward the old man. He had scared the old man into submission and he could clearly see the fear in his eyes. Even though he looked like a cute anime character now the man probably saw him as some kind of ferocious creature. He had given him the stick but now it was time for the carrot.

The people in the room could see Beatrice’s spirit moving and reaching out towards the old man’s chest with his tiny hand. Before they could ask what he was doing a strange magical pattern was felt by the two strong magicians.

“T-this… how unique… What kind of magical energy is this?”

The Principal called out from the side with awe. She could feel a small amount of energy moving from that small hand. There wasn’t much power in what this tiny spirit was doing but the mana was different. Soon the purpose of this magical spell was clear as the Vice Principal let out a sigh of relief, the mark that was on him had been dispelled.

“T-thank you, great spirit!”

“I’m glad you understand my magnanimity!”

Zhang Dong laughed out loud while swishing his long sleeves around. He had made a more wavy robe variant with this form which made him look more like a traditional cultivator.

“Vice Principal Elobarin, is the mark gone?”

“Yes, Principal.”

Both of the mages in this room looked at the small floating cultivator. It looked like a big weight was removed from their shoulders. They were probably glad that this strange Spirit Emperor could be reasoned with.

“This was the reason that you called us here right? Or was there something else?”

Zhang Dong asked while floating to the side. There were a lot of books in this room so he started giving them little pokes. While being here gathering more information was paramount.

He also wanted to make these two mages work for him, they were on the top of the totem pole here. They would be able to speed things up, he wouldn’t need to go through the usual child games that would be happening in the classrooms if he did it the normal way.

“Yes, if the honorable spirit is willing to talk with us, we would like to give him some questions…”

Zhang Dong could see that there was a little glint in the dark elf’s eyes. It appeared since he removed that soul binding technique from the man named Elobarin. It was clear that his unique cultivator Qi was different from mana.

After reading up on some of the spells he figured out a way to make it work in this world as well. The conversion rate wasn’t as good as in his old world but there was a way to transform mana into Qi.

With this cultivation would also be possible here but it would take a lot more time. The people cultivating would also find it harder to recharge their energies after performing their Qi dependant techniques. The whole process was akin to emulation and a lot of energy was lost during it. That’s why he was trying to come up with new ways of using his own Qi here, without the need of emulation. Learning magical spells wouldn’t be that easy though so he needed a lot of research material.

“A few questions?”

Zhang Dong started rubbing his chin that was part of his new bobblehead. The two mages started looking to each other with some concern in their eyes.

“I guess I could answer a few questions, are they about those demons that you spoke about?”

Zhang Dong looked to Elobarin. The old man had previously mentioned that there were some shape-shifting demons running around this school here. Maybe if he took care of that problem he would have something to leverage for.

He didn’t want to waste too much time but Beatrice wasn’t strong enough. That attack that he performed with the help of his soul beast didn’t even reach up to the nascent soul level. It was the most he could do at this point in time. From what he could tell this Principal lady was at about the middle or late stage of core formation.

She was apparently the strongest mage in the whole academy while also making her one of the strongest mages in the entire world. How strong was the strongest he didn’t know but it looked like these people haven’t yet taken a step into the nascent soul level of power. Which was good for him as if he recovered all of his strength he could easily flatten anyone here.

“Yes, amongst other things…”

Zhang Dong nodded, he could tell that the woman wanted to ask him about other things more. That look she had was something he was familiar with, it was very similar to what his junior sect members did. They were always trying to get pointers from him who was the most powerful cultivator in the whole sect. She was looking at him like a pupil that was eager to learn.

‘I should throw her a bone but put some restrictions on it…’

He knew that he needed something to trade with. There was not much that he could offer for the information and resources that this academy had. The thing that he wanted to ask for were the cubes. Mages here would probably know some locations where these items could be located. If this world was like his previous ones the cubes had to be in places that previous ‘players’ like him were summoned to. For now, he decided to push the conversation towards the demons as this looked like a problem that could be tackled.

“Yes, I am sure that the great spirit is aware of the age-long battle between the demons and the coalition of races.”

“Mhm.”

Zhang Dong nodded as he went through some of the history books that this place had to offer. The setting looked to be very similar to games or other books that he had read before. It was quite generic, this ‘Coalition of Races’ was composed of various fantasy-like races, elves, humans, dwarves, and some others but those were the big three main ones with the most pull.

These humanoid races were in an aged long battle against the demon race. These demons came in various shapes and sizes but mostly had one thing in common, their red skin, horns, and a third eye right in the middle of their forehead. There were also existences known as the ‘Demon Lords’ along with a ‘Demon King’ that ruled over all of them.

From what the books said this ‘Demon King’ lived in some kind of secluded castle surrounded by rivers of lava. He didn’t leave this castle and only the demon lords were sent out as his generals. There was a certain reason for that.

This Demon King was supposedly the strongest being on this planet. The only reason that he wasn’t able to destroy the other races was a massive barrier that was surrounding a continent where all of the races gathered.

There wasn’t much explained on how it worked, but supposedly it kept the strongest demons out but weaker ones could somehow squeeze through openings in the net. Some of those demons that made it through could get to the level of the strongest people living on this side.

The gist of it was, that the weaker demons were slowly infiltrating these lands and trying to weaken the barrier. Sometimes they succeeded which allowed one of the demon lords to hop to this side. Thus the war continued to this day, the races were holding on for now but they were slowly losing land while the demons closed in.

“Before that, shouldn’t we do something about that?”

Zhang Dong said while pointing at the cat-girl maid that was listening to the conversation while cleaning.

“Don’t mind Gertrude great spirit, she is someone that has worked at this academy for years and we can trust her.”

The maid perked up at the conversation, she was putting some books back on the shelves. She turned around to give the whole room a warm smile that could melt icebergs.

“Is that so? Can you remind me again, the demons mostly have red skin, horns, and a third eye, right?”

“Yes great spirit…”

The principal replied while not being sure where this summoned spirit was going with this.

“That person has a third eye.”

Zhang Dong pointed towards the girl in the maid uniform while staring. He was someone that had a disguising technique that would even fool nascent soul masters. The demons were using something similar so these people that were below the nascent soul level were unable to detect anything. He on the other hand could see behind this disguise, the girl was clearly a transformed being.

“W-what? Are you certain, great spirit?”

“Can’t you check with that technique of yours?”

The cat lady started backing off while looking at the Principal and Vice-Principal. Both of these mages were looking at her in a strange way.

“W-what? Did I do something wrong?”

The principal looked to the great spirit with confusion in her eyes. The maid here was someone that she knew for a long time. She had worked here for many years and her loyalty had been proven but before she could act the spirit moved in first.

“Well, I can do it for you.. shouldn’t be too hard…”

The Principal looked at the small spirit performing some strange hand gestures while pointing at the cat girl. The girl started to panic but it was too late. The strange spell was cast and the girl’s from started to shift.

All of her hair started to fall off along with the cat tail that turned into some black sludge. What remained was a bald lanky humanoid that wasn’t even female in figure. Its face wasn’t pretty to look at and it had both the horns and third eye that any demonic being possessed.

The demon gave out a loud shriek that caused the windows to shatter. It then jumped out through it while the Principal and Vice-Principal were stunned by the reveal.

“You’ll have to catch it yourself though, I think you should hurry up before it calls more friends over or escapes”

Zhang Dong chuckled while floating around, the old man quickly jumped through the window to give chase while the others were left to discuss more in the Principal's office.

Chapter 286

Zhang Dong watched the monster jump out of the window and the Gandalf look-alike Vice-Principal chasing after it. He was lucky that he noticed the cat girl’s transformation technique, this he achieved after he started poking some of the old-looking books.

As always he was looking for information but he witnessed the third eye flickering into existence after he got closer. His power was diminished so he couldn’t spread his senses into the surroundings to scan people. In this form, he was limited to a couple of meters, maybe more if he had Beatrice lend him some mana. Now after dispelling the disguise he had left the poor girl with another headache.

“Would you be so kind as to give Beatrice a mana potion?”

He asked the dark elf lady who was holding some kind of crystal orb. She was already sending out some orders to other teachers and academy enforcers to catch the shape-shifting monster.

“Ahh… of course…”

The interruption didn’t go unnoticed and the mana potion was delivered. Zhang Dong in his smaller form pointed to a nice leather couch to the side while speaking to Beatrice.

“Beatrice, how about you rest there and I’ll discuss a few things with the Principal.”

The blond girl just nodded while drinking the bitter mana potion. It was clear that she was reaching her limit after the stressful day filled with tests and trials. For now, she could take a nap while he maintained his form with minimal mana use.

The Principal looked to the blond lady that followed the spirit’s instructions. It was strange to see a summoner listening to their spirit and not the other way around. It was also strange to see this spirit maintaining his form without the need for the summoner to concentrate much.

From where she was looking the girl named Beatrice was quite tired, a normal summoner would need to concentrate at least a bit for the spirit to remain in the material realm. Otherwise, they would be forced back into the spirit realm. This worked by the summoner feeding the mana into the spirit themselves.

Summoned spirits couldn’t absorb mana out of the world themselves. They needed the help of their contractor to filter the energy for them and then inject it back for them to work. This spirit here was somehow able to either minimize the effect or go around it in some way. The way it changed its forms to suit the mana usage was also something unique, normally a summoner couldn’t just summon a part of a spirit. It was either all in or nothing.

“While your subordinate chases after that three-eyed goblin we can discuss our new business venture.”

“Business venture?”

The dark elf replied while the small white haired Zhang Dong floated on top of her white desk. The two were now looking at each other. The woman had called Beatrice over here to get some answers and have the Vice-Principals mark be removed. Now after that was resolved she was left with many more questions, the biggest one being who this spirit was and how was it so intelligent. It didn’t even feel like a spirit but more like a human.

“Yes, I already showed you some of my capabilities.”

Zhang Dong said while leaning back, his form was smaller so he could sustain his flight with minimal mana usage.

“Now I would ask you for something in return…”

“Something in return?”

The Principal narrowed her eyes as she had never heard about anything like this. Summoned spirits only came to this world to form contracts with the mages. Mana that was abundant in this world was the only thing they were interested in taking. The spirits didn’t make any demands of other people after forming a contract, only when it was broken would they try to find a new summoner.

This one on the other hand was about to make some demands while offering his demon detection capabilities. The elf thought that this spirit was a lot more cunning, more like a person as it understood how to barter.

“Yes, please take a look at this.”

Zhang Dong replied while waving his finger. He produced a few cubes that looked like the ones that he was looking for. The ones that he had found didn’t always have the same shape and sometimes had strange runic symbols on them. He recreated all of those that he came across so the dark elf would have more to work with.

“I need you to help me find artifacts that look like this. They might not look like much but I’m willing to share some of my knowledge and services if you help me find them.”

The cubes that Zhang Dong produced were just holographic recreations of the originals. The Principal looked at them with interest as the runic patterns weren’t something that she was familiar with.

“This…”

“I know that it might be hard but any help would be appreciated, you would have this Leigongs eternal gratitude!”

“I don’t think that I have ever seen artifacts such as these honorable Lightning Emperor… I will have to consult the old scriptures…”

“That is fine, I would also wish to visit places where some old famous figures were first spotted… I think you also sometimes perform hero summoning rituals…”

Zhang Dong knew where these cubes could be hidden. They were probably buried deep underground where no one could spot them. It was normal for the elf to not know where they were.

The biggest problem now was his system that was severely underpowered. The map that he could use to help him scan everything was limited in range. If he was in his nascent soul realm he could just scan the whole planet in a matter of days. It wasn’t that large compared to the place where he lived.

Due to this, he would need to rely on the people here to take him to places where old heroes or sages were first spotted. Those were the most probable spots where one of these cubes could be hidden.

He also had an idea where one of the cubes could be, which would be on the Demon King continent. He had a sinking suspicion that he would find one in the Demon King’s castle or even inside of the monster itself. Similar to how it was inside of the Cthulhu that he faced.

Besides those spots, he also wanted to visit some of the dungeons that this world had to offer. Those were locations where adventurers set off to gain experience and increase their battle sense. Even though this place lacked a leveling system the people somehow increased in strength through battling many monsters.

After going through some books he believed that this place could have some kind of hidden leveling system that people didn’t have access to. Maybe only the people that were teleported here from other worlds would be made aware of that. Everyone sent here most likely had a similar system that he had to help them in their own adventure.

“Hero summoning? Famous figures?”

“Yes like sages of old… powerful kings, emperors, and maybe some heroes that lived long lives? I’m sure you’ll figure something out. In return, I could help you with that demon problem you are having…”

He had stated what he wanted and now it was time to offer something in return. His spiritual sense was several times weaker than normally so he couldn’t just scan the whole school. He would need to examine everyone up close and personal. This wasn’t his problem though as there were ways to go through everyone even with that limitation.

“T-that would be very helpful great spirit… Is this the only thing that you desire?“

“There are some other things, concerning Beatrice. I would like her to have access to the full library and maybe some pocket money for some items…”

Zhang Dong started listing some things that he wanted. Besides the books in the library, he wanted access to most places in the academy. This would probably be possible by having Beatrice achieving the white uniform status. Then he needed freedom to move through the teleportation gates without needing to pay, some money to get potions for Beatrice so she progressed faster. He also needed a pass for her so she would be allowed to travel through the lands unrestrained while not having to attend the tests and lessons.

“But that would cause problems with the other students; they might not accept a Baron’s daughter...”

“I’m sure you’ll figure something out, don’t you want to get rid of all the demons in your school? They could be replacing your people at this very moment, I don’t think you have the time to care about things like status…”

Zhang Dong shrugged while floating around. He knew that people like this adhered to the status quo. This wasn’t something that he was concerned with, the girl had already shown that she was above the rest during the tests. Her receiving a high reward after breaking old records was something only natural in his mind. If the other students complained he could just have them battle him and Beatrice. He didn’t think that he would lose to any of those youngsters in any shape and form. After defeating the instructor he was quite confident.

“Don’t you have some special exceptions for exceptional students? Where the heroes of old not exempt from the social quarrels and bureaucracy of this world?”

“W-well there is one position but I’m not sure if the noble houses will be too thrilled about something like that, I would need to consult with the other Vice Principals…”

“I’m sure that you will work something out!”

Zhang Dong replied while floating back towards Beatrice. The girl had fallen asleep during his talk with the Principal. The stress from the day had finally crept over till she just passed out.

“I will only aid you after you make the announcement, not sooner. I’m sure that you realize that you shouldn’t waste time as your student lives could be at stake here. I’ll be awaiting your reply but for now, I bid you farewell!”

Zhang Dong’s figure started to change into tiny golden bubbles of light that soon faded away into the ether. It was clear that he returned to his summoner while leaving the dark elven Principal in this room with a hard decision to make.

He found Beatrice sitting in a chair in his castle that he had made before. She had awoken in his soul realm automatically after falling asleep.

“Mr. Leigong… what did you discuss with the Principal…”

“Ah you don’t need to worry about it, you should probably wake up and go to your dorm to rest, I’ll send you on your way.”

Zhang Dong snapped his finger which caused Beatrice to wake up on the Principal’s couch. He then watched the blond be very apologetic before removing herself from the woman’s office.

“Hope that Principal delivers, this could hasten up the process tremendously, hope I can find a cube on this continent but I’m not sure if that will be enough…”

From what he knew one cube would only give him like a 30% chance of returning home, if he got two then that number would double. To be sure he would need three but if there were even three of those around here remained to be seen.

“Well, I should relax. I’m sure they will accept my terms. I didn’t ask for that much…”

He said to himself while snapping his fingers, his soul dimension shifted back to a tropical island location as it was far nicer to relax here than at a cold castle.

“Time to play the waiting game…”

Chapter 287

“The entrance ceremony is beginning soon, all new summoners please assemble at the auditorium. Please remember to sit on the arranged chairs.”

A large bird that looked like a cross between a pelican and a parrot gilded above the academy while doing an announcement. All the tests were now over and from the two hundreds of participants only about thirty made it into the prestige class.

This entrance ceremony was mostly there for these students. They would have their names and noble ranks announced to all the other students that didn’t make it in. The ones wearing the black uniforms would have to take note of this as they would more or less be their subordinates in the future.

‘I think we should hurry up, you are the girl of the hour Beatrice.’

At this moment a frantic Beatrice in a brand new white uniform was running towards this entrance ceremony. Due to the way the whole test debacle transpired the girl couldn’t get much sleep.

The uniform that Beatrice was wearing looked strangely familiar to a regular school uniform. It was mostly white with a blouse, blazer, tie, a skirt, and white socks. The whole getup looked more modern and that it would fit into another setting entirely. This only made Zhang Dong attribute this to being another game or fantasy-like world that took inspiration from other works of fiction.

‘They can’t start without the ‘star’ student, now can they?’

Zhang Dong laughed while Beatrice groaned even more. A large shiny badge adorned her new uniform which signaled a certain rank. Each black-uniformed student that came across her stopped to take a double-take before dropping their head. It was clear that Beatrice had gained a special position by being first on the test.

He could almost feel the cold sweat that Beatrice was giving out the moment he mentioned her new rank. It was obvious that the girl was quite nervous about her new status. This was mostly his doing as he petitioned the Principal for more resources.

The only official way of doing such a thing was to give his summoner a special position in the school. This academy had some unique rankings for students that proved themselves to be exceptional. Thus Beatrice was given this position which made her soar above the rest, even above the high nobles and one of the members of royalty.

This was quite the big thing and also something that very rarely happened. Normally a person that was only a baron household would need generations to rise up in the ranks. Even then it was hard to get past the Count's noble rank.

But when a person with enough natural talent and strength appeared then it was slightly different. If the other high nobles weren’t able to exert their status or power over such a person, the only way would be to have them join their ranks instead. Thus Beatrice was given a high position because Leigong the Lightning Emperor deemed it to be.
“If it isn’t the new star of our academy!”

‘Ugh… it’s that guy again… can’t you just ditch him? I don’t like that look in his eyes…’

Zhang Dong complained as after arriving at their destination they were greeted by a certain green-haired youth. It was this country's prince that went by the name of Ludwig. For some reason, he had been poking his head into their business after Beatrice had come out on top.

The youth was behaving strangely from Zhang Dong’s perspective. He was supposed to be the top dog in this academy and even had the highest status around by being part of the royal family. After getting crushed by Beatrice’s results he expected Ludwig to show some animosity but instead, he was showing interest in her.

“Ahh… G-good day your Highness!”

Beatrice panicked slightly and quickly performed the usual greeting that a noble lady would give to a prince. The grass haired prince just chuckled while waving his hands.

“You don’t need to do that, you outrank me in this academy now, you are the star student and not me.”

This was something that came as a perk. Inside the academy, there was a different pecking order that could be enhanced by a student’s grades. Depending on how well they did they could even start ordering high nobles around even when being of lesser descent.

Even if this was allowed by the academy no one would really go through with it. The lower-ranked students were still trapped in the thing called the status quo which was mostly decided at birth. Breaking off from old habits wouldn’t come easy.

“I wouldn’t dare, your highness is still a prince.”

Beatrice started wiggling around rather frantically which made Ludwig smile even more.

“Prince, we shouldn’t bother Lady Hohenberg, she has to prepare for her speech.”

Another attractive looking male stepped forward. This youth was a bit taller than the prince and had a more robust build, his hair was quite reddish-orange which somewhat reminded him of his old friend Huo Qiang. His name was Lucas and he was this prince’s personal bodyguard and a knight. Even though he was a knight he was also part of an influential family that outranked Beatrice in every way.

‘What’s with those hair colors…’

Zhang Dong was a bit suspicious about what this world was. At first, he thought that every person was similar to this carrot and moss head but after further investigation, this wasn’t true. Most people had regular black hair and quite the average looks. Some others like these two had the more unique appearances, it was as if they were important characters in a story that were made to stand out. It looked like the rest of the people in the world were nothing more than filler that were just there to make these people shine.

‘This might really be one of those otome games that I’ve heard about in my old life, never really played them much but could Beatrice here be the main heroine? Wouldn’t that make that other girl the villainess?’

Almost on cue he and Beatrice could feel some killing intent coming their way. With a quick glance, they could see lady Isabella Hohenberg glaring at them from afar. She was mostly hiding behind a wide pillar with part of her head sticking out. She didn’t do much to hide her presence so it was hard not to notice her glare.

“Is that so? Lucas might be right Lady Beatrice, I’ll be looking forward to your speech.”

The prince just smiled while leaving Beatrice alone for the time being. With the two stooges gone the girl that was hiding behind a pillar decided to show herself. She wasn’t alone though as there were two other girls right behind her that were also part of the special students.

“What is that pungent smell?”

“You’re right Lady Anne, it’s the smell of unsophistication.”

The two girls that were behind Isabella spoke out while laughing. It was clear that they were here to cause trouble and were here to cause trouble. Beatrice frowned at the group of three girls as she knew what they were doing.

“What’s with that glare, a Baron’s daughter dares look at us like this!”

This was also part of this world, someone of lower status was supposed to not look directly at someone of higher status. Their head should be down and only moved up when the person of higher status allowed it, very similar to the cultivation world that he was from.

Beatrice on the other hand didn’t seem to be having any of it. She had clearly glared at one of the girls that were from a count's house which normally would cause some problems. The only thing saving her was the fact that she was a star student who had a special rank here. While in school she wouldn’t need to bow her head before anyone besides maybe the instructors and the Principals.

“Why wouldn’t I dare! I am the star student, you should show your respect to me instead!”

Zhang Dong could feel Beatrice’s rage hitting a new high inside. It seemed that this mostly good-natured girl was finally reaching her boiling point. Even more when standing up against her biggest enemy, Isabella from the main house.

He could see the two noble ladies that were laughing at her being taken aback by the reaction. It was true that her special rank overwrote the previous placements but most of the people in this academy would still stick to the old roles.

“Don’t get ahead of yourself, you might be the star student now but how long will you hold on to it?”

This was another thing about gaining the special rank. The student holding on to it would have to be on top of his or her class constantly. If someone else came out on top then the rank would go to them. This was also why not many people took it that seriously as most of the time this rank was passed around between the top 5 students. It was difficult for someone to hold onto it for more than a few months before the next big test or trial.

While Beatrice was angrily staring at the two noble ladies the main villain was just holding a fan in front of her face. Zhang Dong was only reminded of his own wife who liked to carry around similar fans to cover her face. He could kind of tell by Isabella’s eyes that she was having a fun time and probably laughing while her two cronies fought with Beatrice.

‘That little vixen probably doesn’t want to get her hands dirty. It would seem out of place if someone from a duke household was seen fighting with a baron’s daughter.’

The insults continued to fall from both sides and it didn’t seem like it was stopping. Zhang Dong kind of knew what this was all about, the time for Beatrice’s speech was coming out, and if this continued she would be late.

His lovely summoner seemed to have forgotten all about it while getting in a shouting match with these young girls. Normally he wouldn’t care for something like this, he would even think it was fun to watch a little catfight. The problem was that time was of the essence, he was promised more books and more information about potential cube locations. Beatrice also needed to further increase her mana capabilities, without those he wouldn’t be able to fully protect her.

‘Beatrice, you’ll be late just ignore them and walk away.’

The girl was brought back to reality the moment he mentioned that. She gave the two girls one last glare before walking towards the auditorium. The two ladies of course blocked her way which caused Zhang Dong to groan inwardly.

‘Were these young master types always this annoying?’

Before the two could speak another word a burst of golden energy shot forward. It emanated from Beatrice’s whole body and caused the two girls to fall on their butts. The only person that managed to take this slight energy shove was Isabella.

“Who dares block this Lightning Emperor’s path!”

Soon the girls were treated to a rather cute looking version of Zhang Dong that he previously showed off in front of the Principal. The girls were rather stunned at his appearance, he was already able to get to this world on his own even without his summoner’s mana flow. The only downside was that with this forceful summoning he couldn’t exert much of his power. For that, he needed an official summoning from his contract. It had something to do with the laws of this world that even he couldn’t break.

“T-this spirit… is it that naked man we saw the previous day?”

“W-why is it so small now?”

Zhang Dong frowned a bit as due to the nature of this form he wasn’t very scary looking. Most of the people wouldn’t really take him seriously but he had to show up to move things along.

“The next time you block my way, your lives will be forfeit! Now let us depart Beatrice, you have a speech to present!”

The girls looked at the small cute spirit while Beatrice walked away, none of them were sure how to react. Everyone saw how overbearing this spirit could be.

“Lady Isabella… should we follow after her?”

The lady named Anna asked while glancing at the duke’s daughter but the only thing that Isabella muttered in response was.

“C-cute…”

“Lady Isabella?”

“Huh? Oh no, leave her alone… we should get to the auditorium with haste.”

The girls scrambled to their feet while Isabella went ahead, the two not sure why she ordered them to stand down as this was her idea in the first place. Soon every student was present and the long boring ceremony started.

Chapter 288

‘Huh, is it over?’

Zhang Dong called out with a sleepy voice while Beatrice was going down from the stage. The speech that she performed was rather long-winded and took quite some time. He as well as some other students had dozed off during it. He could even see good old moss head and carrot top barely keeping their eyes open.

‘Mr. Leigong… that’s mean…’

Beatrice started pouting while carrying a stack of papers. She had spent quite some time preparing this speech that she was very proud of. From Zhang Dong’s perspective, it was a bit too much. He was also someone that performed some declarations or lectures. Thus he always made sure to make it swift and not divert too much from the main theme. His contractor on the other hand recounted most of the academy’s history while also thanking all the instructors she had studied with.

‘I told you that you made it too long… hope no one will hold a grudge....’

‘Why you!’

He laughed while safe in his soul dimension. It looked like the girl was slowly opening up her heart to him and treating him more as a friend than a great spirit. Being seen as an equal and not as some otherworldly being of power was something he was aiming for. After many years of that in his sect, he was a bit tired of being placed on a pedestal.

‘Now go take your new key and let us depart towards the library, we will be studying a lot!’

One of the perks of being a white uniform was getting a new dorm room. It would be more of a full apartment that she would have to herself. Her old roommate took the news rather well as she now could experiment more without worrying about any poison fumes getting to Beatrice.

The time started to pass, Zhang Dong was sure to use the library pass to get through each book that this place had to offer. There weren’t that many books and scriptures if you compared it to his own sect but for a world much smaller than his this was quite a lot.

His own family was constantly on his mind but he couldn’t do much about it due to his poor state. His power was limited as he couldn’t even map out the area he was in.

In his regular body, he was able to scan everything for multiple kilometers in all directions but now he could barely squeeze out 200 meters. His system just wasn’t working correctly with the limitations that were put on him here.

This left him wandering around the whole academy with Beatrice as his guide. The Principal didn’t get back to him with those special locations so this was the only thing that he could do. One of those dimensional cubes could be in this very academy or even under it.

The problem was that he couldn’t see any empty black spots on his map. Like before the zones where these cubes were at showed up as those black spots. After going through all the places in this academy he didn’t turn up with anything.

“I think that was all of them Mr. Leigong…”

Beatrice called out to him while looking at a large statue of a long-dead hero. Spots like these were visited by him throughout the entire school area. The only places left were outside this well-guarded academy. For that, he would need the permission of the one in charge and that would probably only come after he returned the favor first.

“Mm, let us go back to your class for now.”

There was not much else to do here. Zhang Dong felt dejected as he just wanted to return home. He couldn’t just leave Beatrice though, the girl was far too weak for her current predicament. The other students weren’t looking favorably at her and he had an idea why.

Isabella Hohenberg, she was probably the villain in this story. Her looks also fit with those long drill-like locks that she possessed. She was the typical lady villain that people could read in various stories or games. She continuously ran into Beatrice and him while they were trying to search for some clues or read books.

Sometimes it would be some other students that picked fights with Beatrice. His cute summoner didn’t know it but he had marked this drill blond the last time they encountered her. Zhang Dong knew that she was always sneaking glances from afar while using some kind of hiding spell. It wasn’t hard to spot for someone of his caliber but regular students would find it hard to notice anything.

The ‘bullying’ was quite standard, this whole academy was built like one big high school. The classes were larger with fewer students but the whole feeling was the same. In the cafeteria, they would try to put some diet pills in her food. While there were swimming lessons someone would try to steal her clothes or put tacks in her shoes.

It was all very childish and made him feel bad for the girl that he was contracted with. Luckily for her, she had him around to spot things like this. Though even he started to get annoyed by how these teenagers were behaving. If this continued he would need to punish them in some way. The reason why he didn’t do anything yet was that Beatrice asked him not to. She was far too afraid of the higher nobles acting up if something bad happened to their children.

‘Glasses guy is giving today's lecture but I’ve already gone through the whole library so this will be quite boring…’

The instructor that was giving the lecture was also quite characteristic. His hair was blue and he was quite the handsome young man. He was an elf of an unknown age but his beauty made all the girls in here blush.

‘Together with carrot top, moss head, and glasses guy that would make it three capture targets… there might be another hidden one… maybe an exchange student will also arrive later…’

He was thinking in terms of an otome game now. These people looked quite flashy and were all gathered in one classroom. This all fit in a setting of a lesser noble like Beatrice being stuck with snotty higher nobles.

In games like those the player that was playing someone of lower status would try to befriend the capture targets. Things like events would pop out here and there, then depending on the player’s choice one of the capture targets could come to like her more. In reverse, they could become more antagonistic if they went with the wrong route.

Isabella fit in as the person that was getting in the way of Beatrice’s progress with the capture targets. She was the fiance of the prince which kind of made some of her reactions justified. No girl would like to see their future husband go after other ladies.

This made Zhang Dong look at the prince with less favor. He was already taken but he was still lusting for other women than his own fiance. Isabella was quite the looker but she didn’t seem to be good at talking to this prince of hers.

From what he had seen she remained stoic and reserved while Beatrice on the other hand was more animated. She found it hard to talk to this young pretty boy and the prince looked quite happy at the awkward reactions that she gave him.

‘That prince guy is no good… he is too much of a ladies' man not sure if he is playing dumb or is doing this on purpose… reminds me of ol’ gramps… at least he hasn’t gone over the line yet…’

He was prepared to give the youth a good thrashing if he attempted anything funny. The only problem was that if he did that then Beatrice would have the whole kingdom after her. It would be fine in his eyes to leave this place but he didn’t really want to destroy the life of this young girl.

“So then if the relationship with your spirits increases you will be able to perform spirit fusion…”

The lecture continued, this teacher was also a summoner. Most of the lessons that had been going on now were all theories but later there would be some practical classes where he would also need to participate.

‘Fusion huh?’

Zhang Dong already knew the theory behind this but wasn’t sure about trying something like this out with Beatrice. This technique was a strong one but it put a lot of strain on the summoner. It would increase his power by quite a lot, the problem was the backlash to Beatrice’s own soul.

The summoner needed to be at a similar level as their summon. If they weren’t then the magic-user could be injured as they would need to contain the force given to them. He was already someone far ahead of anyone here, even the so-called Principal that was the top mage here couldn’t reach his toes.

‘I should probably spend some points to see if I could better this technique… maybe with a better grade the strain on little Beatrice’s soul will be lowered.’

“Beatrice Hohenberg please report to the Principal’s office after the classes are finished.”

He perked up at this notification that everyone in the room heard. This class consisted of about fifteen people all of them of high birth and status. Most of them looked with scorn at the blond daughter of the Baron. No one was willing to believe that an upstart like this was taking away their own glory.

‘Good… think we can move things along now…’

Zhang Dong cheered as it was finally time to do some work. He had made an official contract with the Principal of this school. After helping them with finding all the stray demons in this school he would be allowed to leave and check out the world. They would provide him with a flying ship and some protection.

The only problem in this plan was Beatrice that was feeling skittish. This was quite the normal reaction as they would be traveling all over the kingdom. Luckily he had managed to somehow convince her, her mana was improving day by day.

“Hey Bob, go look into that fusion technique will you?”

“Affirmative.”

His system had started to evolve as well, this AI program that he was now stuck with could actually perform some simple tasks for him. He could just tell him to combine skills to improve some techniques and it would carry out the order to his specification. He was still unsure what this program was but he was stuck with it for now. If it would still be there after he got his regular body back was still left to be seen.

‘Let us go, Beatrice!’

After the lecture had ended a little ball of light appeared in the classroom. The students here had been surprised the first time they saw him but now he had been accepted as Beatrice’s unique summon.

“Make way you fools, the Lightning Emperor is coming through!”

He shouted out which made all the snotty students cringe. While they were being rude to Beatrice he made sure to return the favor twice fold. Taking on an overbearing persona was something he was familiar with. Since his little arena bout, he was seen as a powerful summon that shouldn’t be messed with.
“Please Mr. Leigong don’t make a scene…”

Beatrice just blushed while quickly leaving the room. He on the other hand made it sure to glare at each and every person in the room. Though due to his cute appearance it could have been seen in another way.

“You’re no fun Beatrice… fine let us get some demons!”

Chapter 289

A glowing tiny version of Zhang Dong was floating beside Beatrice as they walked through a long corridor. Next to them was the Principal and the Vice Principal that looked like your regular white-bearded wizard.

“So you have everything prepared?”

“Yes, honorable Leigong.”

“No one besides you two and a couple more know what this is really about?”

“That is right, everyone that we trust have already been seen by you.”

Zhang Dong nodded while looking forward. A few moments ago at the Principal’s office, there were more people present. All of them were examined by him and deemed safe to work with. Now they were on the way to a secluded location where the screening process for the demons would be taking place.

“Fine, just remember that Beatrice is not to be seen.”

He looked to the side, his summoner was walking right next to him and going towards a dangerous location. There was no way of knowing how strong the demons here were. The catgirl that he discovered was a minor one that was apprehended by the Vice-Principal. If they others would be that easy to catch remained to be seen.

The most trusted people that the Principal brought over were just part of the staff and not very strong in general. The biggest threat to the students would come from the other four Vice-Principals. They were already posing as strong people of the races, if they were more powerful in reality defeating them would be hard.

“Don’t worry, we would never let any harm come to one of our students.”

“Oh really?”

Zhang Dong thought back to the countless times he saw students bullying other students in this magical academy. Was this dark elf just oblivious to things like this or did she just not care. This also made him think about his own sect and clan.

He was the leader there and quite similar to this dark-skinned lady. Were some of the disciples getting oppressed by the more influential sect members? What could a new member from a lesser clan do against someone from the main Zhang Clan line if they chose to terrorize them? Would any word of this reach his ears? Probably not, he thought.

“Is there a problem, honorable Leigong?”

“No… it’s fine, but you should probably do something about the power dynamics in this school.”

Zhang Dong mentioned to the surprise of the Principal that he still didn’t know the name off. They had finally reached their destination and were greeted by the people he examined before.

This was quite the varied bunch of individuals. There was a bearded dwarf, a smaller gnome, and even some half orc that was almost three meters in height. All of them were trusted retainers of this Principal and also instructors in this academy.

“Is everything ready?”

“Indeed.”

The dwarf answered while leading everyone to a side room. It gave him some law and order vibes, with him and Beatrice being on the other side of the mirror. The room was dimly lit with a large glass window. Through this window, they could look into the chamber beyond it. Inside of it would be the place where the instructors would gather.

These teachers would then be examined by Zhang Dong. If deemed clean they would just continue on with their day, if not they would be apprehended and questioned for details related to demon activities.

Beatrice looked around while the Principal moved over to the glass window. It had the function of two-way glass. The person on the inside would not be able to see what was inside this room while they had a clear view inside.

“Well, this might take a while Beatrice so you might want to keep yourself busy.”

The blond girl nodded while Zhang Dong floated away. There was a chair and some books for her to keep her busy but she decided to do something else. He had taught her some breathing exercises that would push her mana capacity forward. They would also boost her body functions as if she was cultivating a lesser body refining technique.

“Interesting…”

The Vice-Principal played around with his beard while looking at this blond girl. She sat down in a lotus position and started performing a strange exercise. He could see mana entering her body through passages that he didn’t think were possible.

“Interested?”

The old man snapped back into reality after a small Zhang Dong floated over to him. The old man was a bit sheepish around him after he had placed a mark on his soul. Thus he thought the Lightning Emperor was angry with him after he looked at his contractor performing a secret art.

“Relax, I’m not going to do anything to you. We are allies now, if you help me find what I am looking for I could even part with some secret knowledge that just a spirit of my caliber is capable of!”

There was no way of knowing how long this would take. If he promised more rewards these people might prioritize helping him find the cubes.

Finally, the wait stopped and people started entering the room. This whole thing would take quite a bit of time. The magic academy wasn’t as big as a sect from his world but there were still many people here. They were going through every instructor today and being safe by forcing them inside a closed-off room.

“Hm… she is clean…”

The person inside the room looked a bit surprised after walking in and even more, after she was told to leave after a few moments.

“What did you tell them this was?”

Zhang Dong asked while the old lady that was a teacher left the chamber through a different door that she came from.

“That it’s just a standard examination. We sometimes have instructors make a report of their yearly work.”

He nodded and got back to work. The teachers and instructors were ordered to sit by a desk that was close to this mirror. Zhang Dong’s scanning range had been diminished by quite a bit but this was enough for him to notice any third eyes that were being hidden. Even the blue-haired handsome teacher made his appearance but he had already seen him during the lectures so he was clean.

After about an hour the first demon appeared. It took the appearance of an old man that was similar to the Vice-Principal.

“Are you going to capture him here?”

The Principal shook her head while telling this demon to move to another room. There were actually more than one exit from this room.

“Follow me honorable spirit, I’ll be counting on you to dispel the creature’s disguise!”

“Sure, wait here Beatrice.”

He was able to move away from his summoner without feeling any losses in power. For now, it was about three hundred meters but if Beatrice continued with her training then it would only increase.

In the other room, the Vice-Principal was already waiting with two other mean-looking men. The old man that was the demon looked surprised but he wasn’t blowing his cover yet.

Zhang Dong looked to the Principal that nodded at him. He performed the same technique that he previously used on the catgirl and the old man started losing hair and changing into a red-skinned goblin of a monster.

The monster performed a similar scream of anger at the people inside but before it could charge at anyone a magical circle appeared on the floor. This circle started glowing in green color and caused the red demon to drop down to its knees. It was as if gravity was pulling him down and he wasn’t able to move.

Then the two men that were standing together with the Vice-Principal moved in. They placed some kind of collar on this creature that had some strange runic patterns on it.

“Is that?”

“Yes, it’s a slave collar, with it on the demon will have to follow our instructions, the magic in the collar will compel it to act.”

Zhang Dong rubbed his chin as there were versions of this slave collar in his own world. This one seemed to force people to follow the instructions of someone with a special command item. It was mostly a ring or some necklace that the person wore.

The magic item couldn’t brainwash the person that was wearing the collar. It would send painful shocks down anyone’s spine that wore it. It even worked on non-organic beings and could cause huge amounts of pain to anyone. It was possible to resist this collar but a slow death in agony awaited anyone who did that. The collar would also activate whenever a person lied or harbored bad intentions directed at their master.

“Place it in the dungeon!”

The elven lady called out while the creature was dragged out. This made it the second demon that had infiltrated the academy which didn’t bode well for any other institution. This was one of the most prestigious places in the world. A place to train noble magic users, if demons got in here then they certainly would be able to infiltrate lesser guarded organizations.

“I used to play chess with that man…”

The Vice-Principal called out from the side with concern on his face.

“Let us continue… the sooner we get all of those demons, the better!”

“As long as you hold your side of the bargain, I’m all for it.”

Zhang Dong chimed in from the side while the three went back to the room with the two way glass. He wasn’t given much just yet but he was promised a flying ship to visit other regions that could hold the item that he was looking for. The Principal didn’t give him any other good news as she was not able to come up with any cubes.

This was something that he was expecting as regular people wouldn’t really be able to distinguish them from other artifacts. These strange items could be anywhere and they also varied in size. One could be inside some volcano, while another down at the bottom of the sea. The fastest way for him to find them would be to get himself back up to the nascent soul level. Then to just use his map around this globe but this would take some time.

So the scanning process continued. The vast majority of the instructors and teachers came out clean but like the old man before there were some shapeshifters hiding around. The monsters were probably taking over the lives of these people before using the grand teleportation magic to get here.

Their technique was quite good as they could even mimic a person’s soul and DNA to an almost perfect degree. The only reason Zhang Dong was able to see through this disguise was due to his own technique that allowed him to fool even nascent soul masters.

“Hm… you’re not going to like this, but that one is also a demon… and I think it's a lot stronger than the rest…”

What he was looking at now was one of the Vice-Principals. The demon was masking itself as someone at the lower end of core formation but in reality, it was a lot stronger. By how much he wasn’t sure as he was still limited with his senses.

“Well, if it's too hard to handle I’ll be glad to lend a hand… for a little price of course…”

“Price?”

The Principal asked.

“Yes, how about instead of lending me a flying ship… you just give me it. Also some elixirs for Beatrice there would be nice…”

He smiled while the dark elf’s eyebrows twitched in annoyance.

“I’ll think about it, great spirit…”

“Well good luck then!”

A big thumbs up was raised by this small Zhang Dong while the two magicians pulled out their magic staves and got ready for the coming battle.

Chapters 290

“Watch out!”

“Keep it contained, increase the magic output!”

“W-we can’t hold it, it’s going to escape… We need to evacuate the academy!”

“All of you feeble flesh bags will perish within my flames!”

“Heh, this one is a big boy…”

Zhang Dong commented from the side as he was looking at a five-meter-tall horned demon. It had the classical look of a muscle-bound giant with sharp claws for hands. The legs were hooved and it also had the usual red pointy devil tail. It was covered in an aura of demonic flames that was making everyone here sweat.

For the past few hours, they had been going through the testing process. Most of the instructors and teachers came out clean with the occasional red goblin-looking demon hiding behind their skin. Without knowing what this was in reality the demons all followed the instructions and were captured in that magic circle.

It had some kind of demon binding magic infused in itself which was quite interesting. Zhang Dong made sure to add any spells and magical techniques to his own library. He already discovered that these skills could be used by cultivators, he only needed a better way to convert the energies that were involved in these magic arts.

It was going quite well with five goblin-looking demons being apprehended. This was until it was time for the Vice-Principals to participate. There were four others like the gray-bearded Elobarin. They were all at the lower levels of the core formation if he compared them to cultivators.

It started out well, the first one looked like a three-meter-tall man made of marble. It was some kind of special rocky race of this world. It was quite fascinating as this being was more akin to a body refiner than a magic-user. Following him, there was an old lady that had a nice large witch hat and a broom. She came floating in while sitting on it and complained quite a bit.

The last one was a gnome with a long white beard as well, it was clear that the mighty in this world had a certain amount of age to them. The elf Principal that he didn’t hear the name off yet was actually the oldest person here. It looked like these guys were clean but that was until the last person showed up.

The man was similar to the Principal in the way that he was an elf, but a pale-skinned one. He had long golden hair that went down to his waist and a face that would make all the ladies squeal in joy. He looked like your perfect pretty boy but in reality, he was a form-changing demon.

They managed to get him to leave the room with the magic trap but then the problems started. He was a powerful being by this world’s standards so he realized what this room was. Before the trap could be fully activated he revealed his true form by shedding his skin. It looked quite grotesque to see him expand in size while the fleshy skin he was wearing burst forth.

“How did an Archdemon hide itself in this school!”

The witch-looking Vice-Principal called out while throwing some hexes at the red beast. The other high level magicians were informed about what this investigation was about. Now all the four Vice Principals as well as their Leader were facing off against this red monster.

The problem was that this one was an actual demon lord. It was one of the powerful named monsters that was at the great circle of core formation. This posed a problem as all of the magicians that were gathered here were weaker with the dark elf lagging behind this beast.

“You will all perish here! The day of reckoning is coming and I The Lord of Pain Doth'tollen, will pave the path!”

It didn’t look well for the people of the races gathered here. Zhang Dong used his small body to pass through the walls and back into the room that Beatrice was in. His body wasn’t made of flesh and bone but of mana particles. He was more like a spirit than a real person in this world.

“Honorable Leigong, we need to help them!”

“How noble of you but you should think about yourself first, leave it to the adults to handle this.”

He wasn’t sure of the capabilities of the people of this world so the decision was made to let them handle this monster. The person that he needed to protect was Beatrice and not those four adults. His little cute summoner had leveled up a bit since his fight in the arena but she wouldn’t be able to give him enough magic juice to battle this monster. At most he could perform a similar attack like last time before draining Beatrice of most of her mana.

“B-But…”

“No buts! We need to leave, remember our conversation. Your Principal told you to evacuate if any of the monsters get loose and that is what we are going to do!”

Zhang Dong blocked off the path and pointed to the door on the other side. He wasn’t sure how that group of magicians would do but they had reinforcements coming. The alarms in the magical academy were going off everywhere after the demon threat was identified to be one of the demon lord class beings.

“Now let us go!”

He pulled on her hand while using some strength and forced Beatrice to go towards the exit. It was remarkable that she wanted to help out but this was out of her capabilities. On the outside, they needed to get through some stairs and winding corridors to finally arrive outside. On the way, they bumped into some other security personnel that was running towards the room that the demon was being held in.

On the outside, Zhang Dong noticed that people were slowly panicking. The young students were running like headless chickens without knowing what to do. It was obvious that no one really thought that something like an Archdemon could infiltrate this well-guarded location.

If he didn’t come along to take off its hideous mask it would have probably been far too late to do anything. Now on the other hand the people here had a fighting chance. The strongest mages were already trying to contain the monster while more reinforcements were coming.

*Everyone is to evacuate to the magic shelters as practiced, this is not a practice drill, please follow your teacher's instructions.*

A loud announcement was going off on repeat while people were evacuating. Some of the people who heard it were quick to change directions and move towards those shelters.

‘Do you know where those are?’

‘Yes.’

Beatrice nodded and started jogging towards this shelter but before they could get anywhere close to it the ground started to rumble.

“Lower beings, accept your destruction.”

Both of them heard an imposing voice from the area that they left. Soon the whole place started shaking and Zhang Dong could somewhat feel that something was coming.

“Quickly, get to cover!”

He was still in his small form so he pushed Beatrice to the side with a lot of force. This was just in time as the earth below her started to part.

“I’ll bathe in your decaying flesh!”

The demon soon appeared from a large fissure in the ground and it looked a bit different than before. The number of legs had increased while the goat-like lower body was fully abandoned. This part now looked like some kind of fat worm with hooved legs. Its clawed hands were now elongated into sickles that looked black and razor-sharp. Its head was grotesque with a huge toothy mouth and three horns on each side of its large head.

‘Think Mr. Ugly is angry… where are that Principal and her lackeys? Are they all dead?’

Zhang Dong thought while helping Beatrice to her feet. This didn’t bode well for this entire school and the students living here.

‘Did I make a mistake and activate the final boss…’
He had thought that picking out the demons from the masses would hasten his progress. It seemed that his shortcut had a price, one that could cost other people their lives. If he was fully powered this monster wouldn’t be anything special, he could crush it with his pinky. Now on the other hand he would at most be able to injure it if he got a clear shot.

“Lady Beatrice, get behind me!”

His pessimistic outlook on the situation was brought to an end after the ‘cavalry’ arrived. It was the resident moss head prince and his carrot top knight. They had some other students and teachers with them along with their summoned creatures that seemed ready for battle.

‘This is a bad idea…’

Zhang Dong knew that these children wouldn’t be able to do anything about this monster. At most they could stall it till someone stronger appeared. Normally there were some sort of safety measures in place. This place was filled with noble sons and daughters, their parents should have been strong individuals. With time they would probably arrive to save the day but if there would be anyone left around to save was the big question.

Before the monster could charge at them something large delivered a blow to its side. It looked to be some kind of large stone creature similar to what a golem would look like.

“It’s Vice-Principal Varadath! We are saved!”

It was apparently the marble-looking man that he saw previously. He had changed size to match the monster and the two were now pounding away at each other. Soon some of the other Vice-Principals along with the Principal decided to show themselves. Every one of them was somewhat injured with the Witch lady being in the worst state. She was being carried by Elobarin that looked quite pale.

“Prince Ludwig, what are you doing here. Instructors bring the children to the shelter and leave this to us!”

“I can’t do that Principal, not when fair maidens are put in danger!”

Zhang Dong rolled his eyes and wanted to puke after hearing those words leave this young man’s lips. He was dressed up in some kind of emerald green armor and the orange head next to him in a red ruby one. They looked like two shiny gems that would go for quite the amount in an auction.

The Prince was holding a heavy rapier that had also some emeralds on it. He could feel that this weapon was earth grade and actually would be able to wound this red monster if used correctly. That is if it actually had a competent user, this youth wasn’t even around the foundation establishment level.

“It doesn’t matter how many weaklings you bring, you will all know pain!”

The monster gave out a strange wail that caused most of the people to back away. This attack carried some demonic energies with it and Zhang Dong noticed why. Soon every student and teacher that had yet to be apprehended started turning into three-eyed monsters. It was clear that this demon was calling for reinforcements, the battle was only beginning.

Chapter 291

This was a large magical academy with thousands of students and teachers. The people that they examined today were only a small fraction. There was a focus on the teachers this day but the bulk of people was composed by the students. It would have taken them a week or two to go over everyone here but the Archdemon threw a wrench into their plans.

With a loud howl from its toothy mouth the students and teachers that weren’t tested started to change. Every person that was a demon in disguise shed it and started attacking the closest person to them. The monsters were outnumbered but they were much stronger than the youths. These were noble children that were brought up being sheltered by their parents and knights, fighting in true battles wasn’t something that they were prepared for.

“Protect the students!”

“The students in the shelters are turning into monsters and attacking!”

“Activate the teleportation circle, call for the Falconian Knight order!”

Many shouts filled the area as the young students panicked. Some of them fought with the use of their magic while others just ran away in fear. Most of these young lords and ladies failed to stand up to the occasion and just hid away in hopes that others would take care of the demon situation.

At this very moment, the Archdemon was grasping the hands of the stone golem looking Vice-Principal. The red creature had grown another set of arms just for this occasion. It was now holding its opponent in check with those added appendages and pounding away with its pointy sickle hands.

Soon the rocky golem crumbled into dust and the person inside dropped down to the ground. He was in the middle of the chest cavity performing a spell so he wasn’t directly harmed. After the creature caused irreparable damage to his stone form he was now out of energy, still alive but with no power to activate any other spells.

Luckily for him, there were some other magicians out here fighting as well. While the monster was trying to seal the deal long range spells started raining against its back. It turned around while the magical energy bathed its red skin, it was as if it didn’t even care that it was getting hit.

“You insignificant worms, such trifling magics won’t work on the Lord of Pain!”

It laughed and then opened up its large mouth. Zhang Dong had seen this type of attack and quickly signaled everyone to get down. Regretfully he didn’t have much pull here and the wizards continued to fire off their spells.

What the monster was doing was a massive beam attack. The energy condensed into a dark gray sphere close to its mouth before being fired off. The beam wasn’t uniform in size or direction as it burst forth into many smaller beams. The destruction that followed was massive as it melted into the buildings and magic shields that were in its way.

A massive explosion followed suit along with the screams of people that were in the range of the beam and without any protection. The largest of these beams was aimed at the spot where the Principal and others were standing. Regretfully this was also the area where Zhang Dong and Beatrice was at.

“Idiots…”

The dust started to settle revealing a golden glow behind it. Zhang Dong had been forced to use up quite a bit of Beatrice’s mana reserves to produce a big enough shield to protect the people around him. Due to the injuries that those higher level magicians had suffered beforehand, they were slow to react to protect the students around them.

“Thank you, great spirit.”

The dark elf Principal called out while getting off the ground. She was already drinking some colorful potions and her wounds were being healed. The same thing was happening to the other wounded magicians around here.

“Retreat for now, leave this to the adults, Prince Ludwig I will leave them in your care!”

The Principal shouted as the three turned to face the monster. They were quick to bring the fight to the Archdemon, mostly doing it to stall for time.

“L-let us listen to the Principal.”

Beatrice said while wobbling back while also drinking a mana potion. The prince finally nodded and agreed. Zhang Dong wasn’t sure if he realized that the enemy was too strong or if he just took the chance to act as a gallant knight to protect the lady he was interested in.

The group here consisted of moss head, carrot top, and a few other students of various genders. Isabella didn’t seem to be around and neither were any of her ladies.

“Leave everyone in my care, I will protect them! Lady Beatrice came with me!”

Soon a white steed materialized as the Prince performed his summoning spell. The creature that he possessed was the type that mostly increased his speed and wind spells. It could also be used as a mount while not being able to do much damage itself.

“I…”

Beatrice looked at the horse and the outstretched hand. Zhang Dong could feel that the girl’s heart was racing. It was clear that she was thinking some things that she shouldn’t at this dire moment.

‘Just get on the fairy horse…’

She snapped back to reality and finally grasped Ludwig’s hand. She hopped onto the white steed with his help and they were off. The other students didn’t say anything but some of the young women had strange looks in their eyes.

Soon everyone was retreating while the battle raged on behind them. From time to time a red skinned monster would try to attack them. There were even variations of smaller ones that were more in numbers than the people here anticipated.

“It must be the demon thralls, some high level demons can summon weaker minions to aid them in battle.”

The carrot head knight said while pushing his sword through an imp looking monster’s head. Zhang Dong was made aware of this as he could feel a lot of strange demonic energies popping up all around them. The so-called Lord of Pain was apparently summoning more monsters to help him in battle. There also could have been specialized demonic shamans calling those monsters over here.

For now, Zhang Dong decided to manage his powers. The students looked to be capable enough to take care of these lesser demons. Unless a tougher enemy showed itself he wouldn’t make a move.

‘Can those guys defeat that ugly demon?’

He thought back to the Principal and her aids. They were all in the core formation realm when it came to power but the monster outranked them all. He wasn’t sure if this magic academy had any precautions in place for demon attacks. It looked like it didn’t, it was hard to get in but it was also hard to leave.

The people running this place might have been a bit too prideful. They were so sure that no strong Archdemon would be able to sneak inside that they were lax with the defenses. He could see some mechanical golems running around but they were all at the foundation establishment level of power.

It didn’t seem like anything here was strong enough to handle this threat but he himself also didn’t have enough juice. If he could tap into his old core formation level of strength it would be enough, he just needed it to last for more than one attack.

“Prince we are here… but…”

They arrived at one of the shelters but the door was busted open and the magic circles that were used for the mana shield were scratched up in various places. There were traces of battle and even some dead bodies of young students and red monsters.

‘Damn…’

Zhang Dong looked at some of the dead bodies with worry. He wished that he could help these youths but there was only so much he could do in this situation by himself. It was impossible for him to just set off on his own and get to all of these crimson monsters. There was also the problem of keeping his host Beatrice safe and he didn’t really trust this prince to do a well enough job.

“How about we try the teleportation platform?”

Carrot top gave some advice and the people nodded. Using the teleportation magic to flee would be a good idea but Zhang Dong had a suspicion that it wouldn’t be that easy. While the whole place continued to rumble they moved onto the next building. During their escape, they came across other students that joined them.

Slowly the youngsters led by the green haired prince battled their way towards the teleportation circle. Zhang Dong was surprised how the others were to quickly fall in line, the moss head apparently had enough fame to make everyone submissive and follow his orders.

When they arrived at the spot where the chamber to the teleportation circle was supposed to be they discovered a collapsed entrance. There were even imps running around and attacking some of the teachers that were trying to get inside.

“Did the monsters get to it before the instructors could call for help from the Falconian knight order?”

“Impossible!”

The students looked at the scene with horror in their eyes. It looked like combat was the only option now.

‘What should we do Mr. Leigong?’

‘Probably better to stay in the group, there is strength in numbers.’

“Okay everyone let us split up!”

Ludwig proclaimed while waving his fancy heavy repair around. In the young man’s eyes, it was best to split up and search for survivors and other possibilities. Zhang Dong knew on the other hand that this would just let the smaller number of monsters attack one of these groups that was diminished in numbers.

“You there grass hair, I don’t think that would be a smart idea.”

He decided to speak up, leaving things in these kid’s hands would only bring more harm to them. There was one way of them getting out of this alive and it would require all of these youths to work together.

“G-gras hair?”

The prince looked to the voice that spoke out and could see a somewhat smug-looking small humanoid spirit floating towards him.
“This spirit of yours has quite the mouth, Lady Beatrice…”

The knight with orange hair commented from the side while getting between him and Zhang Dong. The other students looked at this lightning spirit in disdain for calling their heroic prince in this way.

“Silence!”

A loud crackle of lightning brought the attention back to Zhang Dong. Even in his depleted form, he was the strongest person here. The Prince was close but still not in the foundation establishment realm of power. When he released some of that spiritual pressure the kids started buckling under it.

“If you want to save your friends, you will do exactly as this Lightning Emperor orders! Now someone get some chalk, we need to draw a magic circle!”

After going through the magical books in the library he had come across a peculiar spell circle, one that could aid him in temporarily regaining some of his lost power. If it would work depended heavily on the youths here.

“With haste! We don’t have much time!”

The thunder sounded off again before the students got in gear, it was time to perform some magic.

Chapter 292

“Are you sure we should be doing this, Prince Ludwig?”

“Lady Beatrice’s summon was somewhat convincing… if it doesn’t work out we could…”

“Hey, Carrot top, Moss head, be quiet or I’ll zap you again!”

Zhang Dong shouted out from the side while finishing up with his drawing. What he was producing was a combination of a magic circle and an array formation from his own world. He was aiming for something similar to a spirit gathering array that caught ambient Qi from the surroundings. The only difference was that this one was using mana instead.

This circle would also be using all that mana to fuel the central person. It was very similar to the defensive and offensive formation that multiple cultivators used. The same ones that his clan used during the sacred ground that would boost their fighting prowess.

“That should be it… now as I said previously, gather at those locations.”

There were about thirty people here, they were all students. They looked at each other sheepishly but followed the instructions. Zhang Dong was acting in an overbearing way but had also promised that with this magic circle he would be able to help the teachers.

*BOOM*

A loud explosion sounded in the background followed by a magical tower collapsing. The self-proclaimed Lord of Pain was battling it out with the best magic users and knights that the academy had to offer. They were somewhat holding it back but for how long no one could tell. The monster was clearly stronger and without any reinforcements coming any time soon the outlook was bleak.

“Don’t get distracted and sit down in the lotus position, follow my instructions and you will all be safe. This is what I, the Lightning Emperor promise all of you!”

Zhang Dong tried to reassure the kids that had fear in their eyes. Luckily for him, people tended to believe spirits around here. Apparently, a spirit that would break a promise would be somehow punished by the laws binding this world. He wasn’t a spirit though so using a little white lie to get things done wasn’t above him.

Using his small form he presented the sitting position that the youngsters should take and continued with the explanation.

“Yes, now close your eyes and breathe in. The array formation will assist you in gathering the plentiful mana from the surroundings, just let it flow through you and into the formation! Yes, just like that!”

He was glad that everyone here was somewhat competent in pulling mana out of the air. It was a school filled with magicians and taking in mana was something that they learned from a very young age.

“Beatrice, are you ready?”

“Yes!”

The blond girl nodded while also sitting down in the center of this magical circle. All the other people were around her in circles. The outermost students were the weakest while the closer to the center the stronger a person was. Due to this, the prince and his knight were the closest to Beatrice as they did have the highest mana reserves from this group.

A faint blue light filled the area and the giant magic circle that was composed of many geometrical shapes started to light up. Inside those shapes were peculiar-looking runes that started to glow brightly in a golden hue. Soon the outer circle was glowing brightly and the array was starting to activate.

‘Now listen up Beatrice, you are just the conduit. Don’t try to absorb any of that mana or you will sustain damage. Let it flow through you and I will take care of it.’

The girl nodded while trying to relax. Soon the two young men close to her were also concentrating on absorbing the mana and pushing it towards the person in the center. The moment the circuit was complete Beatrice felt a massive surge of energy rushing into her very soul.

‘Yes, just like that, let the power flow through you and into me…’

Zhang Dong was waiting for this moment. His small body started glowing in the usual golden glow that was far brighter than before. His form started to enlarge as he took on his full shape. Long white locks, a chiseled chin, and rippling pecs all behind his usual white robe were materialized.

He gripped his fist strongly and let the lightning energy flow through him. The arcs of blue electricity started going around his whole body as he tried to gauge how much power he was able to output.

‘... Great circle core formation at most… this will have to do…’

“Everyone, stay here. You will all be protected by my lightning, keep this formation going and I’ll take care of that demon.”

After nodding he materialized a protective barrier around the whole magical circle. Soon he was flying away towards the demonic being that caused it all on his mind, the Principal and her aides. He wasn’t sure if they would still be alive at this point, he could only hope that this would be enough power for him to get rid of that monster.

…….

“Was that all? The people of the races are unworthy to face the king if this is all they amount to.”

A grinning demon was looking at the defeated magicians that had faced off against it. For a moment they were able to hold him off but after running out of mana they were nothing but dead weight.

The crimson creature was now looking at the dark elf that was all bloodied up. Her companions were to the side, some of them missing limbs after getting them cut off by the sickle arms. If they were still alive was unknown but even if they were, their faith had been sealed, no one would be walking out of here in one piece.

“Are the demon lords always so chatty? Just finish it you bastard we will never surrender to demonic scum like you!”

The Principal spit out some blood to the side while looking with avarice at the ugly monster. She knew that even if reinforcements arrived it wouldn’t change anything. It would take several duke level magicians to defeat this monster, maybe only the current king could face it off in a one-on-one battle.

“Death by my hands is a blessing. I will reap your souls and present it to the king as a token of my devotion.”

The monster opened up its toothy mouth as wide as it could. A gray ball of demonic energy appeared in front of it and increased in size as the attack gained in power. With nothing more to do the elven woman closed her eyes. Thoughts of simple days in her youth filled her head and caused a single teardrop to form that combined with the blood on her face while it dripped down.

“Oh no, you don’t!”

Before the attack could go through a familiar voice was heard by her. Baffled by it she opened up her tired eyes to witness a man in a white robe kicking the large mouth of the red monster upwards. The sheer force behind this kick forced the beam attack to shoot up while also shattering some of those pointy yellow teeth in the process.

“T-the spirit?”

She called out in surprise as the massive demonic beam shot up into the air and split into many smaller beams. It looked like gray stars were raining down from the heavens. Soon those beams collided with the ground and caused many small explosions around their location. Luckily there was enough space between them to not cause any casualties.

“He really didn’t pull any punches…”

Zhang Dong had appeared before them, his aura filled the area and caused the monster to buckle backward in surprise.

“Who dares?”

“I dare. You damn overgrown caterpillar!”

“A lowly astral realm being? I will eradicate your existence from this realm!”

The monster released its aura causing the rubble to shake. Every person that was close by could fear an overwhelming aura of evil moving forth. The moment it collided with their senses they were paralyzed with fear, unable to move or even scream for help.

“Don’t think you’re the only one that can do that.”

Zhang Dong’s eyes glowed in a golden color and his entire body shone. Several bursts of light started shooting out from his form. These rays enveloped the whole area and bathed everyone in its protective light.

“W-warm…”

The downed elf muttered while basking in the warm holy energies that Zhang Dong was giving off. There was a small healing property to this golden aura that was coming from the Lightning Emperor. Even though it wasn’t all that much it was enough for the Principal to get to her own two feet and go for a healing potion.

“What is this disgusting energy… it burns!”

A wail of anger and pain could be heard from the red monster. The holy element was doing wonders against this monster’s skin that started to melt from just being near him. It wouldn’t be that easy, when the monster noticed his opponent's aura it coated itself with its own to repel the holy element that was being used against it.

“Lowly astral being, accept your demise!”

The monster charged forward with its massive body and many legs destroying the ground below it. The sharp appendages that were once its arms had multiplied and were now slicing the air around while coated in some dark energy.

“Accept this!”

Zhang Dong didn’t just stand there and do nothing. He closed his hand into a fist and condensed a sword of light. This was one of his first techniques that he didn’t use in quite some time. With the added bonus of his holy dao the thunderlight sword looked like a spire of golden energy.

A clash between light and dark commenced. The creature swung its many blade arms around while breaking the sound barrier. With only using one hand he started batting away those attacks with the help of his energy sword. Sparks flew and more dirt was kicked up as these two beings of power clashed with each other.

“U-unbelievable…”

The Principal muttered while slowly moving away from the battle zone. She had found the Vice Principal with the bushy white beard with a missing foot and was slowly dragging him away.

While running away she had turned to the fight to see the spirit clashing with the monster. Leigong was far stronger here than he was during the arena match, she didn’t know where this boost of power came but this was the best moment to reorganize.

The whole battle was now taking place in a different location than where the monster exposed itself. While slowly limping away the Principal came across one of the students shivering behind a large pillar. The characteristic drill hair made it obvious who this person was

“Why are you still here, you should have evacuated a long time ago!”

The blond lady looked to the bloodied dark elf with wide-opened eyes. After looking around for a moment she seemed to have made up her mind as she approached the two injured people.

“L-let me help you.”

Normally the Principal would tell the child to just run, but she was far too tired and injured. Any help at this point would be appreciated.

“You have my gratitude, we must escape towards the inner parts of the academy while the spirit is keeping the Archdemo…

Before she could finish the sentence a beam of demonic energy flew right towards the three people that were evacuating. Yet before this attack could connect with them a friendly white-haired Lightning Emperor swooped in to save them.

“You’re not very good at getting away are you…”

The small group of three was enveloped by a warm golden shield together with the spirit inside. His eyes glowing and flickering with lightning energy. The battle was not over quite yet as the monster's scream caused everything to shake and crumble.

“Your end is nigh!”

“This might be harder than I thought…”

Zhang Dong muttered to himself while looking at the monster that was healing itself with its own demonic energy. His own on the other hand was running out, the students left behind to act as his batteries were probably not able to hold on anymore. He needed to finish this fast or else it could be the end for everyone here.

Chapter 293

People were floating around in a bubble while being slowly healed by Zhang Dong’s holy energies. He had moved forward to distance himself a bit while facing off against the red demon.

The situation didn’t look so good at his end as he could feel that his power was fading the more he remained in this world. The young students that he had left to lend him power were transferring less and less of it his way.

There was also the problem of too many unconscious and injured people around him. With them here he couldn’t really let loose any unconcentrated attacks in fear of killing someone in the process. This was also why he was using his thunderlight sword and facing the monster in close quarters combat. This technique was made of holy energy so it worked quite well against a demon like this.

‘I need to get them out of here first…’

“Listen up, I’m going to send you all into one location. There you will find my summoner, if you wish for me to defeat this demon you must lend her your mana.”

“Lady Beatrice?”

The one that asked was Isabella, the big drill-haired bully.

“Yes, that one. It would be nice if you forgot about your misgivings about her and lent her your power. ”

Zhang Dong gave the girl a big manly smile before looking down at the Principal. She was the strongest mage here and also had the most mana. If she somewhat recovered and added her mana to the array formation that he created there would be a chance.

“I…”

The young blond lady opened up her eyes wide and it looked like she was thinking about something. There wasn’t much more time for chit-chat as the Demon Lord of Pain was now charging their way.

“Death will be your salvation!”

Zhang Dong rolled his eyes after having heard enough edgy one liners from this guy. He used a big chunk of his energy to pull every bruised and battered body towards the energy sphere. This caused some discomfort for the previous people within it but not like they could protest.

“Now go!”

With a little shove, they flew into the air as he aimed to place them somewhere close to the mana gathering magic array formation. Right on cue the monster was there, attacking with his many sickle-like hands. This time around he found it a lot harder to bat them away as his cultivation realm was regressing below into the late stage.

“I must keep my distance and stall for a bit…”

He was mad that no one in this academy was able to actually do anything about this demon. This also made him think back to his own sect grounds. Without his system’s detection ability some spies could make it through the cracks. There were the scanners but they weren’t at all locations and one rat or another could always make it through.

“Tch… screw of!”

The golden sword of light shone brightly as he brought it down on his enemy. He utilized one of his slashing attacks from his own swordsmanship style. Thanks to having reached sword heart before it gave him enough advantage to keep up even in a lesser realm of power.

“Your power is fading spirit, soon you shall succumb to pain!”

With the high-powered slice, he had managed to shove his enemy back. He even managed to slice through one of those bladed hands. Regretfully with time, it would regenerate itself back to its original form.

“Yeah well… your breath stinks…”

‘Hope they make it there in time…’

He jumped to the side to evade another one of those beam attacks and the battle continued. Back at another location, a group of people were rolling in a big ball of light. This ball burst like a soap bubble to reveal many injured and unconscious people along with the Principal.

“Is everyone okay?”

The elven woman called out, the people that were conscious started groaning. Some of them were able to stand up while others remained silent. It was unknown how injured everyone was but there wasn’t really any time to care for everyone. The battle was still not over and the Archdemon still remained.

“Principal, I’m sure my father will arrive soon.”

Isabella commented while gathering herself to her own two feet. During the whole ruckus, she was separated from other people that she knew. The girls that used to hang around her were quick to run towards the shelters without even waiting for her.

“The Duke? … let us hope so…Elobarin, can you walk?”

“Give this old man a second…”

The Vice-Principal was also here, he was missing a foot but after casting a spell green energy started condensing towards this injured spot. The man didn’t grow a new foot but a one that looked to be made from wood. It was clear that this procedure wasn’t anything comfortable as his eyebrows twitched in pain.

“That should do it...what is that?”

He pointed into the distance where a strange light was coming from. After a moment other people started to notice it too.

“Didn’t that spirit say something about this? Could that be where student Beatrice is?”

Leigong the spirit had given them some vague instructions. They didn’t really know what he meant by lending Beatrice a hand. They were slowly running out of options, the most powerful magicians from the academy had been defeated. If Leigong didn’t come to their aid the group of people here would have been already dead as well.

“It is possible, we should investigate.”

The old man said while producing a wooden cane to help with his prosthetic leg.

“Please everyone, help the ones that can’t walk we must move.”

After nodding the Principal moved forward along with the others. There were enough able bodies to help the other people on the way. When they arrived at their destination they noticed the large glowing shield and the students inside of it. Some of them were on the side and clearly passed out. Others were barely keeping up while panting.

There were also some charred bodies of what looked to be small imps and demons before the magical barrier. It was clear that they wanted to penetrate inside of it but were burned to a crisp during the attempt.

“This must be it… fascinating. What is that magic circle… it is gathering mana from the surroundings and focusing it into the middle...”

The elven Principal commented while the people here moved forward. Every mana and health potion that could be used was now emptied. While some people from the group tried to regain their senses others approached the large mana gathering array that Zhang Dong made.

“He said to lend his summoner mana?”

She looked inside this barrier and could see Beatrice in a sort of trance sitting in the middle. It was clear that the girl was taking in the vast amount of mana from the surroundings and channeling it somewhere. It looked like it was going towards the astral realm where her spirit resided; this was also probably why its power had increased by this much.

“Is it wise to give up our mana? Shouldn’t we evacuate and wait for the Knights or the Dukes to arrive?”

“Y-yes, we should evacuate. Why are we even here?”

Some of the people from the side started calling out to the Principal as staying alive was the priority. None of them wanted to waste this opportunity to get away, no one actually believed that the spirit that helped them could beat an Archdemon.

“I think we should listen to what the spirit said…’

Isabella commented from the side while some of the instructors were shouting between each other.

“Silence! Don’t you feel ashamed for yourself? Act like adults.”

The Principal was mad that the instructors and teachers in this school that were hand-picked by to be the most talented were so cowardly. Everyone here was a noble, so she feared that they were used to the easy life too much.

“We will aid the spirit while we wait for reinforcements, not like there is a place to hide. Look around you, the academy has been mostly destroyed.”

She proclaimed while touching the golden magic barrier that was protecting the students inside. The others looked at this with fright due to the dead monster bodies close to the barrier. It looked like this magic was highly destructive and could hurt anyone that was touching it.

“Calm yourselves, this isn’t that type of magic...look.”

The moment she made contact with the golden light her hand just passed through. It looked like it was fine for people to go inside but not for monsters.

“I see… this is how it functions. Listen up, this magical circle will absorb your mana into it. Replace the collapsed students with haste before…”

The moment that she uttered those words a sound of a thunderous explosion could be heard by everyone here. The people turned to the direction of the noise to see a glorious Leigong flying their way. He was bouncing off the ground like a ragdoll and crashing into everything though. Ending his voyage by sliding for about fifty meters and making a small crater.

“W-why are you taking so long…”

The spirit groaned while grasping his head. He wasn’t looking well, there were visible injuries all over his body and mana was leaking from them. Spirits from the astral realm didn’t really bleed like people from the material realm. They would leak energy that they were composed of in the form of bright-colored energy bubbles. Even though Zhang Dong was slightly different his current body was also composed of various energies.

“Your end is nigh, astral creature!”

The demon lord was not far behind and he could clearly see the large array formation that was glowing in the background.

“What is this disgusting energy? Begone from my sight!”

“Shit…”

It looked like the plan had failed. The people that he shot over to the mana circle that he created to help him regain his strength were scattering to the sides. The only person that actually entered it was the Principal but the others were now running away for the hills. If he got an injection of power now then he might have stood a chance but it didn’t look like the monster would give him any time for that.

The demon lord took aim once more, this time with a more concentrated beam. This monster seemed to not tire or run out of mana at all. It was now seeing the array formation as an eyesore and ready to destroy it along with the students and Beatrice inside.

Zhang Dong jumped to put himself between them and the monster’s beam attack. Everything went bright as his holy energies and the demonic ones collided with each other. The massive torrent of pressure tossed everyone in the surrounding back while they screamed for help.

The monster grinned after looking at its opponent that even managed to injure it a couple of times. Zhang Dong was slowly fading away, his energy had run dry and even Beatrice was slowly losing consciousness. It looked like it was over for him but he had to somehow get the kids out of here.

‘Can I toss them away from here… but this monster will follow after them anyway…’

"Thus begins the slaughter!"

The monster laughed but then something strange occurred. Isabella Hohenberg during the confusion had made it inside the mana gathering array and was now right next to Beatrice. She looked quite serious as she went down to her knees and grasped Beatrice’s hands together with her own.

Isabella closed her hands and started focusing. It was clear that she wanted to aid Zhang Dong with her mana but at this point, he knew that it wouldn’t be enough. That was what would have normally happened but for some reason, the two girls started glowing in an even brighter light than before.

“What is this?”

Zhang Dong was baffled by the strange light show that he was seeing. This wasn’t all as he could feel his energy returning to him in truckloads. The hands that were fading away just a moment ago took shape and all the wounds that he suffered were mending themselves.

“Is this the fabled power of friendship? I thought those girls hated each other though…”

The monster released another burst of multiple beams as it noticed that something was wrong. This time around there was a change. Zhang Dong just waved with his finger and it looked as if time stopped. The beams that were about to collide with multiple targets stopped in the air, not budging a centimeter.

“You had your fun, now become a good punching bag for me!”

Zhang Dong cracked his knuckles as he charged forward, he wouldn’t let this sudden boost in power be wasted.

Chapter 294

A whirlpool of bright golden energy surrounded two blond-haired maidens while people watched on from the sides. The moment they touched a sort of trans took them over. Their bodies were now floating up in the air while the two young girls were holding their hands together, not letting go as they spun around in place.

Not far away from the girls was another person that was going through a transformation. The Lightning Emperor Leigong that was about to fade away was just getting his second wind. His body was reconstructing itself as many tiny wisps of energy condensed onto him.

“Not sure how this is possible but I’m not complaining…”

“How could this be… what is this wretched light!”

Zhang Dong had now stopped the Archdemons attack that he shot out through its mouth again. The dark rays were frozen in the air while he kept his finger pointed forward.

“Be turned to cheese!”

With a small flick, the demonic energies did a U-turn and shot towards the creature that fired it off. The monster put up some defenses but the demonic rays managed to do some damage. This damage was fast to close up as this creature’s vitality was quite high.

“You can’t regenerate if there are no particles left to regenerate…”

A massive spike in holy energy caused the whole academy to rumble once more. This power was many times above whatever the Archdemon could output and left the Principal and other magicians in awe.

Zhang Dong wanted to end this fast with the strongest attack possible. How long his new power boost would last was unknown, he needed to use this energy before it ran out.

“This matters not astral being, you will fall like the rest!”

The ugly monster wasn’t having any of this as it charged forward once more. If the ranged attack didn’t work then maybe close range combat would seal the deal. Unfortunately for the Archdemon during his charge, its opponent vanished for a split second.

“Think fast!”

With a swift kick to the face, the Lord of Pain was sent tumbling into some buildings. This kick was packed with holy lightning energy causing the monster excruciating pain, its screams were quite audible to everyone here.

What followed was a one sided beat down. The denizens of this world looked on as the white haired Leigong kicked the huge demon around as if it was a football. There was no end to the hits and the creature had no way of countering the faster opponent. Soon it found itself floating up in the air with many shattered bones and broken teeth.

“yOu...sHaLL… pErIsH...bY…mY…hAnD”

“Not if you perish first.”

Zhang Dong first had to incapacitate his enemy. With swift kicks and punches, he had caused some surface-level damage to make the monster’s regeneration to kick in. He had noticed that during this period the monster would lose most of its speed. The last part was flinging it up into the air as it didn’t possess any flying capabilities that he was aware of.

There was also the bonus of making the monster crash into the giant demon repelling barrier that this academy was surrounded with. This protective bubble was just what he needed to keep this monster in one place.

When the creature connected with this shield he could see the demonic energies and it counteracted each other. It was causing it some harm but it wasn’t enough to kill it. This type of barrier was there to keep things out and not to destroy them.

“Okay, wait there, this is going to be a big one…”

Another light show was started that piqued everyone’s interest. The spirit named Leigong turned into a large sphere of energy that started expanding in all directions. This energy egg started floating up while constantly growing in size till a cracking sound was heard.

“By the gods… what is that?”

“C-could it be…”

The stunned magicians below could see a giant webbed wing appearing from the torrent of bright energy. It was truly gigantic and followed by another one to the other side. Soon a large golden dragon head was seen by everyone. The people that witnessed Zhang Dong’s arena fight remembered this head but not it was attached to the rest of the flying beast.

“A-ancient D-dragon?”

“How is it so big?”

The Principal and Vice-Principal called out with wide-opened eyes. The large dragon that they were seeing was at least fifty meters in height. The wing spawn was even larger which made this majestic creature look even bigger than it already was.

Thanks to Beatrice and Isabella, Zhang Dong was able to reach a state of half-step into the nascent soul. With that, he was now able to manifest his soul beast out into the open. He chose it as it possessed quite the ferocious breathing attack that worked wonders on demonic beings alike. It was backed by holy and lightning energies as well as plasma, this would make quick work of this Archdemon.

“iMpOsSiBlE! HoW cOuLd oNe oF tHe oLd oNeS sTiLl bE aLiVe?”

The Lord of Pain shouted while fighting against the magical barrier that was keeping him from regenerating fully. Regretfully for the red monster, it was too late for him to flee. His opponent in the form of a golden dragon was already charging up his breath attack.

‘Ancient Dragon? Old One?’

The names that were getting thrown around made Zhang Dong raise a brow while looking at his soul beast taking aim. It seemed that his soul beast’s form was quite popular in this world. Maybe thanks to this he would be able to gain some notoriety, luckily for him, most people liked golden holy element dragons.

With a final burst of energy, the dragon moved its head towards the trapped opponent. It opened its large maw to release a torrent of heated plasma and holy energies. It looked like a giant beam of sun radiation shooting out of the dragon’s toothy mouth and it was on a collision course with the Archdemon.

“iNcOnCeIvAbLe… hOw cOuLd I… mY kInG…”

The monster was unable to dodge while being affected by the academy’s large protective barrier. It was bathed in sun-like flames of Zhang Dong’s soul beast, the particles that it was made from quickly evaporated into nothingness. The demonic energy that was shielding it previously didn’t even last for a second.

He made sure to perform the attack for a bit longer. During his travels, he had come across many monsters that could regenerate themselves. Without making sure that the monster was really dead he wouldn’t feel comfortable.

‘I think it's dead… I can feel that its demonic soul has been erased… but what is that?’

Zhang Dong had traded spots with his soul beast and was temporary in his own soul realm. His little Ai helper Bob flew over as it also discovered this item.

‘Nuclei signature detected’

It started glowing red as he had told it to alert him whenever it found anything about the cubes. It would seem that it was inside of this monster for some reason and it couldn’t be harmed by his dragon’s breath.

“That’s enough, I’m coming out…”

He needed to look at this with his own eyes. The energy that he was given was now slowly fading away, there wasn’t much time before he would be forced to take a backseat once again.

The people that were looking up had to avert their eyes as the dragon’s breath was far too hot and bright. When they glanced back up they could only see the large dragon vanishing and Zhang Dong appearing out of the blue. For all intents and purposes it looked like he was the dragon while in reality, it was just his soul beast switching out with him.

While the people were in a state of shock and awe and before the unwelcome guests that he also noticed came over he decided to grab the item he was looking at.

‘It looks corrupted…’

What he was holding wasn’t a cube but a dark crimson gem.

‘Is this really it Bob?’

His Ai companion started beeping after a little ding he gave an answer.

‘Affirmative, this is a portion of a Nuclei but it is incomplete. Should I begin the absorption process?’

‘It’s not complete? How better are my chances of getting home… my own sector after I absorb this thing?’

‘Calculating… 5,1%...’

He frowned after hearing that, before Bob told him that one full cube would give him around a 30% boost in the chances of getting back to his family. This incomplete nuclei on the other hand just got him a measly 5%.

‘This is better than nothing… probably these other Archedemon's that call themselves Demon Lords have these with them. Their King will probably have the biggest one yet…’

From what he knew there were five Demon Lords, which would bring his chances up by 25% after he killed them all. The Demon King was their boss so his Nuclei could be twice or many times more capable. It might push him past the 50% mark which could be enough for him to get home.

‘Killing these demons is probably the fastest way of taking care of things here but…’

He looked down to where Beatrice and Isabella were before. The two were still grasping each other but slowly descending to the ground. From what he could tell their souls had some kind of strange reaction to each other the moment they got close inside the array formation. The other girl's soul was strangely similar to Beatrice’s, he would need to investigate this later as now wasn’t the time.

He was holding the corrupt gem in his hand now after his soul beast had returned. At least that is how it looked to the people around him as there were more of them here now. While he was disposing of the Demon Lord he blasted a hole through this magical barrier revealing what was on the other side.

This barrier kept the outside as well as the inside hidden. It was constructed to not let people from within see any landmarks to keep this place hidden. Now it was gone and he could see the sky above him and also some steep rocky formations. It turned out that this school was built inside some kind of huge volcano. Even if someone looked from outside they wouldn’t be able to see any of the buildings that were placed inside.

This wasn’t all that he was looking at. There was a certain large black dragon looking at him, behind it were other lesser flying dragons with people on them. It was clear that this was the ‘cavalry’ that was late as always.

On the largest beast there sat a man with blond hair and a matching yellow beard. It was clear that the people outside witnessed him destroying the Demon Lord and now they were watching as he turned the monster’s corrupt gem into powder.

“How could this be… an Ancestral Dragon Emperor!”

He could hear the man call out while the other dragons became loud. They soon floated downwards and dropped all of their heads down. It looked as if they were prostrating themselves in front of him.

‘Do they think I’m some kind of Dragon Lord? Well… if this lets me get more resources then it's fine but for now it looks like the time is up…’

Zhang Dong looked at his hand that was previously holding the corrupt gem. He had absorbed it but now his body was going transparent. He used the last of his time to move his hands behind his back and do his usual ‘Senior-straight-like-a-sword’ pose before he faded away into mana particles. This signaled the end of the battle and the end to the demon menace in the academy.

Chapter 295

A note from Kuropon

I'll be taking a 3-day break during Easter, so the next chapter will be delayed by 3 days.

Happy Easter everyone.

“Huh?”

“Rise and shine~!”

“W-what is this…”

“Glad to welcome you back amongst the living, want something for that dry mouth?”

A dumbfounded Isabella was looking at a white-haired man behind a tiki bar. There were various colorful cocktails sitting on that bar counter and the wind was making the bamboo chimes hit against each other.

There were some large totems to the side along with tropical trees and even hula girls dancing in the background. Along with the man there, there was also Beatrice that was slowly getting on one of the wooden barstools. She looked not as bewildered by this whole predicament as if she had gone through the whole thing before.

“Here take a seat, relax. We need to talk about a few things, I bet you are confused but that is because of the soul resonance you two had gone through.”

“Soul resonance?”

This time it was Beatrice that spoke up first.

"Yes, you seem to be connected more than by your bloodline."

After the battle was over Zhang Dong returned to the soul realm but there he also found both of these blond girls. Seeing Beatrice there wasn't anything out of the ordinary but now he also saw the drill blond that was supposed to be the villain here.

Both of them were a bit out of it after trance they were through so he prepared a nice tropical setting for them. Something like this was quite easy to him, by shaping his soul repeatedly he was gaining familiarity with it. The more he did it, the stronger it became and the more access to his spiritual energy he gained.

"This is knowledge that isn't that well known so let this Leigong explain."

During the stay here he had gone through all the possible books and scriptures that this academy had to offer. Thanks to his special disposition he could even go through the Principal notes and the old archaic books. Through this, he knew a few things and one of them was this soul resonance.

“You see, this is a very rare occurrence and only happens between two or more members of the same bloodline. It also depends on how remarkable the ancestor was that you were drawing power from.”

“Ancestor?”

Isabella finally decided to join the group as she awkwardly sat on one of the bar stools. Next to her was a drink with a little umbrella in it. It had a strange light pink coloring to it that was strangely alluring. The young girl resisted the temptation of giving it a sip as she had no idea where she was.

“Yes, with the soul resonance you can call up the powers of your ancestor and materialize them to some degree. Your souls must be quite similar to a powerful summoner, thus you were able to lend me enough mana so I could exert more of my original power.”

This is what he learned from the books. He was sure that the other magicians in this world would know about this as well. What they would do with the knowledge he didn’t know. Beatrice wasn’t fond of the main house that Isabella was from.

Then Isabella wasn’t very welcoming to Beatrice that she saw as some upstart trying to go out of line. Now the two girls would need to work together and help him defeat all the demon lords. This was something that he needed to do as it was his only clue to finding more cubes.

“Yes, it must have been someone good with mana as your powers increased exponentially. Thanks to you two I managed to slay the Archdemon.”

“You were able to defeat a Demon Lord?!”

Isabella jumped to her feet while slamming her hands on the tiki bar counter. The drinks started shaking around while she looked at Zhang Dong in disbelief.

“I knew you could do it Mr. Leigong.”

On the other hand, Beatrice gave out a sigh of relief, she at least had belief in his power. After spending so much time in his soul dimension she had also grown accustomed to his quirkiness.

“Of course, that little demon was nothing. If I had access to all of my power I could crush it with my little pinky!”

Zhang Dong gave out a laugh while Beatrice rolled her eyes a bit. After being close to him so much she kind of knew that he liked to joke around a lot. She also knew that he might be telling the truth as his power was something real.

“Where are we... how do we get home… what is this place…”

Isabella on the other hand was slowly waking up to the reality of this moment. She was on a strange tropical island. There was a large golden dragon playing around in the water in the background. It looked to be wrestling with some kind of huge prehistoric-looking fish. There were also the hula dancers that after a while started to vanish into thin air.

“Don’t be afraid, we are just in the spirit realm.”

Beatrice smirked a bit while looking at her old enemy. She was glad to rub it in and Zhang Dong could tell that she was liking the fact that Isabella was acting afraid.

“Spirit realm? H-how can this be...how do we go back home…”

“Calm down little girl, no one is going to harm you. Due to the strain on both of your souls, your bodies went into a coma. With time you will recover while I nourish you back to health with the help of my own power. Look.”

Zhang Dong pointed to the side and Isabella followed his finger. There a rift opened up to show what was happening in the real world. Both the girls were together in one room and were being watched by some adults. The man that had ridden the dragon was also there, besides him was a familiar-looking man in a mustache.

“Father?”

“Pappa?”

Beatrice named her father quite traditionally while Isabella on the other hand referred to him as pappa. She noticed that both Zhang Dong and Beatrice looked at her in a funny way, this caused the girl to blush.

“Yes, they are both there. I’ve spoken to them about this so don’t worry, in a few days you will recover and be able to return to your bodies.”

Zhang Dong thought back to a day before, this was the moment that he brought down the demonic being called the Lord of Pain. The salute that the dragons gave him was quite unexpected but it also gave him the leverage to proceed with his little plan.

The person that came riding on the dragon was a Duke and current leader of the main house that Isabella was part of. He was the most powerful summoner in this kingdom that used his black dragon to battle foes. Thanks to Zhang Dong’s draconic soul beast they thought that he was some kind of old Heroic Ancestor Dragon. This made things easy as they took the whole soul resonance explanation easily.

He had explained to the Duke the connection that the two girls had. The man was hard to read as he kept quite the poker face. He didn’t know if the man liked the idea of her daughter having a similar soul to someone from a weak branch house. It was possible, these noble types saw their weaker relatives as nothing more than moochers.

Their existence was dependent on the main house but now it seemed that this branch family was standing out. Zhang Dong was afraid that these people would not like how things are turning out. First was the grandfather that was one of the more capable summoners, even close to this Duke in power if what Beatrice’s parents said was true.

For now, the Duke was cooperating with him but this was probably due to the status of ‘Dragon Ancestor’ that he had now. What would happen if he wasn’t there anymore was bothering him. He needed to make Beatrice strong enough to fend for herself in one way or another.

“So, you two can get acquainted. Why don’t you two try working together?”

“Us working together?”

Beatrice’s face contorted a bit while looking at Isabella. The blond with the drills narrowed her eyes as well before turning her face away.

“Why do I need to work with the likes of her?”

“The likes of her? What do you mean by that!”

Beatrice jumped up to her seat while slamming the poor tiki bar with her fist. The wood started buckling under the pressure and even broke in a few spots.

“Not even an ounce of dignity and decorum!”

Zhang Dong wanted to facepalm as the two girls started to argue. He knew well that Isabella was the reason Beatrice was being bullied in the academy. This was something she knew as well, working with your bully was not an easy thing to do. Why Isabella had it out for her wasn’t out in the open, he attributed it to the pretty boy with green hair.

He was her fiance but was showing more interest in Beatrice than Isabella. If he had other girls on the side wouldn’t really surprise him. In this country, high nobles were allowed to have mistresses but only one wife.

Normally Isabella’s parents and the royal family would never allow the prince to take Beatrice as a wife. But then he appeared, a super-strong spirit that was able to defeat a demon lord. With this Beatrice’s stocks would flourish and she would be seen as a proper marriage candidate. The moss head was also not the crown prince, so he could be used as a pawn to get other powerful families on the side of the royals.

What he needed to do now was to somehow get these two girls to work together. They were stuck here with him so they would need to interact. Speaking with others wasn’t his forte but he would probably need to play the nanny in this situation.

“That’s enough!”

A crack of thunder and lightning resounded through the entire place. The sunny sky turned cloudy, hurricane-like winds picked up and rain started to fall. The two girls instantly looked to Zhang Dong who was now out of his bartender role and back in his white robe.

“Stop bickering, you’re acting like little brats both of you.”

He pointed his finger at the two while they backed away.

“You will have to learn to work with each other from now on. The lives of many are at stake, do you think the demon lords will wait?”

One of the Archdemons was dead, news of this would probably reach everyone in time. Maybe the demons already had gotten this information and were now preparing for a counterattack. Beatrice and Isabella were now both in danger and he wouldn’t be able to protect them unless they performed their soul resonance.

“Please great spirit, appease your anger.”

Isabella, who didn’t know Zhang Dong well, was quite afraid while Beatrice grumbled under her breath. But after he gave her a glare she also started apologizing, the fear of balancing heavy objects while running away from menacing beasts was still with her.

“Good. Now we can talk about your future endeavors!”

The weather turned back to normal and the girls were handed fresh cocktails.

“Endeavours?”

“Yes, you two must learn to get along with each other and also be able to perform the soul resonance when the time comes!”

“You don’t mean?”

Beatrice gulped while backing away.

“Yes, we are going to do some special training!”

“Nooooooo….”

The sound of the waves blocked away the screams of the two girls, soon their new training would be starting.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 296

“G-great Ancient Spirit, is this truly necessary?”

“Yes… do we really have to do this, Mr. Leigong. I’m not sure how this is supposed to help…”

“You dare question my methods?”

“I dare not Great Spirit but…”

Isabella answered while looking at Beatrice that was narrowing her eyes at the spirit called Leigong. For one reason or another, the scenery changed to a large dance hall. It looked like a party fit for wealthy powerful nobles.

The hall was large but mostly empty. The floor was polished to a shine and made from some expensive stone resembling marble. There were some yellowish patterns here and there that made everything look as if it was bathed in gold.

Isabella was wearing a lovely-looking yellow ball gown with a lot of beautiful accessories. She looked quite dolled up for the occasion. On the other end, there was Beatrice that looked a bit maddened by the fact that she was wearing a noble man’s clothes.

The two were opposite each other and it was clear that they were supposed to dance.

“Your assignment is to dance! One will lead while the other will follow. Also, be wary of the sharks and alligators below!”

This was another part of this strange scene. The dance floor was quite large but at the edges, there was a pit filled with water. In this water, there were many flesh-eating fish, alligators, and even sharks.

“But…”

“No buts, now start!”

Zhang Dong clapped with his hands and the two girls looked at each other. Beatrice was used to the strange training methods that her spirit offered her by this point, thus she was more relaxed. On the other hand, Isabella didn’t know what was happening. The spirit told her that both of them needed to practice their soul resonance but how dancing would help with that was unknown.

With a clap the music started, a large beam of light was pointed at the pair and indicated the start of the spectacle. The two girls looked at each other with mixed expressions. The two weren’t very close with each other. They were actually more akin to enemies than friends. The predicament with the Prince going for another woman than his fiance brought this upon them.

“You should start dancing… otherwise…”

While the two looked at each other with spite the stage started getting smaller. The sounds of splashing and gnashing of teeth forced the two girls to move forward. The two had gone through extensive etiquette and dance training in their youths so they knew how to perform.

The problem was that one of them needed to play the part of the man and lead in the dance. This would fall to Beatrice but Isabella wasn’t that eager to follow at that pace. Thus it resulted in stepping on feet while the awkward dance continued.

“You need to understand your partner more, your spirits must become one. When one leads the other follows…”

Zhang Dong looked from the side while examining the dance. This was actually a very basic way of training people to work with each other. In his sect, something like this was used to teach new disciples to work with each other during formations. It was required to know their partner while performing specialized movement techniques in combat formations.

Dancing was a good way to bring people together. Though most of the time they would perform the same dance side by side, mimicking each other's movements at the same time. He went with a more noble dance due to the upbringing of these girls but it might have been a bad decision as they weren’t working together that well.

Isabella wasn’t willing to follow Beatrice’s lead during the dance. Beatrice on the other hand was very forceful in guiding the dance, not willing to pace herself. Thus the two were awkwardly moving around and soon the sharks came into play. The stage continued to shrink due to their failures to sync up and thus their end was nigh. Both of them fell down into the pit filled with sharks, their screams filling the air.

This was nothing but an illusion but the feeling of wetness was quite real as the two found themselves back on the same stage with drenched clothes.

‘Hm, it looks like their dislike for each other is keeping them from working together... how did they even manage to get in that state of soul resonance in the first place…’

He tried to remember back to that moment. Beatrice was close to passing out before Isabella moved into the picture. The two collided with each other by mistake and somehow went into the state of a trance.

‘I might be able to force this state by tweaking the spirit gathering formation… but a forced technique will always be weaker…’

Zhang Dong knew that if the two learned to work together this soul resonance could get stronger. It might even be able to boost his power towards the nascent soul level. It was unknown how strong this demon king was in this world. He was probably above the demon lords that were at the great circle of core formation level.

‘If he is at the half step into the nascent soul level the forced method might be enough… If not…’

There was also the option of gathering more mages into the gathering formation to fuel his transformation. Getting people to cooperate with him would be the hard part. Isabella’s father seemed to be wary of him but due to the dragon ancestor title he was willing to work with him.

The number of core formation experts was also limited. To get enough power to push him towards the nascent soul level he might even require a thousand of them. These two girls on the other hand pushed him into the half step realm even with a forced soul resonance. This was an easier way to give him a power-up.

Otherwise, he would need everyone in the academy to power him during a fight against the Demon King. If the other demons would just let them power him during the final battle was something out for debate.

“Okay start over again, remember you have to work together, if not for yourself do it for the people close to you.”

The girls looked at him while thinking. He had already explained to them that if they lent him enough power he would take care of the demon menace that was plaguing the whole continent. This was something they were willing to believe as he did trash the Lord of Pain quite easily with their help before.

What followed was a myriad of trust-building exercises between the two girls. Dancing wasn’t the only thing Zhang Dong was making them do. To some, it might have looked like he was giving them random tasks but in reality, there was a purpose to this madness.

One of the exercises consisted of them being chained together and having to run away from some ferocious monster. Another one pitted them in various sport events against some soul constructs that he made. Unless they were willing to work together they would not be able to persevere in these tasks.

The days passed and while it did the girls continued to recover their lost soul power. While Isabella was here he also used some time to teach her some new techniques to gain more mana. He wasn’t directly connected to her soul but when Beatrice was close by there was a soul connection formed. Through it, he could pull her into his world after she recovered.

‘Think I might have overdone it a bit…’

In his attempts to get the two girls together he had forced them to live in one room. They had to eat together, clean together and even bathe together. They had started out staring daggers at each other but after a while, something clicked. Now he was looking at the two again, they were even braiding each other's hair and applying makeup that they were able to produce with the help of soul power.

“You sure look cute with this hairstyle Lady Isabella.”

“Not as cute as you~”

They laughed and smiled at each other while continuing to play around in the soul realm.

‘Think they started acting like this after seeing that…’

He was thinking about the time ago when the girls asked him to show them what was happening in the material world. Through his summoner he was able to peek around the room they were sleeping in and a bit further beyond.

There was no reason to refuse so he obliged. To his surprise, there was a certain moss head hanging around them. At first it looked that he was just there to leave some flowers along with sweet words. The problem was that the girls wanted Zhang Dong to see what he was up to outside the room. There a little scene played out that he wasn’t expecting.

“My prince, it might be harder to court lady Beatrice after this event.”

“The harder it is, the better the rewards will be my friend. You saw what that spirit could do, we need to have its secrets!”

Quite the scene played out behind the doors as the two were leaving. It was now clear that the prince had ulterior motives which was Leigong the Spirit Emperor. Apparently, he only approached Beatrice to get to her secrets. He might have even wanted to steal him from her in some way or another.

“Will lady Isabella be fine with it?”

“Isabella? She has already been sworn to me, she just needs to follow the path that was laid out to her. She won’t mind a Mistress or two.”

It was clear that this prince was quite the character. He closed the connection before the girls could hear too many chosen words. This reveal had shattered their worldview quite rapidly. At first, they didn’t want to believe it but soon rage took them over. It was clear that the two were now dead set on getting back at the casanova of a prince.

‘Well, at least they can focus on one enemy… thank you moss head, your sacrifice will be remembered!’

He did a little prayer for the pretty boy in his head. In the near future, he might have to give him a little thrashing if the girls deemed it so. This would all be to increase the soul resonance and bring him closer to his own goal.

“Okay, listen up you two. Your souls have recovered and will soon be drawn back to your bodies. For now, continue with your training when you return.”

With the new techniques at hand reaching a level of a foundation establishment expert wouldn’t be a dream anymore. How long it would take both of them to get there was vague as it depended on them. Zhang Dong felt that if that happened they would be able to boost his power even more, maybe enough to propel him back into his true realm.

“Isabella!”

“Beatrice.”

The two sleeping beauties were back amongst the living and their parents were there. The man with the mustache was more reserved than the blond haired Duke that was hugging his daughter.

“Let us return to our estate!”

The Duke called out while checking Isabella from head to toe. Beatrice’s father didn’t say anything for now as there was a little agreement made beforehand. It looked like the Duke was trying to not follow through with it. Thus Leigong the Dragon Ancestor had to make an appearance again.

“This wasn’t what we agreed on. Your daughter is to aid me and my contractor in defeating the Demon Lords.”

A little clash of wills was upon them, the Duke was quite strong so a diminished Zhang Dong couldn’t really make him budge just yet. The little stare-off between the Duke and Zhang Dong’s small version was broken through Isabella’s words.

“I wish to stay with Lady Beatrice's father, we will lend them our flying ship, the Jergintarth!”

“But sweety…”

He could see the girl with the drill hair pouting with a disappointed look while the Duke tried to appease her. It was quite obvious that she had him wrapped around her finger. If they could use that to their advantage then it would be fine, getting a mobile flying vessel was something that was very high on his to-do list. With it, he could finally start the search for a way home.

Chapter 297

A smaller version of the Lightning Emperor was standing upright at the helm of a middle-sized flying ship.

‘The technology is quite similar to our own but the engine looks to be more refined. If I could implement it in the Argonauts design when I return...’

Some time had passed since the Archdemon’s attack. Thanks to the healing spells and potions in this world the casualties were lessened. People like the Vice-Principal that lost a limb could also recover without that much of a problem.

It was clear that when it came to healing this world’s magic was stronger than Zhang Dong’s. Missing limbs would require special pills that required even rarer materials. Only people at a very high level with the holy element like him would be able to emulate the priest spells from this magical world.

“Lady Isabella you must reconsider what will the people think about this…”

“I have already decided, please don’t associate yourself with me anymore, Prince Ludwig.”

Zhang Dong’s attention was brought down to a little scene. There was a group of young noblemen and women bickering about. On one side stood Isabella and Beatrice also along with a few maids. On the other side was the Prince with a couple of knights. It was clear that after eavesdropping on Moss head’s conversation both the blond girls were furious with him.

He couldn't fault them for that and was quite glad that they all listened in on the conversation. Since Isabella was a proud lady she found offense in the way the prince was thinking about her. She was nothing more than a tool, someone to just link him to her strong family.

‘Not much different here than where I came from huh…’

This wasn’t anything new, something like this was how people in the clans formed bonds. The problem was that Isabella apparently didn’t see it like that. She was a young maiden that was still apparently looking for love. From his perspective, it would be immensely hard to find a loving partner in that way. His wife had grown on him through time and the love came later.

‘Well, at least this helped me to get this ship…’

Isabella was part of the main family that Beatrice belonged to. Since the two were required to work together to help him fight the demon lords he was given this ship. Together with it a crew of knights and wizards from both the academy and the Duke Hohenberg of Dragonridge household.

Beatrice’s father also lent some soldiers in the form of the old man that he previously faced off against. He was tasked with being Beatrice’s bodyguard and would have his work cut for him. The young Beatrice didn’t have much pull here to make any decisions. Only thanks to him were they willing to listen after he defeated the Demon Lord.

“Lady Isabella, I’m sure this is some kind of mistake I would never…”

Before Ludwig could continue with his words Beatrice stepped next to Isabella and started glaring at him as well.

“Lady Beatrice… you too…”

The prince looked quite baffled. From Zhang Dong’s perspective, he was just the young master type that never had any hindrance in his life. He was also not the crown prince which lowered his responsibilities while still giving him a large amount of status. This was probably the first time one of his schemes had gone down the drain.

“My lord, think we are done here. The great Holy Dragon Ancestor has requested our aid to rid the whole of humanity of the demonic scourge. We mustn't keep him waiting!”

After the little battle with the Lord of Pain Zhang Dong had gained another glorious title. Thanks to his draconic soul beast everyone thought that he was some kind of heroic spirit of an ancient dragon god. Due to his unknown name, they thought that he just had to be some long-forgotten ancestors, maybe even the father of dragons.

‘Daddy of all dragons doesn’t sound so bad… I hope none of them will try talking to me though…’

Dragon’s were an elusive species around here and revered by all. The high tier ones could change their form to look human thus his disguise was perfect.

He glanced at the conversation below and could see the prince moving to block Isabella’s path. After the cat was out of the bag Isabella asked her father to annul the engagement. The duke was quite fond of his daughter and almost instantly obliged.

From what he knew, the one who actually wanted the marriage was Isabella. The prince was a sweet talker so he did manage to weasel himself into her good graces. Now on the other hand he was going to lose quite a bit. Not being able to marry someone at the level of a Duke’s daughter was a hit to his face and prestige. It looked like he wouldn’t just give up like that.

“Please prince Ludwig, we are done with our conversation. We must depart towards Isthvar to gather more people for our quest.”

“Worry not Lady Isabella, how about I join you on your trip and have my men accompany you. They are the very best! We then could talk about everything in private…”

‘I got to give it to him, he doesn’t easily give up. Having some royal knights along the trip isn’t something that could be easily refused…’

Refusing this aid would normally be seen as foolish. The royal family possessed quite the military might that could bolster them. There was also the problem of a Duke’s daughter not being able to decline the help of a prince if he really imposed it on her. Their ranks were quite close but still in favor in old moss head’s. So then, before the conversation could go in the wrong direction a thunderclap was heard and a bolt of golden light descended towards the bickering children.

“That is enough, you may leave young prince of the humans, your services won’t be required.”

It was clear that this young casanova would try to somewhat sweet talk both of the girls along the flight. Maybe a few lucky events could somehow bring them all back together. Zhang Dong on the other hand wasn’t really interested in having this guy on his ship. He would clearly not be willing to listen to him, it was best not to bring him or any of his men along as they couldn’t be trusted.

“Lady Beatrice… your spirit…”

“My spirit?”

Beatrice narrowed her eyes while looking at the green-haired prince. From what Zhang Dong could tell she was mad that he referred to him without any honorifics. It was clearly rude to refer to a Dragon Ancestor as ‘Your Spirit’ but the young prince didn’t see spirits as beings above him.

He probably only saw them as useful tools, nothing more than a machine to do their bidding. This was quite normal for the young master types, even more, when his father was the strongest man on the continent. From what he could deduce this King should be at least on par with an Archdemon. In the eyes of this youth, he probably thought that his daddy would have no problem in slaying that beast alone.

While he was shaking his head Isabella took it upon herself to jump in.

“How dare you speak in such a way to the Dragon Ancestor, apologize immediately!”

“That’s right, apologize to Mr. Leigong!”

After the two had reconciled due to the prince being a sleaze bag, they were quick to work together against him. He wasn’t sure if Beatrice was still angry at the main house about her grandfather but at least she didn’t seem antagonistic towards Isabella anymore.

“Apologize, me?”

The prince was of course taken aback, he probably never had to apologize to anyone besides maybe his parents. While Zhang Dong wanted nothing more than to look at this comedic routine to play itself out he had things to do.

“ENOUGH!”

Zhang Dong’s form expanded into his regular size and lightning energy covered his whole body. When the girls were close by he could exert more of his power without Beatrice passing out.

“We don’t have time for your mortal squabbles, we must depart before the demon scourge causes even more chaos.”

He exerted some of his strength which pushed the people from the prince’s side to their knees. It was a very similar aura attack that cultivators loved to perform to assert their dominance over others. No one here was above the foundation establishment realm in power, even the knights only reached up to about the early stage at most.

“Beatrice, control your spirit, this is going too far!”

This time it wasn’t the moss head but the carrot top instead. From his perspective, this was an obvious attack against someone from the royal family.

“Oh, am I going too far? Why don’t I eat you along with that little prince of yours.”

To scare the duo Zhang Dong’s pupils turned draconic in nature and resembled reptilian eyes while he stared at the two young men. He wouldn’t eat them of course but the people here didn’t know that. To them, he was a scary spirit that could change into a huge dragon if he wanted to.

The two flinched at the notion of being eaten and started inching back while still underneath the pressure of Zhang Dong’s aura.

“Don’t worry, I wouldn’t eat you, human meat is disgusting.”

It was fun to play around with these kids but he didn’t want to be labeled as some kind of flesh eating monster. He waved his hand and the two girls started floating up into the air. Soon all of them were flying towards the ship where most of the people were already waiting for their departure.

“Mr. Leigong… how do you know how human meat tastes?”

While flying he looked to Beatrice that had a silly smirk on her face. It was clear that she saw through his bluff. Isabella on the other hand was more gullible as she saw him as some kind of god like being that had descended to this very earth.

She also for some reason liked him in his small form, to the point of asking him to allow getting petted. He had noticed that the girl had been looking at him funny from day one and it was apparently due to the love of cute things.

“Why you little…”

He wanted to give her cheeks a good pull but they had already arrived on the flying ship. People were already done loading all the necessary items and they were close to being able to depart. The principal couldn’t leave with them due to her position but the old friendly Vice-Principal was going with them. With him as a guide, they would be able to pass through most of the pesky barriers between the large cities and nations.

“So, do we have any information about any demon sightings?”

“Yes, there has been movement by the demons, they are fleeing as we speak, we must catch up to them!”

The one replying was the Vice-Principal who had his leg healed by now. He looked quite invigorated that he was chosen for this mission. It was clear that he wasn’t a fan of the demons and saw this as a good chance for retaliation.

“Well then, let us depart.”

Zhang Dong looked at the magic academy that he spent a few weeks in. He was glad that he was finally able to move on. With the help of these people, he hoped to reach his goal sooner than before. Hopes of meeting up with his family again grew even higher than before and he was ready to do everything in his power to return.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 298

Darkness filled Dorian’s vision as he awoke. It was clear to him that he had something in the form of a sack tied to his head. It made things hard to breathe and very uncomfortable.

He was just a regular farmer’s son that had been out on the field all day. The last thing that he remembered was going back home after working. The sun was setting as they had to hurry up with this month’s harvest. Then things became blurry, something happened between the time of him walking home and arriving here.

“Ughhh…”

When he tried to speak something compelled him to not. There was nothing inside of his mouth but when he tried to open it, he couldn’t. It was as if his lips were glued together and the only thing he could do was to mumble. Soon he heard rustling from the sides and similar mumbling and groaning were heard by him. It looked like he wasn’t alone in this place.

“The sacrifices are waking up high priest.”

“It matters not, the ritual is ready to begin, the Lord of Terror will be pleased with us!”

In the silence there were voices, the young farmer had no idea what was happening but this had something to do with the demon worshipers. His parents had warned him about them when he was younger.

There were certain people that worshiped the devils that were banished from these lands. They would perform strange rituals to open the rifts in the barrier in hopes of getting power in return. This could come in many forms but mostly they would turn into demonic beings themselves then serve the demon that they worshiped till the end of their life.

“Remove the sacks, let the sacrifices bask in the Lord’s glory!”

Footsteps followed the man’s words and the bag on his head was removed. What he saw was many people like him. Hands bound and curled up on a strange red circle. He wanted to scream but couldn’t after realizing that this magic writing was painted in human blood. There were multiple headless corpses to the side that were used for this purpose.

The other people looked to be mostly commoners from the villages just like him. They were of various genders and ages, even of mixed races as apparently no one was spared. The women were crying while the men were looking with anger in their eyes at the massacred people and the demon worshipers that were responsible for this.

“Be glad sinners, you will be graced by the Lord’s love! He will devour your very souls and use it as nourishment to cleanse these lands from the rot that covers it!”

A man in dark robes and various strange accessories stood out on a dim-lit platform above them. There were others like him gathered in this place around them. It was clear that they wanted to sacrifice them to some kind of demonic being. Running was the only option for survival.

Dorian’s struggles didn’t bore fruit, his body felt sluggish and he just couldn’t untie the ropes that bound him. The same thing happened to the others as even the more robust-looking men couldn’t break free. Something was sapping their strength already and soon some kind of strange portal appeared. It was right in the middle of this dastardly demonic circle and looked like it was made from blood.

“Yes! YES! The Lord is coming through!”

“Behold the lord’s glory infidels, bask in his light!”

The cultist started mumbling some strange incoherent chants while the people on the ground tried to flee. Soon the portal started expanding in size and with time something started to push through.

A large hooved leg appeared, it was covered in some tight red leathery skin. With a thump, this leg slammed to the ground below and caused it to tremble. Soon the demon’s form was revealed. It was many times larger than a human, close to ten meters tall. Its lower half looked like it belonged to a goat while the top half was more human-looking.

This being had similar characteristics to the first Demon Lord of Pain. The torso was muscular and covered in red leather. Its head didn’t possess eyes instead its brain was sticking out, below it a large toothy mouth with black teeth that were covered with blood. Various horns and spikes were coming out of its spine as well as from its fists.

“We greet the Lord of Terror! We present you these sacrifices, please feast on their immortal souls!’

The giant demon lord was able to get through the demonic gate of blood fully revealing itself. Even without any eyes, it seemed to be looking deep into everyone’s soul that was here.

“Inadequate…”

The monster’s shrill voice filled the area without it even talking. It pointed out towards the cultists with its large digit. The person that was getting pointed at evaporated into dark gas that was then absorbed into the creature’s mouth.

“T-the sacrifices weren’t enough, we have angered the lord!”

The person that looked like the boss of the bunch started backing away but it was too late. It looked that the monster was unhappy with the number of sacrifices. The moment it stepped through the portal it started to devour its own worshipers. Some of them tried to escape while some just kneeled down with opened arms as if happy that they could be of use to this demonic being.

It went after the cultist first, even devouring the main priest. Soon it turned to the people in the magic circle that were still alive. It didn’t point with its finger but instead started moving towards them. For one reason or another, it grabbed Dorian with its massive hand and raised him up towards its toothy mouth.

The man screamed out, after the cultist had been devoured whatever was stopping him from speaking was now gone. The monster’s grip was far too strong to break out from the only thing that he could do now was watch that ghastly orifice opening up to devour him whole.

His death was before him, everything that he couldn’t do flashed before his eyes. Regrets of not asking that one girl to the festival a few months ago, not helping his parents more, not being able to become a man. He wasn’t ready to die but there was nothing he could do, the demon was far too strong and he would consume him like the rest of the people here.

But the beast stopped before devouring Dorian whole. It was as if it noticed something, it moved its head up and Dorian looked up as well. There it was, glowing in bright light and coming straight for them. Before the monster could react something collided with the ground right next to it.

Dorian felt weightless for some reason and soon he realized why. The monster’s hand that was grasping him just a moment ago was evaporating into nothingness. He was afraid that he was getting erased as well but instead, a gentle golden light covered his body and guided him away from the demonic creature.

He wasn’t the only one that was being saved. Every person that was bound at that bloody circle was quickly floating away why shielded by bright energy. Soon they all were further away with their bindings gone.

“W-what is that…”

A woman pointed at the demonic being that previously swallowed up all those cultists with just a pointing of its finger. It was being held in place by some kind of golden figure. This figure looked to be of similar height but more majestic in outlook. It was some kind of being of energy that was bathed in bolts of lightning. At the moment the two beings were clashing in a contest of strength but the demon was losing.

“Is that an angel?”

“A holy spirit?”

The people looked on in shock and awe while the two huge beings continued to fight. They were duking it out in close quarters combat, throwing punches filled with either divine or demonic energy. The previously scary monster with the brain sticking out looked a lot less intimidating the moment it started getting smacked around by this golden giant.

“Please don’t stand around and evacuate.”

Suddenly a voice from above called out to them and the people could see a large flying ship descending their way. A group of people in shiny armor jumped out and started evacuating everyone to this flying vessel.

The people that were previously sacrificed had no problem going with these knights in shining armor. It looked like they had come to save them in their time of need. Everyone was slowly carried off while the two powerful beings were fighting in the distance.

When everyone arrived on the flying ship they saw another strange sight. There were two beautiful girls kneeling in the center of this ship’s deck. They were surrounded by armored men from all sides and their bodies were glowing. The glow was akin to the one that the being of light had which made Dorian connect the dots together.

This was of course Beatrice and Isabella carrying out their soul resonance. The duo had been traveling the lands and searching for demon lords to defeat. This wasn’t their first rodeo either as this Demon lord of Terror was their third target.

Soon a giant monstrous roar that could only belong to a massive beast was heard. Everyone gathered at the ship looked to it to discover a giant golden dragon discharging rays of energy into the ground below. Its aim was clearly the Archedemon that it was fighting, now not much remained from his body as he was melting away at this very moment.

“Could it be… the Twin Saint Priestesses?”

Dorian looked at the person that called out from the side. It was a woman from his village and she was pointing at the two cute girls that were holding hands together.

“The Saint Priestesses…”

He knew that name, it was something that took the land by storm not even a month ago. First, there were some rumors that one of the Demon Lords was slain by an unknown entity. Then with time, another one fell not long after, the rumors suggested two virgins bathed in light were always present when such a thing occurred.

They commanded some kind of giant dragon emperor that could spit out lightning and control the holy elements. This had to be true as the beast that was slowly burning away the demon was an actual dragon that fit the description. The golden figure had somehow transformed into this majestic beast during the battle.

Soon the energies from the surroundings faded and people were greeted to a giant crater that had been dug up by the dragon’s breath. The monster vanished soon into many tiny particles while the whole scene was illuminated by a clear sky and moonlight.

The third Demon Lord was gone and the legend of the Twin Saint Priestesses continued. The two ‘saints’ in question were not that happy about their new title. Their divine dragon wasn’t either as he was seen as nothing more than their contracted beast without a mind of its own.

“Three down… two to go!”

A strange man dressed in a white robe appeared out from nowhere. Dorian and the rest glanced at him in bewilderment as he had some kind of strange otherworldly aura to himself. Soon he vanished into particles of light while the blond girls returned to normal. The fight was over and everyone rejoiced.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 299

Zhang Dong returned to the ship after crushing the demonic stone into dust. This was the third one that he had received. It was looking good on the outside but the search was slowly coming to an end. These monsters weren’t that hard to kill, finding them was the hard part.

The massive protective barrier that separated the continent of the races from the demonic lands was an issue. These demonic lords had a hard time coming through to this side. He was already lucky that he managed to get to three of them in such a short amount of time.

Even this Demon Lord of Terror was more of a fluke. The only reason that they found him was that his senses had expanded and he was able to sense a big spike of demonic energies. The cultists were also quite bad at hiding their tracks as they picked off people from close by villages without bothering to hide their tracks. Anyone that was lucky to be leftover was quick to report their movements to the authorities.

“Bob, with this one what are the chances of returning back to my sector?”

“The chances are 17,78%”

Each nucleus had a different amount of energy which then increased the percentage by a random amount. It seemed that the stronger the Archdemon was the more percentages he would get.

He had already asked Bob about the way back home. It wasn’t as hard for him to actually do it at this very moment. He would only need to design the proper teleportation formation and then focus all of the energies he had gained onto it.

When he activated it he would be blasted to the same path between worlds. That would be where the absorbed nuclei would come into place. The energy from them would be required to tether himself back to his own world. As someone that was an owner of a body that belonged there, he would be able to materialize there without being a spirit like here.

He required these cubes to be sure that he would make the journey back home. Depending on where he initially started out in, it would require more energy to find the connection. Then even more to make it.

Bob even told him that if he was able to reach a realm above the nascent soul level then the cubes wouldn’t be required as much. He would be able to travel between worlds of his own accord. This was something that he couldn’t wait for, even getting to the great circle of the nascent soul level would take many years. Even more in a world without spiritual energy but mana that wasn’t that suited for his cultivation.

This is why he needed to get as many of the nuclei from this world as he could. Otherwise, he could be lost between worlds forever. He was lucky enough to come in contact with this world during Beatrice’s summoning. The next time he tried there could be no Beatrice to pull himself to, then he would be left out in the void and die alone.

“Twin Saint Priestesses! We are saved!”

His attention turned to the two girls that were sweating. Their teamwork had gotten better and he was able to keep his form for longer while also adding more power. Ever since the first demon lord was killed rumors had been spreading about their adventures.

He was doing most of the heavy lifting in sensing the Archdemons and actually battling them one on one. On the other hand, he as a summoned spirit was pushed into the background while the two Summoners that used him were at the forefront. Everyone praised them as the Twin Saint Priestesses or the Golden Saints. There were various other nicknames but the two were now very popular with the common people.

Due to him requiring the Archdemon gems they traveled through the continent to demon-infested regions. They cleared them out one by one while watching out for the demon lords. Though he was doing most of the ‘clearing out’ by disintegrating the demons with his lightning.

‘The ungrateful life of the summoned spirit… I wonder why you do it…’

Zhang Dong looked at a water nymph that belonged to Isabella. Since the soul resonance, he could also access the other girl’s soul. Through it he could actually interact with the spirit she made a contract with.

This spirit in particular had the appearance of a beautiful woman but regretfully he couldn’t converse with her well. He wanted to know more about the spirit realm as he wasn’t really part of it. This spirit wasn’t that chatty though and also could only perform basic commands. Due to his massive strength, she also saw him as someone to be listened to. He could actually overwrite Isabella’s commands that she placed on this spirit.

After pulling the spirit into his own soul realm he had it interact with his soul beast. The dragon was actually happy to have someone else to play with. Though this water nymph wasn’t that fond of him and mostly turned to water whenever the big guy tried bothering her.

‘Hey, you two. Get some rest and let us return to the city. The mana engine needs to be refilled.’

He vanished after taking care of the Archdemon and left the two girls to tend to the crowd. With them around, he wouldn’t need to interact with the crowd at least.

The academy life was over for now and they returned to a large city of Elfheim. This was this country's capital and was the largest city in this world. Even though it was the biggest, the population was only at about two million. His own Spirit Spring City that he hailed from was way bigger. This world’s size and population was a lot smaller than the sun-sized world he came from.

With time the ship arrived at the dock. Thanks to something akin to a magic floating stone it was able to remain up in the air. The mana engine was only needed for the propulsion speed while this strange rock kept it afloat.

This place had been their base of operations. The Principal was an influential magic user, she gifted them her villa as a place to stay along with the Vice-Principal as help. The old man was necessary to get things going. Without someone with some status it would be impossible to just fly around the whole continent unchecked.

Isabella’s father had also supplied them with many guards for protection. With them around, he could safely battle the demons while the girls concentrated on lending him mana.

“Glad that you have returned.”

Elobarin greeted the two girls along with Zhang Dong that was saving his energy in his smaller form.

“You should go rest, I bet the battle was hard-fought.”

“Not really, I think he was weaker than the last one. The ritual that those cultists were performing was incomplete.”

Zhang Dong replied while the Vice Principal chuckled. The old man wasn’t as afraid of him as he was previously. Leigong was now seen as a force for good and a powerful being that aided the people of the races. He knew that people talked behind his back, telling everyone that he was quite eccentric.

“Is that so…”

Elobarin rubbed his beard while chuckling but then looked to Zhang Dong as if he was worried about something.

“Is there something more?”

“Ah yes, there is such a thing but we shouldn’t talk about it here, let us return.”

Zhang Dong raised his eyebrow but nodded. The soul resonance wasn’t such an easy technique to perform. The girls were always tired afterward and needed at least a day to sleep it off before returning to normal.

While moving down from these flying ship docks he looked at the city once more. There were various smaller devices flying around, not all in the form of a ship. There were also people like witches, magical beasts, various types of golems moving back and forth between everywhere. It looked quite busy, flight seemed to be a lot easier here than back home, probably thanks to items like the floating stone used in the ship.

They all returned to the villa that the Principal provided for them. It was nothing compared to his own house back home but in this world, it would be considered quite large. Inside there were many maids with dog and cat ears alike. This time around they weren’t demons but just regular women.

There was a barracks for the knights to stay in as well as a field for their training. They would normally head out for a week to scan the areas for potential demons. Though the one doing the scanning was him. The range he was able to monitor had increased but he wasn’t able to find any spots with more cubes. The only clue that he had were the Archedemons but after taking out three the trail started getting cold.

“Are there any news about more Demons? We should rest up and head out tomorrow if it's possible.”

Zhang Dong declared while the two sleepy girls yawned. They were inside the main room of this mansion with a few other people that joined them on this journey.

“The young miss has to rest, there is no news of the demonic presence, we have done enough for now.”

Elobarin replied while scratching his beard. Zhang Dong on the other hand was a bit anxious about no news of any demonic lords around. It has been a month since they left the academy and he wasn’t even close to getting all of the nuclei.

“Now now, there is no rush. Let us talk about other news, a letter from the royal castle arrived. They wish to invite young Beatrice and Isabella to the yearly royal ball.”

“The royal ball?”

Beatrice, who was almost asleep, opened up her eyes wide after hearing this news. Isabella on the other hand narrowed them as if she wasn’t that keen on going there.

“The ball…”

“Mr. Leigong we must go, all the members of the royal family will be there… what should I wear…’

Beatrice started bouncing around as if the previous drowsiness didn’t exist. Soon both she and Isabella left to discuss some lady business. Zhang Dong on the other hand was left with Elobarin.

“Will the king be there?”

“Yes, he will but please you must not be rude to the king! That man’s temperament is something no one can control!”

The old man started panicking while looking at Zhang Dong who just raised an eyebrow.

“Have I ever been rude to anyone before?”

“Well, there was that one time when…”

“It was a rhetorical question! More importantly, the king is the person that could help me battle the Archdemons, maybe even organize a preemptive strike...”

“P-preemptive strike?”

Elobarin started panicking even more. Attacking the side of the demons was something that he didn’t think was possible but for Zhang Dong the time was ticking. He couldn’t wait months or years for the monsters to decide to attack.

“Yes, we bring the fight to them… Don’t worry, I’ll speak to him myself.”

“T-that’s why I’m worried…”

The old man called out while Zhang Dong shrugged and vanished into his own soul realm. While waiting for this royal ball he would continue his cultivation.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 300

“Have you heard, another demon lord has fallen.”

“My gosh, doesn’t that make it three already?”

“Yes, isn’t it grand? Do you believe that it is all thanks to the Hohenberg house? Who would have known that they were hiding such strength…”

“It only took them this much while the royal family hasn’t been able to do anything…”

“Shhh… be quiet… do you want to get your head cut off?”

A group of noble ladies and noblemen were talking while surrounded by lavish decor. This was the place where the nobles gathered each year to promote their own houses. This large party was the perfect place to talk with powerful figures.

High nobles like Dukes along with members of the royal family were required to participate. Thus the lower seated ones were always eager to speak with them. Everyone wanted their sons and daughters to be married off to well-off houses. This year around the Hohenberg house was quite prominent.

The title of the Twin Saint Priestesses held power over the people. It gave them hope in this world filled with demonic beings. This wasn’t entirely good for the powerful ducal house that was behind them. With more fame came more troubles, other factions would see them as a foe that was trying to gain more power. This time they were stepping on the toes of the royal family.

No monarch liked being questioned about their motives. Leigong the Lightning Emperor was making the actual Human Emperor look bad. During his rule, the demonic menace only spread and it didn’t seem that he was doing anything. He was a powerful individual that ascended to the throne early after battling his brothers for supremacy.

Being powerful didn’t mean that he could freely move throughout the lands. He was required to stay in the capital as fear from a demon attack to their stronghold was a possibility. This didn’t keep the regular folk to spin rumors around of a powerful king not acting when his people needed him most.

“What are you chattering about?”

“Ahh… nothing your highness, long live the king!”

The group of nobles flinched at the appearance of someone from the royal family. It was one of the princes, they were all characterized by their colorful heads. This prince in particular had fallen out of favor after his arranged marriage to a powerful duke household had fallen through. His name was Ludwig and he was Zhang Dong’s favorite moss head.

“Calm down prince, you shouldn’t mind such gossip.”

Carrot top was there to cheer up his lord that he was sworn to. Ever since Beatrice and Isabella started giving them the cold shoulder nothing was going their way. They lost a lot of funding from the royal family, Ludwig was now required to find another potential wife or beg Isabella to reconsider. This was also one of the reasons that he was hereafter knowing well that the two girls would be here.

The ball was taking place in the grand castle of the Palodis Kingdom. It was the strongest Kingdom on the whole continent due to its military might. Due to the demon menace, the other countries were allied with each other but it was clear that if conflict would ever arise then this kingdom would be victorious.

Elves were the most magically gifted and dwarves could build the strongest weapons but they couldn’t compete with humans when it came to battle. This race multiplied fast and was very adaptive while the others found it hard to change their ways.

The second in power were the elves thanks to their aptitude for mysticism. The only problem was that their birth rates were small compared to the humans. They were outnumbered ten to one but somehow made up the difference in sheer magic might.

The third were the dwarves, they had more people than the elves and used the underground as their kingdom. They were divided into many dwarven city-states and had a hard time in working together with each other since their last king died to one of the demon lords.

These were the three main races with the others being too minor to matter in the big picture. Thus the human kingdom reigned supreme with their king taking the title of strongest man alive.

“Now arriving Ladyship Beatrice Hohenberg of Dawn Lake and her grace Isabella Hohenberg of Dragonridge….”

The people were slowly gathering and all eyes were on these two noble ladies. Some were more interested in the new upstart lady Beatrice. She was still an untapped resource that people weren’t sure how to treat. Isabella on the other hand had the Duke backing her, she couldn’t be approached as easily as someone that was a daughter of a baron.

“Also...uh…”

The man that looked like a high-class butler straightened out his tuxedo but continued to announce the peculiar arrival.

“His Excellency, Lightning Emperor Leigong…”

This was quite the peculiar sight, behind the two ladies that were all dolled up in costly dresses there was a man. He had an otherworldly feel to him and looked slightly different than these nobles. His hair was long and white as the whitest snow. His jawline was strong and made him look quite handsome. The ladies were quick to hide their gaping mouths behind their fans.

People knew who he was but were surprised that a spirit would make an appearance at the royal ball. He was wearing a strange white robe with quite the assembly of costly-looking accessories. There were various gems and gold-like metals embedded into this more ceremonial-looking robe which made some nobles gulp.

‘I guess we need to get through this one way or another, hope this king guy can lend me some help against the demons…’

Zhang Dong had decided to show up in his regular human form. With Beatrice progressing at a steady pace he could hang out in the material world normally. This was also made possible with some artifacts that he fashioned for both his summoners. With limited resources and time, they were only able to slightly increase the mana that he was receiving.

He was also able to remain at something around the early stage of core formation without the girls needing the soul resonance. If he actually fought anyone then Beatrice would be drained as always but with the bonus from her new items, she would last a lot longer.

“Is that really the famed spirit that defeated the Demon Lords?”

“It looks more human than I anticipated…”

The people started whispering from the side while Zhang Dong remained close to the two girls. Whenever someone tried making a pass on Beatrice he would be there to glare and send some oppressing aura their way. There weren’t many nobles that could block something like this out so he proved as the best chaperone for the two young ladies.

“Mr. Leigong… you are scaring the Aristocats…”

“Do you really want another Ludwig to pop up?”

“N-no….”

Beatrice shrunk down while looking around. She was a fish out of water and knew no one here. Isabella on the other hand was mingling with the crowd and smiling. This wasn’t the first time that she was at a party like this and she had her own circle of young ladies as well.

The ones that left her up to dry at the academy were already banned from it but she was quick to replace them with new ones. There was a wide range of noble ladies willing to go to various lengths to get into Isabella’s circle of friends.

“But you are right, I can’t protect you forever. Maybe you should join Isabella, I bet she will guide you through it.”

Zhang Dong urged Beatrice to go to Isabella’s circle, at least there she would be with someone that she knew. The moment she left he himself was ganged by nosy nobles. Mostly women for some reason that were enamored with his looks. Some of them even tried touching his hair or arms, though they found themselves quickly electrocuted.

“This Lightning Emperor is spoken for, disperse you, harlots!”

He could only cause a little scene which caused some of the nobles to laugh while the women that were trying to get his attention were quick to leave. The people here were quite more promiscuous than the ones back home.

‘What’s wrong with them, are they possessed by some sex demons?’

Cultivators were more reserved and lust was something akin to a demon that everyone tried to purge to progress”s with their cultivation. Here on the other hand the nobles were bored and willing to delve into more debauchery. As someone with children and a wife, he was unwilling to give in.

‘Old gramps or Qiang would have a field day here…’

He wanted to chuckle after remembering his own family and friends. Though his smile turned to a frown quite fast after being reminded that he was still stuck here with no certain way of getting home.

For now, he became a wallflower with arms crossed over one another. He kept his gaze around the large ballroom that paled in comparison to the one he used during his wedding. Soon everyone had arrived and it was time for the big shot to make his appearance.

“His Majesty, Alexander Angelo Palodis”

The people looked up as a man dressed in a royal uniform and a big golden crown hovered down. Zhang Dong could feel some pressure coming off from this person, he was clearly utilizing his aura to keep people in check. Everyone hit by this aura was forced down to kneel.

‘He really is stronger than a Demon Lord.”

Zhang Dong remained leaning up against the wall while this attack happened. Like most of the magic here it was aimed at the soul which was ineffective to someone like him that had already advanced his soul past the nascent soul level. The fact that he was the only person not kneeling wasn’t unnoticed by this king.

King Alexander looked like a man in his late forties. He was large in stature and his might was very real. His hair was dark blue just as the well-kept beard that made him look more regal.

He floated down onto his throne and moved his hand up. Soon the oppressive force subsided and everyone was able to stand up. Some of the nobles noticed the glances exchanged between the fabled spirit and the strongest man alive. It was a worrisome sight as people knew that the king had a short fuse.

Luckily the king just leaned on his hand while closing his fist. The man that was previously doing the announcements then clapped his hands.

“His Majesty is happy to be the host for the annual…”

The man performed a practiced speech for the king while he continued to stare in Zhang Dong’s direction. It was clear that the show of resistance was something uncommon.

‘Don’t think he likes me but without the girls supporting me I wouldn’t stand a chance.’

Zhang Dong decided to keep up his poker face but he didn’t use any oppressive aura or soul attacks to get back at the man. He was a guest and acting out would be bad for Beatrice and Isabella. He was also here to get some help with the demon situation.

“Get on with it.”

The King called out in a low tone to the man doing the speech.

“My apologies, your Majesty. This Royal Ball will be a special one, I am glad to announce that the Hero Summoning ritual will be possible this very day.”

“Huh?”

Zhang Dong gave out a perplexed sound while the people cheered out loud.

‘They can summon heroes here?’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 301

“The hero summoning can be performed? What a wondrous occasion!”

“It hasn’t been performed in many generations.”

“We might really be free of the demon lords and take back our lost lands!”

The people cheered while Zhang Dong on the other hand was to the side listening. It sounded like the people here would be performing some kind of ‘Hero Summoning’. If he went by the knowledge from his more nerdy days he kind of knew what this would bring.

‘Will they really summon people from outside? Could they be from my original world?’

He was the only one here that really understood from where these ‘heroes’ were coming from. Just like him before they might be clicking on a strange email and getting transported. There could be other ways of them being transported here but one thing was clear.

‘If they can summon people into this castle then one of the cubes must be close by… probably right under it…’

With this reveal came the good news. With a fully functional nucleus, he might be able to boost his chances of getting home. There were a few problems with this though.

‘I don’t think this king will just let me dig under his castle, the cube might even be in the summoning chamber directly.’

Zhang Dong was just a summoned spirit, he couldn’t just take the castle apart to find the item that he needed. The king was stronger than him in his current form, getting the girls to aid him against their own monarch would probably not be possible. There was also another problem with his plan, mainly these new heroes.

What would happen if he took the thing that brought them here with him. After absorbing it, the cube would lose all of its teleporting capabilities. The people being brought over here would be stuck here forever.

‘But is there even a way back home? I’ll have to observe and decide later…’

There was a possibility of just swiping the cube and running for it. That wasn’t really his style though, his morals kept him from betraying Beatrice and the people that he was helping here.

“We will be performing the summoning ritual soon, please everyone gather in the hall outside!”

The person that looked like a high-class Buttler proclaimed while the nobles shuffled outside. Apparently, the ritual wouldn’t be taking place in any chamber but somewhere out of the castle.

When everyone stepped outside they could see a cleared-out space. It was clear that there was something like a large garden or a hedge maze here before but it had been cleared out.

Instead, there were five large pillars that were connected by a magic circle. Inside of it was a large podium that was surrounded by a pentagram. After reading all of the books he was sure that this was akin to a teleportation formation. He even tried to recall the one that he saw back in his own world, the one under the spot that he appeared in.

‘It is similar...the cube might be below this area or somewhere in the general vicinity.’

He wasn’t sure about the range these teleportation spots had. In his world, it was directly under the open field he appeared in but it was buried several kilometers below ground. If he didn’t have his system map he would have never found it in the first place.

‘The range is still too small…’

When the people were gathering he started to move around with his map out. There were no dark spots on it even when he was standing outside with the others. There was nothing more that he wanted to do but dig underground but he had to wait till this ceremony was over. First, he needed to see this so-called summoning ritual being performed.

‘Bob, record everything that will be happening. Maybe if you get more data on this teleportation circle we can use it to get me home faster.’

The problem of getting home was the route. Only after escaping this world would he be able to triangulate the world where his wife and kids were. But now when this grand summoning ritual was taking place there was a chance of getting more data. He might be even able to tell where these ‘heroes’ were summoned from.

“Isn’t it great Mr. Leigong, I would have never dreamed about being able to witness a hero summoning.”

Beatrice said while standing to the left of Zhang Dong.

“This is truly a joyous occasion.”

Isabella commented while she was on the right along with some other nobles from her friend circle. There was a lot of space here so everyone could look at this ritual.

“Hm, is it?”

He replied while rubbing his chin. From his perspective being summoned to another world was a traumatic experience. Now if he was dropped off here with many strange noblemen and noble ladies looking at him he would be even more traumatized.

There were guards and wizards all over the place. It looked like they were expecting a demonic being to appear there and not a hero. What would happen to the people that were forcibly brought over here?

It looked like this king wouldn’t take a no for an answer. The heroes would probably start out fairly weak which would not help Zhang Dong with his situation. There was also a possibility that they would come with some kind of cheats included. This could hasten the process of them heading to the demon continent and getting the DemonKing.

“Is there something wrong Mr. Leigong, you look troubled?”

Beatrice turned to Zhang Dong, the white-haired man was intently looking at the summoning circle while everything was being prepared. Apparently thanks to the stars aligning in the right way this very moment it would be possible to summon these people. He himself knew that this was probably a lie and somewhere a cube was going to power this teleportation function.

“Ah, it’s nothing.”

It was finally time to start the ceremony. Many mages in blue robes gathered around this summoning circle and there was a large number of mana stones gathered as well. These stones were similar to spirit stones but Zhang Dong wasn’t able to absorb their energy as he could with the ones from his own world.

The king was just looking at everything from afar without even coming out from the castle. He was up on a large balcony and just sitting on a large chair. There were other people with him with various hair colors. It was clear that this guy had multiple spouses and children, Zhang Dong could spot at least 10 youths of various ages along with four women there. The king couldn’t hold a candle to Zhang Jin but probably for this type of world, he was in that ballpark.

Soon the chanting commenced, the magical circle lit up in deep blue and started shining. The sun had already set so it was quite the mythical show. Tiny blue lights danced around while forming the spell formation.

‘World rift detected.’

Bob sounded the alarm while Zhang Dong looked up to the sky. The clouds were opening up as rays of blue light descended to this magic pentagram. With his enhanced vision he could see something in that hole in the sky. The image was flickering about but he could somewhat see into that world.

‘Are those cars? … what country is that… ‘

It was clearly a similar world that he came from, if it was the same was unknown. He couldn’t make out too much as the portal was opening from above the clouds so he could only see skyscrapers and cars that looked like small ants.

‘I think I have seen that tower somewhere, wait… could it be?’

“Now everyone, the stars will align, pour all of your mana into the summoning circle!”

The main court mage shouted out while everyone focused. The magical pentagram started shining brightly and a column of light shot up into the sky above. It was really bright and even caused some of the nobles to avert their eyes. Zhang Dong on the other hand was staring at the whole display with much interest.

‘Bob, try to find the nuclei, it will probably give off some kind of energy signal when this summoning spell is activated… Also, what are my probabilities of survival if I jump through that hole in the sky right now?’

‘Calculating… data inconclusive…’

‘I figured…’

He could try jumping through this gate to another world but if he would be able to go through it was another thing. Then if he ended up in that world would he even be able to survive? What if it was his old mundane world and he would lose access to his system altogether? Then returning to his new home would be impossible.

In the end, he decided against diving into the large hole in the sky. It was more probable to gather to just gather more cube energy here and draw up a teleportation circle himself.

Soon more and more light burst through the sky and covered the entire area in warm light. Zhang Dong could feel someone slipping through the opening and being transported to this place.

‘One… two… four people?’

Even before the light stopped shining he could tell that there was more than one person present. The light began to fade and the opening in the clouds vanished from this world entirely.

‘Bob, did you get it?’

‘Affirmative, the location is 12….’

His trusty AI started listing him the geographical location of where the signal originated from. To his dismay, it wasn’t directly under this summoning circle but a bit to the side, which would put it directly under the castle. It was also quite far beneath the ground, further than the one that he spotted in his own world.

‘Damn, that puts me out of range of Beatrice and Isabella…’

If he ever wanted to go down there he would need to at least take Beatrice with him. How to explain the plan of digging down beneath the castle was something that he would need to come up with.

“It’s the heroes!”

“It really worked, the legendary heroes have arrived!”

Some of the younger nobles cheered while looking at the platform where the people were summoned to. Everything was quite loud and the youths out on the platform looked quite confused.

“Koko wa doko?”

“Hm?”

Zhang Dong listened to one of the summoned heroes speak up in a different language. This was a language that he was familiar with due to watching certain animated movies back in his old shut-in days.

What he saw was a group of dark-haired Asians. There was one youth of about fifteen or sixteen years of age and around him were three young girls. The group of girls varied in age, size, and demeanor.

There was the young sister type with twin tail hairs. There was the busty older sister with quite the chest. Then to end it there was the one in the middle that more or less was a combination of the two. The young man on the other hand looked quite average, he wasn’t that tall or muscular, just normal in all sense of it.

“Is… Is that a harem protagonist?”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 302

What Zhang Dong was looking at was a group of high school kids. They were wearing matching school uniforms and even carrying bags. It was clear that the summoning ritual forcefully pulled them over here.

This was different from how he got here. After filling up that strange email his mind was transported into the body of Zhang Dong. His previous persona of Matt was slowly being fazed away through all these years.

In his mind, he would always go back to his core beliefs but it was clear that he was slowly changing with time. Killing enemies and defending his loved ones was the biggest reason for that. Now he was a leader, one that needed to make hard decisions and prioritize the many over the few.

Now, these four were put in a similar situation but instead of leading others, they were here to kill demons. Those creatures didn’t pose a threat to someone as powerful as he was but to non-combatants as these, it would probably be hard to stomach.

He also robbed them of a few encounters by taking out three of these archdemons during his travels. Thus he might have saved them from actually having to participate.

‘Were these children supposed to arrive here at this time?’

Zhang Dong started thinking, he wasn’t here for long. Only about a month had passed since his arrival. If these youths came at this very moment the demons back in the academy wouldn’t have even shown themselves.

If he took this as a generic plot to a movie or novel then the kids here would be the protagonists. They would go through their training phase slowly fighting progressively more powerful demons till finally taking out one of the demon lords. The ones he fought were of similar power but they got progressively stronger with each iteration.

‘I wonder if they also have some kind of system like me…’

He turned to Bob, his Ai companion. He wasn’t visible to anyone besides him here as he resided in his soul world and reacted to inner voice commands.

‘Scanning… scanning… affirmative, signs of similarities to the user's system detected.’

After nodding he continued to look at the quartet. The kids sure looked confused with so many people staring at them. Even more, considering they were of a different race and from a different world. He didn’t notice it before but black hair was rarer here than blond or even the other exotic colors like green and blue.

‘Interesting… now what will this King do with these kids….’

“The heroes are here but the language they are speaking is foreign to us, mages!”

The butler-looking person called out to the group of mages. They quickly moved in to deliver some kind of accessories which they then tried giving to the scared kids. They looked to be earrings, probably they would convert the sound and let the youths hear this place's language.

There was a slight problem that these people miscalculated. These adolescent youths weren’t that trusting of the people gathered here. Everyone was looking at them as if they were zoo animals. The smallest girl quickly went behind the oldest while the only male from the group tried going forward to block the approaching mages with his body.

‘Hm, at least he isn’t a coward… though I can see that he is quite afraid himself…’

Zhang Dong could tell that the boy was sweating, his eyes were darting all around. It was clear that he was under a lot of stress but the mages continued pushing forward with outstretched hands, some of them even stepped forward while trying to put one of the earrings on one of the girls.

“Hey, get away from me you weirdo!”

The girl delivered a swift kick to the middle age mage that was going towards her. The man was clearly not expecting this as he fell on his butt while grasping his stomach. This girl looked like the more sporty type that was prone to anger, the look on her face was quite dejected.

“Is everything okay… the heroes look scared…”

Beatrice commented from the side while everyone looked at the scene playing itself out. It was clear that these kids weren’t prepared for the summoning. The people here were quite mistaken in thinking that the heroes would just accept this sudden turn of events.

Zhang Dong on the other hand knew very well how they felt. He also was scared when he first arrived in a strange new world. There were monsters lurking in every corner but he was lucky enough to have an iron body to protect himself. He wasn’t sure if these youths started out with enhanced capabilities. Their form of world travel was different than his so probably not.

“Don’t worry, let me handle this…”

The King that was hanging out in the back looked progressively angrier. If he didn’t do anything about this, there could be consequences for these rowdy high schoolers.

Thanks to him being quite of a weeb in his old days he had sat through many anime shows alike. Now with his enhanced intelligence, he was able to piece the language together that he once heard. The people here couldn’t understand what these scared youths were saying but he on the other hand could.

“Wait, what is that spirit doing…”

The king wasn’t alone in his booth, he was there with his current queen as well as with his concubines. His children and current crown prince were also here. This young man was in his early twenties and had a similar stern look like his father.

“Interesting… let us see what that spirit does…”

The king proclaimed which made everyone in this booth quiet down. Anyone besides the crown prince was afraid to utter a word, even he went silent the moment his father spoke up.

Down on the ground Zhang Dong had arrived at the scene of the summoning. Even before speaking to the high schoolers, he had Bob perform more scans on this area.

“Calm down, no one is going to hurt you.”

He proclaimed in Japanese while looking at the group of four. The girl that kicked the mage managed to get herself his staff and was now swinging it around against the others. The young man on the other hand was shielding the other two girls with concern in his eyes.

“W-what is this place, who are you people?”

“This is going to take a while to explain but let me ask you this first, are you really from Japan?”

The four looked at each other and then back to the somewhat imposing Zhang Dong. He was much larger than the kids and also looked out of place even among these mages. It was normal for them to also fear him but he was the only one that could speak their language.

“Y-yes, but where are we?”

Zhang Dong wanted to ask them about things concerning his old world. Things like the president from a popular country or what year it was. These youths could be from an Earth similar to his but not from the actual one that he came from. First, he had to talk them down and accept those earrings though, without them they wouldn’t be able to communicate.

“Well, this is another world. These people have summoned you to be their heroes. A somewhat selfish reason if I might add.”

“Another world?”

The boy asked while his eyes got big.

“Yes, I bet you saw many shows or read some books, it should have been a very popular genre in fiction…”

“How can this be another world? Take us back home!”

The sporty girl shouted out while pointing at him with the stolen mage staff.

“I wish I could but I’m not the one that summoned you here, it was the people from this world.”

“From this world? You speak as if you don’t belong here…”

The one that spoke out now was the oldest girl with the largest assets that was hugging the youngest girl against them. Zhang Dong wanted to not disclose the information about him coming from a different world. He didn’t really know the character of these four, telling them all of his secrets could bite him in the behind down the line.

Yet he felt a kinship with them. They were as he was, tossed into another world without any notice. The only real difference was that they weren’t alone when coming here but they also weren’t quite as strong. He could tell from just looking, they were just regular untrained humans. There was a certain potential behind them though, probably attributed to a similar system that he had.

“You’re quite observant, yes I’m also like you, a person from another world, though my origins are a bit different than yours…”

The four looked at him while he tried to smile. Being soft-spoken and kind-looking wasn’t really his forte. Mostly what he did was look mysterious or be a reliable teacher. He was still working on the reliable part though.

“What are they talking about, shouldn’t we stop them? How does it know the language of the heroes? Was it a hero before?”

People at the sidelines continued to watch as the summoned Spirit that belonged to Beatrice conversed with the Heroes. There were a lot of rumors about him, maybe now they would think that he was some kind of born-again legendary hero.

“Enough, tell them to accept the magical devices.”

A rumble was heard from behind as the King finally spoke out. His voice wasn’t loud but thanks to the infusion of mana it could be heard by everyone here. The group of high school kids trembled for a second as the voice and mana that was carried with it washed over them. It was something that their bodies weren’t used to so they instantly dropped down to their knees while panting.

“This guy has no tact…”

Zhang Dong waved his hand which caused the mana that was pushed out by the King to vanish. It looked like the man was trying to assert some dominance over these kids here. Regretfully if it came down to a fight, in his current state Zhang Dong would be on the losing end.

“We don’t have much time, listen here. Don’t trust the King and the people here, they just want to use you but for now, you will have to follow their instructions. The earrings that they offered you will allow you to understand their language. You probably aren’t aware of it yet but you have certain capabilities that will let you grow strong in a short amount of time. Use this time well but with some luck, you won’t need to act.”

Zhang Dong quickly told them the bare bones of what they needed to know. The most important fact was not to trust the people here. They would probably try to pull them to their side and use them as disposable pawns in their fight against the demons. What would happen to them after that was done was up to debate.

“I’ll try to visit you later, for now just listen to what they tell you but be careful and best to keep our conversation for yourself.”

He picked up an earring that had fallen down and handed it to the male of the group before heading out. While leaving he looked at the king that was glaring in his direction.

‘Ah, he has such a punchable face…’

After groaning inwardly he decided to go back to Beatrice and the group she was in. The heroes finally decided to put on the earrings and the ceremony continued, now without his involvement.

‘I wonder if I could dig up that cube... Well, not like it's going anywhere. I can focus on the demons, for now. Then come back and dig it up later...’

He thought to himself while moving back to his summoner, the day as not yet over so he would take his time to keep an eye on these new world travelers.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 303

“Sato-kun are you sure we can trust that person…”

“I don’t know…”

“I don’t like that king, he had a condescending look!”

The group of youngsters were talking while gathered in one room. This was already the following day after the summoning occurred.

All of them were on the way to school while they were trapped in the summoning ritual. The male youth of the party was called Sato Takeshi. He was just a regular average boy at the age of sixteen. The only thing that caught a person's eye when looking at him was how average he was.

Then there was his class mate Takagi Ami. She was the one that kicked the mage when he was offering them the earrings. She and Takeshi were childhood friends and had known each other since they were small.

Lastly, there were two sisters, Sakura that was the youngest at 13, and Yua Yamamoto was the oldest at 17. They were his neighbors and all of them always met up on the same street while going to school. This time on the other hand they were blasted into a foreign land and greeted by magical beings.

“The king was scary but the prince was…”

Sakura blushed a bit while happily munching on some sweets that were given to them by the castle maids. All of them were being treated quite well, given new fashionable clothes and interesting food that they had never tasted before.

“Which one? There were like… five of them?”

“Hm… the one with green hair!”

Sakura replied after Ami asked her this question. The girl tried remembering which one that was but there were two that fit the bill. The shades of hair colors in this world were quite confusing.

“What about that white-haired man? They called him Leidong? Do you think he is more trustworthy?”

Yua asked Sato again while the other two girls were eating the sweets. It looked like those two weren’t taking things as seriously as the rest.

“I think it was Leibong. He did speak our language but I’m not sure we can trust him either, he might be hiding something from us”

“That guy? Are you sure you aren’t jealous of his looks Takeshi?”

Ami smirked at the youth while he frowned at the question. It was true that he couldn’t compare in any shape or form to that Leigong character but that wasn’t the problem. This person was apparently like them, from another world. He also placed a seed of doubt in them by telling them not to trust the king or the people here.

“That person wasn’t wrong, the people here are strange… they are letting us have all these things but we aren’t allowed to leave this room without an escort…”

Ami said while finishing up some food. It might have seemed like they were being wined and dined but there was a restriction placed on them. They were unable to go out, they needed to ask for permission. Even now there were armored guards outside this very door and they were placed here to wait for further instructions.

“What do you think big sis?”

Yua thought for a moment before smiling and clapping her hands together.

“I think we can trust that person, he seemed genuine.”

“If big sis says we can trust him, then we can trust him!”

The youngest girl with the twin tails commented while moving both her hands up into the air.

“I’m very happy that I am so trusted!”

A manly voice resounded through this room and the youngsters jumped up the moment they heard it. It was clearly the voice of the man they spoke to previously. The group wasn’t wearing the translation earrings at this moment and speaking in their native language. The white-haired man was the only one that could understand them here.

“C-cute…”

The first to notice him was the youngest girl. Zhang Dong had squeezed in through the closed window as a mass of magic particles and reformed his body into his small form. He was now a rather cute version of himself at a whole eleven inches of height.

“By the way… It’s Leigong, not Leidong...“

He had decided to pay them a visit. After he was done with his talk he was unable to converse with the kids anymore. They were moved over to meet up with the king, there a long-winded speech ensued about needing their help to save the world. They were clearly trying to somehow bring them over to their side. It was clear to him that they only saw these kids as a potential war asset.

The visit with the king wasn’t the only thing that they went through. They were also clued in about their versions of the system. Previously Zhang Dong had figured that there was no such thing as that in this world but that was only for the regular people living here. These youths on the other hand were different.

They were able to access a game-like interface that closely resembled an RPG game system. They apparently had things like strength, agility, intelligence, and other attributes that they could see themselves. It was somehow similar to his own system but he could only measure people by cultivation levels. This system that the kids had was a bit different and more akin to a game than his own.

Only these high schoolers had access to it just like him. After the activation, they were taught to use some skills like identification. They just needed to concentrate a bit on the desired item or person and think about it. They would then have a description of it in their status. The description depended on the intelligence stat and the skill level and also on the level difference.

If they tried to examine Zhang Dong they would only get question marks. This was also what most of them were doing. The question marks along with the red color proved that he was way out of their league.

“You won’t be able to see my statistics, even if you strain your eyes that much, little missy…”

Sakura the youngest one was not good at hiding her attempts at scanning.

“Who are you calling little? You’re shorter than me!”

“Hah, this form is only temporary. You on the other hand are probably past your growth spurt.”

Sakura was quite short compared to the rest of the young people here, even for her age she would be considered quite meager. He wanted to laugh as the young girl started going red in the cheeks and pouting. The other youths in the room weren’t that relaxed though and he couldn’t fault them for it.

“Getting used to the new world? I see they have you under lock.”

He floated around in his small form which made the kids realize that this was really a different world filled with magic.

“Don’t be concerned, I just wanted to discuss a few things with you. If everything goes as planned you will be able to return back home without even facing any demon or monster.”

The small group had heard about the battle against the demons that the people were having but there wasn’t anything specific. They were to train with some knights and get used to the equipment. Each and every one of them had some specialized skills along with a corresponding Hero class.

Takeshi had the ‘Sword Hero’ class, Yua had the ‘Healing Hero’ Class, Sakura was a ‘Mage Hero’ and Ami was a ‘Fist Hero’. Two close-range fighters and two supports looked to be your generic setup, the thing they lacked was a thief or an archer.

From the class names, it was painfully obvious what archetype everyone was given. The only male in the group had the popular sword as the main weapon. It seemed like he would be the main character while the girls acted more as supporters.

Even now Zhang Dong could feel like there was something off here. After further examination and with the help of Bob he figured out why. Takeshi was apparently the only one with a full system while his friends had only some pseudo ones that were connected to his own. It was clear that he was the protagonist of this story just like Matt as Zhang Dong was of his own.

“Why should we trust you?”

Takeshi stepped forward while looking down at the smaller Zhang Dong.

“Would you rather trust that King? Or did you fall for one of the princesses already?”

He was on the sidelines during the introduction but the King of this country didn’t act very welcoming. He just sat there on his throne while not saying much. He had one of the princes use his charm on the girls while a pink-haired princess was all over Takeshi. The youth acted similar to him when he had his first experience and was probably still shaken up to this very moment.

“He is right, you had a dirty look on your face Takeshi… animal!”

Ami commented while the three girls looked at the boy. They were clearly judging his performance from the day ago.

“Don’t worry I’m not judging you but you have to hold back those hormones. You girls weren’t better off, I saw you looking at that princes…”

Moss' head was quick to strike in trying to get into the good graces of Ami here. One of the older brothers on the other hand moved into court the other young ladies. They were all good-looking young men and women, these kids here stood no chance to their allure.

“What, I was not looking…”

“Oh my…”

Ami denied it all while Yua just grasped her cheeks and blushed. He wasn’t really blaming them for acting like this as this was clearly done to keep them in check. Every hero would probably have a member of the royal family assigned to them like this. They were all beautiful in their own way and looked exotic to these youths.

“Well, I could teach you a skill to clear your mind and not be affected by your hormones if you let me but first we need to discuss some things.”

Zhang Dong had sneaked in here before the youths could be led out to train. Thanks to Isabella’s water spirit that could camouflage herself quite well he was able to gather some information.

They were planning to train the heroes up while also not allowing him to move as freely anymore. The king had ordered Isabella and Beatrice to remain in the city for now and also they were to help the heroes progress. They would be assigned to be their party members which meant that they would have to wait for them to grow enough.

He wouldn’t just sit there twiddling his thumbs around, he had to figure out a way to get out of here sooner. The king was blocking him from moving forward into the demonic continent where the other demon lords resided. Taking him out was not an option as this would make Beatrice and Isabella an enemy of the whole kingdom.

The only way out was to make these kids progress faster and for that, he needed to know how their system worked. By knowing the ins and outs he was thinking of doing some good old-fashioned power leveling.

Luckily apparently below this very castle, there was some strange dungeon that only opened up when the heroes were summoned. It appeared to be the training spot for them, maybe there he could raise their levels to the stratosphere.

“Let us start with how I got here and then I can explain my plan to you…”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 304

“Um…Leigong-san are you sure this is the best way to do this?”

“What do you mean? Of course, it is, now stab it through the eye… though I think you could also do it through the ear, just be sure to hit the brain.”

Takeshi, dressed in light armor and with a steel sword in his hand was looking at Zhang Dong who was holding something. It was a large orc looking monster, it was the type of orc that was more pig like but also had green skin.

“You must land the last hit to get the experience you’ll get even more if it's a critical hit, aim for the eye!”

The youth with the sword wasn’t alone here, with him was the whole party of girls. They were all looking from the sidelines. Some of them were covering their eyes while others were peeking from between their fingertips.

“O-okay…”

Takeshi took off running and activated one of the basic skill called ‘Sword Thrust’. His steel sword started glowing in blue before increasing in speed and penetrative power. The Orc was subdued and stationary so it was quite easy to land the critical hit through the eye socket.

“UuRGhhh…”

The orc cried out for a moment before succumbing to the deadly injury. Soon its body disintegrated into many tiny particles. These small glowing dots formed a torrent of energy and headed towards Takeshi and entered his body. Soon the youth watched as his status screen popped out before his face signaling him that he gained a couple of levels.

“See that wasn’t that hard!”

“Y-yeah…”

Zhang Dong looked at the people gathered here. They were in a special dungeon that was opened up right after the Heroes received their classes and unlocked their class system. He was sure it had something to do with this world's scenario as this place was clearly a tutorial stage that helped these kids earn levels easily.

This dungeon had many levels and was situated directly under the capitol castle. It reminded him of the smaller version of Cthulhu that he fought. It also was right at the spot that he appeared on and was corrupting weaker monsters that he could train against. It was his first real obstacle that let him achieve a small breakthrough in his own demeanor. Only after defeating that monster did he start to gain confidence.

Now these youths were in a similar situation. Thanks to Isabella’s and Beatrice’s positions they were able to wiggle into a spot at the heroes party. There was actually quite a large number of people here. Just like he thought the members of the royal family were trying to weasel their way into the hearts of these heroes.

There were princes in costly shiny armor here along with the cute princes that was adept at buffing magic. She was constantly staying close to Takeshi and batting her long eyelashes at him. Even though Zhang Dong had told him to not trust them the young man was not good at listening.

The youth was constantly blushing and sneaking in peeks at the pink haired princess. It was clear that this was the first time that a beauty of this caliber had given him so much attention. There was no way of him not falling for her, he was barely sixteen with no experience at all. This all felt similar to his first real experience that he had so long ago with that one vixen.

‘I wonder if she is still at the sect…’

His thoughts trailed off to his home again. He had been trapped here for over a month now and time was ticking down. After defeating the three demon lords there was no new news about the other ones.

The first Demon lord of Pain he had forced out into the open. The second one was an established Archdemon with his own little territory that people knew about already. The monster was kept under wraps but no one could fully get rid of it till he came along. The last one had freshly descended into the human domain through a ritual and was also now gone.

Zhang Dong was out of options as he had already gone around the known continent and tried to find more demons. After his little eradication spree they were now in full hiding mode. The only place one of them could be in was one of the buried dwarven countries or somewhere on the island of the elves.

The former was unlikely as the long ears had a vast array of protective magic along with detection spells to counter any evil beings. Though the Principal was also an elf and she had a demon working for her as a maid. Thus there could be a high ringing demon hiding there but it was also possible that there were no more Demon Lords on this side.

It was possible that the two last Archdemons were waiting for them behind the huge barrier between continents. News of three of their generals being killed had probably reached their ears. It would be stupid of them to not be cautious and just continue invading in the same way as they did before.

“Oh my, Lord Takeshi let me bring you some water, you must be parched…”

“Ah, thank you Princess Delilah.”

While thinking about how to get the other two corrupt gems from the Demon Lords he was reminded why he came here. The Princess was all smiles and cheering on Takeshi while her handsome male counterparts were talking it up with the female heroes.

“But I didn’t really do much… Leigong-san held it in place.”

‘I thought this would be a harem route… but everyone is getting their own prince or princess to play around with…’

The same princess looked at him after Takeshi mentioned his name. He could tell that under those girly smiles there was anger and resentment. Due to his involvement these royal family members were having a hard time kissing up to the heroic party.

What he did was to examine their versions of the system. He needed to figure out how it worked and how to increase their fighting power further. Without these heroes getting to a certain point the King would not allow them to leave this place or go to the demon country.

To actually begin the invasion they would need the three great races to open up the barrier surrounding the continent. Zhang Dong had actually examined this barrier and could tell that without reaching at least the early realm of nascent soul he would have no way of going through it.

Attempting something like that would probably drain his human batteries which were Beatrice and Isabella. Even if he got the barrier open he would probably not have any energy left to contend with any of the demon lords for at least a day. The demonic army would probably just not sit idly by after the barrier was gone though. That approach could just doom the entire human race and all the others.

The system was a bit similar to his old one with mostly a switch in genre. Instead of cultivation realms, the high schoolers were shown classes and levels. They had one main hero class which was static while the subclasses could be advanced further.

Takeshi for instance was a Hero : Sword User, After reaching level ten he was able to change his class into Hero : Swordsman he was now at level fourteen and which also indicated that higher classes had more requirements for further evolution. The girls had the same options like changing from a Hero : Healer to a Hero : Cleric and so on.

How they gained experience and levels was very RPG like. They only needed to kill monsters and they would absorb the energy as experience which was then converted to levels. Zhang Dong also noticed that there wasn’t much loss of anything after killing, almost all of the energy was quickly absorbed into their bodies. It was as if their bodies were perfectly created to get this energy.

Their skills would level up a bit differently. They received separate points that could then be spent to level up skills that they deemed worthy. There was also the possibility of leveling them up by using them and training. Just like with the Ork now, when Takeshi landed the killing hit while using his skill. He would get a lot more points to spend in his build like this than by training the skill himself repeatably by himself.

Thus he came up with the fastest way of giving the kids a boost by power leveling them. There was no loss in experience if he helped them, the person that scored the last hit would get most of the points. What he would do was to subdue the more powerful monsters and hold them in place with his overwhelming aura. Then one of the heroes would deliver a few blows to critical areas.

The biggest problem at first was their cleric, the shapely big sister was unable to deliver any kind of punishment to even the weakest monster. Luckily for them her magic had the holy attribute to it and there were some undead creatures in this maze like dungeon. He only needed to find a particular monster that each of these youths was good against.

Monsters weak to magic were pitted up against Sakura who was a mage. Ones that were weak to blunt attacks had to suffer under Ami’s fists and kicks. While Takeshi took out mostly regular creatures that could be pierced by his sword or could have their head severed. He was the easiest to level up from the whole bunch and also had the highest stats. It was clear that he was the main protagonist of the story.

“Mr. Leigong do you need any help?”

Beatrice called out from the side while dressed in some battle gear. She was wearing a nice summoner robe that boosted her magic power. Next to her was a bored Isabella who was looking with disgust at a certain green haired prince.

“Not really, you both can relax and do some breathing exercises. These monsters are quite weak, if an Archdemon doesn’t pop up we should be fine.”

With the excuse of Hero protection he was assigned to this party along with his summoner. Lucky for them the King wasn’t that impressed with him for some reason. He wasn’t sure why but maybe he thought that he didn’t have anything to fear from a summoned spirit.

This was probably true as he was quite limited by his summoner. Zhang Dong feared that Beatrice’s life would be in danger if he ever got out of line. That didn't mean that he wouldn't act if the king got out of line. He was already thinking of a couple of bluffing tactics that he could use.

“Okay listen up kids, there is a boss chamber ahead of us! Here is the plan…”

Everyone perked up as due to Zhang Dong the whole adventure part of this trip was being called into question.

“I’ll hold it down and you’ll whack it. We’ll have to be sure that everyone gets enough whacks in to spread the experience out equally!”

The people narrowed their eyes and just continued forward. This type of fighting was easy but also quite boring.

“Now let us head out!”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 305

A set of large doors were opened and a man dressed in a colorful tunic walked through them. He had his head lowered and quickly dropped down to one knee. Silence filled the room only when he heard the order did he reply.

“Speak.”

“Yes my King, we have news concerning the dungeon.”

“Mmm, how far have they gotten? Don’t tell me that they weren’t able to even get to the 10th floor?”

“No my King, actually…”

The man that came with the news stopped himself before speaking out as if scared to utter the next sentence.

“Get on with it!”

A malicious magical aura filled the room and brought the man down to both his knees.

“T-they completed the dungeon all the way to the 99th level and the heroes managed to find all of the holy weapons!”

The man was quick to reply and felt the weight be removed the moment he finished the sentence. He managed to peek up and noticed that the King had an unusual facial expression. Most of the time he looked mad and grumpy but this time around he seemed to be confused.

“It’s only been two weeks, how is this possible. The heroes of old were said to have spent many months before being able to complete it.”

“W-well my king… actually…”

“What is it now!”

The king smashed his hand into his large chair which made people flinch.

“They had apparently reached the 98th level within a week…”

The messenger painted a picture for the king. From what they knew the spirit that belonged to Beatrice was helping the youths gain levels at an increased pace. He would disable monsters for them and they would only deliver finishing blows.

The dungeon was a magical place built by an old sage from days past. No one really knew how it worked but it activated when the heroes arrived. The creatures inside would somehow miraculously regenerate themselves after a while and give the heroes power after they were slain.

This place was used to get the heroes up in strength to face the demon lords. It was there to put them on a somewhat equal footing or so said the legends.

Due to Leigong’s involvement what should have been a tiresome process of combat changed to a small expedition. The man reported that this spirit bulldozed through the lower levels not even giving the heroes a chance to level up. Only at about the middle level did he start letting them perform attacks.

Unbeknownst to the king and his aides, Zhang Dong was just performing a basic power leveling tactic. There didn’t seem to be any restrictions so he chose the strongest monsters available for the heroes to kill.

This was just basic mathematics. Why let the heroes fight monsters that gave 10 experience at a time when he could just let them deliver a critical blow to one that gave 1000 experience points. Holding them down didn’t seem to work against him, it was as if the system didn’t see his involvement as anything out of the ordinary.

The dungeon would end after the last boss was defeated so after arriving at the 98th floor he took the chance to level the kids up as far as they could. Only after the monsters started giving meager rewards did they move up to the final boss.

“It seems that the last floor was actually completed by the heroes without the spirit’s involvement…”

The king had retainers keeping an eye on everything happening in the dungeon. They did allow Beatrice and Isabella to participate thanks to their spirit. The king wanted to keep an eye on them and there was nothing better than examining how the spirit does against the dungeon monsters.

He had no way of knowing that they would finish it in about two weeks. The people that he sent inside weren’t even able to send consistent reports. Everything was happening too fast as the whole hero party steamrolled through the monsters inside the dungeon.

The magical devices that they had to communicate with the outside were apparently also not working correctly. There was always static and it was hard to make out anything. Also due to the fast pace, there wasn’t that much time to make a proper report. Even less when the scary Lightning Emperor was looking over their shoulders.

“So they managed to complete the secret dungeon?”

“Yes, my Liege!”

The man replied after being finished with the report. The dungeon went down and the party had food to last them for a month but no one expected for something like this to happen. The king thought that he would have half a year to slowly work on the heroes.

When they were weak and gullible it was the perfect time to place a seed of doubt in them. He was afraid that if they got too powerful they could turn against him. This was also why he was using his offsprings for courting.

He hoped that they would control the people from the other world through their emotions. The king even encouraged his kids to have sexual relations as a baby would tie the heroes to the royal family. Only with strong bonds like those would he be able to relax.

“It's that blasted spirit isn’t it? No… could it be…”

Before continuing with his train of thought the king waved his hand to indicate that the messenger was allowed to leave. The man just bowed and quickly removed himself from the throne room glad that he could finally go rest.

“Bernard.”

“Yes, your Majesty?”

The man that looked like a high-class butler appeared from the side and bowed before the king.

“What do our spies say at the Hohenberg house? Did they start moving?”

“Our people haven’t been able to find anything out of place, it would seem that the Duke isn’t involved.”

“Impossible! Damn incompetent fools, tell them to get more information!”

The king started to rage while also causing his throne armrest to splinter into tiny chunks with his fist. The man called Bernard remained standing while being able to hold his composure. It was as if he was used to these outbursts.

Others could feel the castle rumbling as the King continued to let his emotions out. In time he managed to calm himself and sat back down on his destroyed throne.

“The Hohenbergs might still be holding a grudge since ‘that’ incident. This spirit might be just the beginning, prepare the men, make sure that everyone is on alert, and increase the guards. Be sure to question the members that were with the hero party, we need to know if those Hohenberg’s are plotting anything!”

Since Leigong showed up the King couldn’t stop worrying. The spirit outmatched him in strength, the magical soul attacks were unable to harm it in any way. He was quite certain that if he struck fast he could take out the summoners before this spirit could act. The king was a very cautious man, there were far too many unknown factors here.

There were situations where a spirit went berserk the moment their summoner was slain. It could function for a couple of minutes which could be enough to deliver a deathly blow. This was mostly the reason why he hadn’t done anything, fearing that this overpowered spirit could kill him after he crippled its summoner.

There was also the whole predicament with Duke Hohenberg. The man had a large territory and army of flying dragons. The man could also come asking for trouble or even go to another kingdom for aid. There was too much risk in acting for now but something had to be done as the heroes had progressed away from schedule and before he could prepare more contingencies.

Before a new plan of action could be thought through the whole castle started to rumble. It started off slowly but soon transformed into a giant earthquake that caused the marble floors to crack.

“What is this? Is the Demon King attacking?”

The magical king spread his senses to try to find the cause of these tremors. But even when he looked far and wide he couldn’t spot any demonic energies or any foreign attackers coming from outside. His attention was then moved towards the lower regions and he noticed something.

“T-the secret dungeon is crumbling?”

He could feel that the many tunnels that were below the castle started to cave in. It wasn’t an attack from outside, nor did any monsters pour from within the premises. The dungeon that was under the castle for many generations started to crumble.

“How could this be, the legends never said anything about this?”

The man looked to his retainers that were running around like headless chickens. The castle was shaking violently while slowly sinking down. This wasn’t the first time that a hero summoning had been done. The dungeon was used by previous generations and even after the last boss was slain nothing like this was written down in the texts of old.

During the chaos, he also felt something, a massive surge of power coming from below. His eyes went wide as this strange power even overshadowed his own. Soon the person to whom this power belonged appeared.

He was hard to distinguish due to the large golden bubble of light surrounding him and his companions.

‘It's that damn spirit again… how could he be this powerful?’

The large sphere of holy energy burst through the ground and was now floating above the whole castle. It continued to shake and sink down into the ground for a good couple of minutes before about one-third of it was below ground. At that point, the shaking finally subsided.

Soon the inside of the sphere was revealed to have people inside. Beatrice, Isabella, and the heroes were all there. So were the people that the king had sent along on the expedition, all royal family members included.

Beatrice and Isabella were holding hands while channeling their power thus allowing Zhang Dong to reach his powered-up state. This state had gone up slightly since the start of the trip and was above the King in power.

“What is the meaning of this!”

The same king wasn’t amused after spotting Zhang Dong and the others. It was clear to him that they were somehow responsible for this disaster. In a fit of rage, he gathered his magical energies and flew towards this large bubble of power. Heading straight on a collision course for the group.

But as soon as he was near he saw the spirit called Leigong look at him. His eyes were glowing and he had a strange otherworldly aura of holy energies covering his body.

“An Emperor doesn’t take orders from a King, begone human!”

Leigong’s eyes glowed in a fierce hue before a massive surge of energy descended on the King of humans. He tried to protect himself but was unable to fight against this massive aura that this spirit gave out.

For the first time in his life, he was forced to retreat and this was done by his enemies' aura attack that overtook his own magical energies. Other people looked on from the sides as they saw their king fall down like a wet noodle and leave behind a small crater on the ground.

What was left was an astonished group that finally floated down from the sky. Leigong’s face remained without emotions as he looked at the human king that wasn’t able to contend with his power.

‘Hm, did I overdo it? Think he did receive the message though…’

Zhang Dong could see a glint of fear in this man’s eyes. Which was what he was aiming for. The expedition was more fruitful than he anticipated and he also received a nice reward at the end.

In his hand was what looked like a square box. This cube soon crumbled into dust and faded into the scenery.

‘This brings me closer to my goal… Don’t worry, I’ll be back soon.’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 306

Zhang Dong hovered above the partially sunken castle. It was still the tallest building in this city even though a third of it was now below ground. With him were all of the hero party members and also Beatrice and Isabella. Everyone was looking down with mixed expressions after he had sent the king blasting away to the ground.

“... D-did you have to do that?”

“He was asking for it!”

He replied to Beatrice while shrugging.

“I could take him out if you want, just lend me some of that power.”

A big grin appeared on his face while the two girls waved their heads to indicate a refusal to this option. They were already powering down so Zhang Dong was running on fumes but he was sure to give the King a little scare. From what he could tell, this stunt had worked and he had successfully planted some doubt in this magical king’s heart.

“No, please don’t do that…”

Finally, the group started to descend down into a mostly undestroyed area outside of the castle. Everyone was still baffled by how far it sunk down to where the dungeon they were previously in was.

Zhang Dong started to recall what transpired down below and how this predicament came to be. It was mostly what the spies reported to the king. They all moved quite fast while he disabled the monsters for the heroes to defeat. For some reason he could function better the further down they descended and he attributed it to the cube that he had found below.

The last chamber on the 99th floor had a giant hydra monster with many heads lurking. It was supposed to be the hero's final test which they succeeded in doing even without his help.

After taking time to overlevel them to the fullest the boss monster was easy to beat. It had a rather easy-to-read fight pattern which the four youths could counteract with their skills. Due to their increased stats, the monster was unable to hit them or even deal much damage. When it did the healer of the party could just bring everyone back to full health without losing many mana points.

While the fight was underway Zhang Dong activated his map while making sure that no one would die. There he realized that there was a large black spot that he couldn’t examine and it was right past this chamber.

After the Hydra was slain it disintegrated into tiny particles of mana. These went into the heroes but some were carried down into a certain chamber. In there they found the legendary weapons that were meant for the heroes.

Sword for the sword hero, gauntlets for the fist hero, and so on. They all looked like ancient artifacts with cool designs. In Zhang Dong’s eyes, they weren’t all that great and about the level of high earth grade treasures. If he had had the materials he could fashion a half step heaven grade weapon.

This treasure room wasn’t all, he soon discovered a nearby wall that followed a similar pattern to the one he saw in his own world. He was scanned like before and allowed to enter the chamber inside.

It was a carbon copy of the cube room that he saw back then. He didn’t just snatch it like a greedy madman. He had Bob do a few scans and answer a few questions. The biggest problem he had was leaving these kids here out to dry.

When he took this item he would sentence the youths to a long life here. They already had superpowers but would not be strong enough to go against nations. He couldn’t just leave them here without being sure that they wouldn't get in trouble.

They might be like him and actually, like the new world they live in but they were a lot younger than he was when this happened. While he was an adult that had taken a bad turn in his life and the new world was a chance to start anew. These youths weren’t even in their twenties, they never even had a chance to spread their wings at home.

Luckily after some scans, Bob informed him that it would be possible to triangulate the world that the youths came from with this cube. He would need to use up some of the stored power but there would be some left for him to use.

This was an acceptable resolution to the problem. After defeating the demon king and the rest of the demons he would be able to send the kids back home by himself. He wouldn’t even need to come back here as the schematics for the teleportation formation were already in his head.

The only problem was the moment he decided to reach for this cube. Bob had forgotten to tell him that the whole dungeon would collapse when he did that. This was new to him as no such thing happened back in his own world. Here on the other hand the moment he absorbed the energy the whole place began to shake.

Everyone started panicking and he quickly returned outside. The whole place was collapsing onto itself and the whole group of people was trapped 99 levels underground. It was all up to him to save everyone, with the help of Isabella and Beatrice he powered up and protected everyone with his barrier.

The rest was history, now he was looking at a somewhat slanted sunken castle and a surprised King. He was sure to raise his chin up to look quite lofty, just like an Emperor would act. He needed to sell his superiority and that he wasn’t afraid of this man in any sense or form.

In reality, he would probably be downed by one punch if this guy decided to attack him now. His power level was still at the lower end of core formation even absorbing the cube didn’t really help him with that.

“Father!”

“Daddy!”

The members of the royal family could see their father slowly getting up from the rubble. His hair was messy and his royal robe was also dusty. This was the first time they had ever seen him taking a loss like this. They were still afraid of his might so they didn’t comment much about it.

Before they could move towards him the king moved his hand up to stop them. All of them soon parted to the side while the King looked to the white-haired spirit and the heroes behind him.

The King continued to stare for a moment, the people here gulped as they could see sparks flying between the two older men. Soon the royal guards arrived at the scene to back up the king, the moment they arrived the old man gave out a snort and turned around.

Soon he started flying away while his own kids began to chase after him. Zhang Dong turned around as well, he wanted to compliment himself on his poker face skills that were now almost perfected.

“Mr. Leigong was that really necessary?”

“Of course it was.”

Beatrice asked and slumped her shoulders forward after Zhang Dong was quick to reply. The four heroes behind them started to laugh as after the journey in the dungeon they started to open up.

It was clear to them now that Zhang Dong was a person from their own world. At least from one that was quite similar. They had the same politicians and countries as well as continents.

The date was also really close, the time in his original world seemed to be moving slower as it looked that only about a month had passed since his disappearance. For him, it was already years, if he returned he could probably just say that he went through a midlife crisis and return to his old life.

This was not something that he wanted to do. Why return to a dead-end job when he was a respectable Patriarch? The only thing that his old world had going for it was the internet and video games. Now after spending time as a powerful cultivator such things as video games lost their appeal. Though there were a few things that he missed, arguing on the internet while being anonymous was one of them.

“Are you sure you should be doing that?”

Takeshi asked while holding his large sword over his shoulder. The youth was now fitted in a shiny new armor along with a brand new sword. His companions had also found ‘legendary’ items that somehow all fit their frames perfectly. Though the caster girls were wearing robes one black and the other white.

Zhang Dong turned his head to the group of youngsters. He wasn’t sure why but Takeshi looked a lot manlier now than just two weeks ago. It could be due to the stats increase which somehow also affected his stature. Gone was a mostly skinny boy and now he was looking at a toned strapping young lad.

His tone had also changed and he sounded a lot more confident in himself. He mostly went through a week's worth of monster-killing but this was apparently enough to make his character shift. The only thing that could have done this so fast was his system, it had somehow boosted the youth’s confidence.

‘I wonder if it was affecting me as well before that…’

His mind went back in time to his own journey forward. He had used system points to buy the Tranquil Mind skill which then made him a lot calmer. Since then he had his head in the game but he could say that this was the system's effect and not him growing as a person himself.

‘As long as I wrap this up within this month they should be fine when they return home…’

Bob didn’t confirm anything as he didn’t have any data but he wasn’t sure what would happen to this system once it was through with the user. When sending the boy back would this system remain with him or would it vanish?

He knew that there was someone working in the background making these systems but for what reason he had no idea. There was a certain risk in sending the boy and the girls home with an intact system.

Would they be safe and sound, or would they explode when passing through to their original world? Bob continued to tell him that he doesn’t have enough data but after absorbing some more nuclei he could formulate an answer. Zhang Dong would need to wait until after he took out the demon king.

“Don’t worry, that King might be overbearing but he isn’t stupid. He won’t act unless he is 100% sure that he will be victorious. Why do you think he never attacked any of the demon lords?”

He answered while the group reorganized themselves. It was time to rest before asking for the construction of an attack force. If everything went well, they would be finally organizing an attack against the demonic beings.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 307

The word that the Heroes had been summoned reached the masses. The kingdom was unable to hide this fact after the large castle sunk down into the ground. They had to somehow appease the commoners that thought that their capital had been attacked by the demonic beings.

Soon the heroes with their brand spanking new legendary weapons were getting paraded around the city. Since leveling up Takeshi started to change, both in his looks and demeanor. He started acting cocky and was clearly enjoying how everyone looked at him with a twinkle in their eyes.

Zhang Dong was examining everything from the background. Ever since they got back from the castle things were being prepared. There was no reason for them to wait anymore but it would take some time to rally the troops.

Due to Zhang Dong’s power leveling, the youths levels had skyrocketed. They had probably reached a level that was above what they normally should after that dungeon. Instead of slowly fighting their way through normal enemies and then taking out a boss monster they were grinding on those very boss monsters instead.

The amount of experience had no cap which allowed them to reach a power level at the core formation level. With the weapons and armor and considering that there were four heroes, it could be possible for them to take out a demon lord. That is if their teamwork was satisfactory but there wasn’t really time for something like that to occur.

Easy kills thanks to Zhang Dong had made these kids powerful in general stats but that didn’t mean that they had good battle sense. An experienced opponent with lower stats and worse skills could be able to defeat them.

‘I wonder if it’s the system's fault… I made him reach close to his maximum potential. The nascent soul early stage is probably as far as anyone can go in this world.’

Zhang Dong could only speculate as his own system was somehow damaged when he almost died against the early stage nascent soul pride demon. But after Takeshi entered the core formation level of strength there was a shift in how he behaved.

He started looking forward to the battles even taking on monsters and demons alone. Even without Zhang Dong’s help, he started to be able to mow down his enemies. The difference in stats and skills was apparent.

There was a certain skill that allowed the kid to look at the world in slow motion while also being able to think fast. Due to it, he was almost able to react to anything coming his way. Zhang Dong started seeing him transitioning from a scared young man to a daredevil. The three other girls weren’t as bad but they also seemed to grow to like the battling.

‘Could the system affect someone’s psyche? Or was this something that was always in them from the start?’

“Hey Bob, can you access Takeshi’s system if I pull him into my soul dimension?”

“Not enough data…possibility of the task at 27%”

“I thought so…”

“Accessing user Takeshi’s system may prove fatal to user Matthew. Current user’s location could be discovered by an Overseer, caution is advised.”

“An Overseer?”

Zhang Dong recalled that this was how he was seen by the scanning AI in the place he found this or the previous cube in. From the naming sense, these Overseers sounded like some mods in a forum or chat. It also sounded like there was someone above them, an admin. This being could very well be the person that created this strange system and game-like worlds.

“Hm, won’t they become aware if I send the kids back to their own world not through the previously setup teleportation formation?”

After hearing the Overseers be mentioned he started to worry. Would they know that something went wrong if the heroes that were supposed to be here for years returned back in a month’s time? There could also be some kind of tracker or alarm system the moment the space between worlds was opened.

“User’s current system isn’t connected to the mainframe, tracking from outside isn’t improbable.”

“If you say so…”

He would have to take his AI’s word for now. There was no way for him to know if this would come biting him back. He needed to get out of there and send the children home, if an Overseer noticed him going around worlds was something that he couldn’t control. Bob here at least thought it was a bad idea to get involved with these world moderators.

“Is everything alright Mr. Leigong, you’re looking a lot more grumpy than usual?”

Beatrice brought him back to reality. While the party of heroes was being shown off to the masses on a large flying ship they were trailing behind on a smaller boat. Even though the size was a third of the one the heroes were riding on, it was still very lavish. It belonged to Isabella who was to the side sipping from a fruity drink. It was quite similar to the one he had made her at the tiki bar. Since then the blond with the drill hair had started loving these bubbly drinks.

“Just thinking about some things, I think we should go to the other kingdoms.”

“What’s the rush? The demons won't go anywhere.”

Beatrice stretched out while also drinking some sweet alcoholic drinks. From her and Isabella’s perspective, there was no reason to rush things. They would even like it if he took things slowly, mostly so that they could train and become better at their combination technique.

“You sure about that? Think they will just let us have as much time as we want?”

From his point of view, these demons should be doing something in the background. There was no way that they wouldn’t prepare anything after three of their strongest fighters were dead. Would they just twiddle their thumbs and await for the nations together with their forces only to then get attacked?

They could also think that the people of the races would never actually try to get rid of the barrier. This was something that would open the flood gates to an all-out war between everyone. Though from what he knew the whole barrier wouldn’t be broken, they would just fly in through a small opening.

It sounded all like the last map from an RPG where you go attack the demon castle. The heroes would remain inside while the normal people defended the small opening from lesser demons. Keeping it open for when the heroes needed to retreat.

‘I wouldn’t be surprised if they close the barrier behind us the moment we enter through it…’

“You’re worrying too much Mr. Leigong. I haven’t heard of a spirit that worried this much. Look at Undyne, she isn’t worrying.”

Zhang Dong looked to the side to spot the water nymph that Isabella still had. This spirit hadn’t been able to do much besides spying. It was just wiggling around while looking down at the people from the flying ship. It was even smiling and waving to them.

“Don’t compare me to her!”

He wasn’t actually a spirit that wasn’t able to think much. This water nymph had the intelligence of a six-year-old. Beatrice just chuckled while Zhang Dong thought about the ways to spice up the dream training.

The parade continued for a bit, it ended with Takeshi lifting up his holy sword and making a beam shoot up into the sky. The people cheered as their faith in the kingdom was restored. Some of them also glanced his way but were more interested in the two blond girls which were now official members of the hero party.

In a few days, it was finally time to pack up and leave. The ship that was lent to them by the Duke could still be used. They were even gifted two more with even more people and now also the heroes.

While they were slowly boarding Zhang Dong could see Takeshi walking together with the pink-haired princess. The three girls on the other hand had a prince to contend with. It seemed like the three old friends stopped talking to each other after a while, busy with their new partners.

It was clear that the King’s scheme to rope these youths was working. He couldn’t control them with strength alone so he switched it up. Since reaching the higher levels the high school kids also became more susceptible to their carnal desires. It was as if they were slowly losing themselves to this power.

“I should probably hurry, the longer we wait the more could happen…”

For now, he was here so he could look over these horny youngsters. He feared that if he left them to their own devices then an accident could happen. If it did it would be a lot harder to take these four back home. With an added family member they would need to remain here.

“First stop the dwarven kingdom, then the elven kingdom and then we will reorganize.”

He nodded to himself while talking in his regular form. Beatrice had also progressed thanks to the dungeon and the cultivation techniques that he gave her. She was now able to allow his full-sized form in clothes to freely walk around without a problem.

While they were departing another scene was playing out in the background. A blond-haired gentleman was kneeling down before a familiar-looking grumpy monarch.

“Do you know why I summoned you here, Duke?”

“No your Majesty.”

The man replied instantly while also standing up. His face was without any emotion while he looked at the strongest man in the kingdom.

“Don’t lie to me, you know what this is about. We had this talk, that time it was that old man from your family but this time...”

This was the father of Beatrice. His head turned to the flying ships that were on the horizon, his daughter on one of them.

“The spirit…”

“Yes, you know what I want.”

“What will happen to my daughter?”

“She is free to go, the one I want is the summoner. My people say that your daughter isn’t connected to it, so she may live.”

The man clenched his fist after hearing the response. He waited for a moment before bowing.

“It will be done…”

Soon he removed himself from the throne room and headed over to where his dragon was waiting for him. There he found one of his trusted retainers waiting for him.

“My lord.”

He was an older man with a full beard that was gray. His frame was larger than average and there were many scars on his face.

“Let us depart, we will gather the forces to aid with the hero's endeavor…”

The man bowed and moved to his wyvern that was standing right next to the Duke’s large dragon. As the man flew away to carry out the order the Duke looked at his summoned beast and gave out a sigh. He knew what must be done and he didn’t like it, just like before he would need to take the life of a family member. All this to protect his own line, to do this an innocent girl had to die.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 308

“So that’s the world tree huh? Thought It would be bigger...”

Zhang Dong commented while looking at a giant tree that reached up into the clouds. It was majestic and green but from someone used to things being large, this wasn’t that spectacular. Back in his own world, he had gone to forests with similar-sized trees already.

“What do you mean, it’s huge!”

Next to him, an astonished Sakura bounced around while looking at the large tree in the distance. All of them were on a large flying ship flying towards this very tree.

“If you say so…”

The only thing Zhang Dong could think about was the tree’s name Yggdrasil and how it was the same as the tree hugger sect that he bumped heads with. The naming sense from this world and his own was strangely similar. Even this tree’s name was a very popular name in fiction and games that was mostly used as the point of origin of elves.

Here as well, this tree was a focal point of their civilization. There was a legend that the first elves were birthed from this very tree. Only afterward would they proliferate throughout the lands the usual way. Even then the birth rates were quite low, many times below the human race. What they lacked in numbers they made up in magical power.

“The mana density around this forest is very high…”

Beatrice commented while also gawking at the large tree.

“So you’ve noticed, practicing your breathing technique here would boost your development. I’d say double it, at least?”

He replied while Beatrice’s eyes started sparkling. This girl had reached the mana capacity of an early-stage foundation establishment person. Isabella had also caught up and with this, it was a lot easier to keep up with the soul binding for the two of them.

Regretfully even with the power boost, he was still unable to tap into his full nascent soul power level. He was inching towards it slowly but it still remained in the half-step region. This mostly made him worry about his upcoming fight with the demon king. Would the monster be above him in terms of strength?

The only thing he could compare it to were the demon lords. They were at about the great circle of core formation, which made them easy targets for his half-step prowess. Through this he expected the demon king to be about at his level. The heroes he pushed through the dungeon weren’t all that strong either. He tried to base the maximum strength on the strongest person in this world that he met, which was the human king.

He didn’t think that whoever set up this world would let the heroes lose. So the demon king should not be that much off from this king that would never act on his own.

‘Though it could be one of this power of love or friendship endings where their power multiplies many times over…’

This was one of the options that he didn’t want to be true. If this was the ending it was going for here the demon king could even be at the very top of the nascent soul level. The heroes would have to have some kind of breakthrough during the fight or would get some aid from their system that would perhaps give them a temporary boost in power.

If something like this happened he would be in a lot of trouble. The demon king would make quick work of him and maybe even Beatrice and Isabella. This could actually push Takeshi and the three girls to get their breakthrough of power.

He was going off script though, so anything could happen at this point. Zhang Dong knew it was risky but he didn’t want to wait half a year to train the heroes and his two summoners. There were other ways for him to get power, for that he only needed the cooperation of the races and access to their people.

‘I’d have to construct some formations on these ships… I hope the elves give us some of theirs and also give me access to their library…’

They were finally here, the grand elven city. At least right in front of it. There was a large glowing barrier blocking their way forward. This one was much larger than the academy shield he pushed the demon lord against.

This made it clear that the elves' magical knowledge was above the humans. He could tell that this shield was of better quality even after one glance. It would be really hard for any demon to cross to the other side.

He could feel holy energy radiating off this shield. Any demon that came in contact with it would be incinerated by the holy fire it was made off. It was similar to his dao but felt a bit diminished due to the fire part.

Zhang Dong’s holy cultivation had been progressing at a steady pace after he came here. This was all thanks to him being able to focus on his soul which was related to this Dao. He expected a boost to his cultivation when he returned home. This soul expansion would cause his nascent soul power to be enhanced further even without reaching the next realm.

“We greet the heroes from the human kingdom and their followers.”

After being stopped for a while a group of beautiful golden-haired elves arrived. Their skin color was akin to the jade beauties from his own world. If Zhang Jin was here he would probably be going crazy at this sight before him. He on the other hand preferred the darker skin tone that a dark elf would have so this didn’t really get his heart pumping.

Just like before the Heroes were more important than he was. Most people didn’t realize that he was the main powerhouse of this journey quite yet. He didn’t want to argue with anyone about such a thing so he just left the talking to Takeshi and his party members while he waited in the background.

“Are you feeling well?”

He looked to Beatrice that was glancing at a particular green-haired youth. It was Prince Ludwig that switched from Beatrice to Sakura, the youngest member of the party. He was quite a handsome young lad and had a silver tongue. The young girl was unable to resist his approach.

He wasn’t the only royal family member here. Zhang Dong hoped to ditch them during this journey but they came as a package deal with the ships they were getting. He couldn’t go to the king and complain without the soul resonance up so he had to let it slide.

“I’m fine…”

It was easy to tell that the girl was still a bit mad at the whole predicament. From Zhang Dong’s perspective, this was actually a good thing. Beatrice was hit by reality, people weren’t always what they seemed to be. He hoped that she would learn from this event and grow. It was actually good that this happened now and not after she was too attached to that casanova.

“I'm ashamed that I ever considered someone like that as my fiance! Truly reprehensible!.”

Isabella was to the side as well, she looked quite annoyed. It was clear that she wanted to go over there and tell the moss head a few chosen words. She had to restrain herself though, he was still a prince. The girls here were unable to word their disdain due to the barrier in noble ranks.

“Just learn from this experience, I’m sure you’ll find yourself a fitting partner in time.”

“How about you marry Mr. Leigong Isabella.”

Beatrice poked the grumpy Isabella from the side after hearing the conversation.

“W-what? Marry him?”

Zhang Dong just smiled down at the two girls. Isabella went bright red in the face which only made him want to tease her more.

“Regretfully I’m already spoken for, but I’m flattered nonetheless.”

“Oh, you have a wife?”

Beatrice asked as he had somehow managed to evade this topic through his stay here. No one had asked him to marry him though, being a spirit and all.

“Ah yes and two kids!”

“Spirits can have children?”

Beatrice and Isabella looked at each other but soon they recalled that Leigong here wasn’t your average spirit. He was a special never before seen one with a somewhat strange unknown background.

“Well, here take a look.”

He wasn’t against talking about his own family. The girls were already close to him so he didn’t mind sharing some of his secrets. Though at this point in time they still knew him as a strange spirit and he didn’t mention him being from another world.

While the two girls moved closer he held out his hand and a little 3D hologram of Zhang Liena appeared. She was dressed up in an exquisite robe that she wore during their wedding.

“Oh… she is beautiful… but…”

The two girls' eyes wandered on the presented hologram and the shape of the woman’s body. Soon they both focused on the chest area that was quite prominent.

“Big…”

“Yes big…”

Both of them moved their hands to their own chests while looking at the hologram of Zhang Dong’s wife. He could tell that they were feeling defeated which only caused him to chuckle, his laughing didn’t go unnoticed.

“Does size really matter?”

“Yeah…”

He wanted nothing more than to rub it in but he also didn’t want these two girls to get some strange chest size complex. Due to this, he moved to the next hologram which was of his little cinnamon roll.

“Oh, who is this cute little girl?”

“She looks a bit similar…”

“I see that you have noticed, this is my oldest daughter, isn’t she cute?”

The girl’s eyes started sparkling as they saw the child moving around in the palm of Zhang Dong’s hand. While they were cheering he on the other hand started to get less excited. The sight of his daughter only caused the worrisome thoughts to enter his mind again.

The hologram then changed again to his wife holding a newborn in her hands while the older daughter was to the side full of smiles. He started staring at his family without saying a word only a louder call out from Beatrice managed to snap him out of it.

“Mr. Leigong, are you okay?”

“Ah...sorry about that…”

He moved his hand away while removing the hologram of his family. The two girls that he tried to cheer up were now looking at him with concern in their eyes.

“Well, it looks like Takeshi and the others are done with the elves, we will be moving into the elven city you two should get ready.”

Beatrice and Isabella looked at Zhang Dong who was clearly trying to shift the conversations. Before they could actually ask if he was really fine the flying shift jolted forward. They had to give up on their cross-examination as they would also be required to enter the elven city. There they were supposed to get the aid of the elves against the demonic beings.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 309

“Are you done Mr. Leigong?”

“In a moment…”

Zhang Dong was waving his hands around while some books and scripts floated towards him. Around there were some people like Beatrice and the elven folk. They were in the elven library and he was in the process of absorbing all of their knowledge.

“I’m sure you’re glad that you don’t need to touch these books anymore.”

He laughed as he remembered that in the beginning, Beatrice needed to poke the books by herself. Now with her reaching a higher realm of power he was able to move around freely and do this himself.

“There that’s the last one… do you have any more?”

“Yes oh illustrious Spirit Emperor, the secret texts are in the levels below, it would be a pleasure to lead you there!”

A beautiful elven woman prostrated herself in front of him while he tried not to laugh. He started to recall what had happened a few hours back when they arrived in this place. He was standing in the background at first and let the heroes do their thing.

He had discussed the plan with them beforehand and it looked like they had more status than a spirit like him. That would soon come out as a big mistake after they managed to get an audience with the elven monarch.

“It’s an honor to greet the Elven Queen!”

The biggest problem was that there were unwelcome guests with them. Three strapping young lads and one pink-haired princess that were clinging to the hero party. The oldest prince was the one that greeted the Queen this time around while the rest were left to kneel down.

That is, besides one white-haired person that was hanging out in the back. Due to the way he had set up his persona as a haughty and mighty Spirit Emperor he couldn’t just bow down before this woman. He did the same thing when he met the human king and he had to keep up appearances unless he wanted his act to crumble now.

This didn’t go unnoticed by the elven people around them. A large man in a pure white robe with his hands crossed over did stick out like a sore thumb.

“Show your respect to the Queen, human!”

One of the royal guards called out, it was a beautiful-looking man in a shiny golden armor. The elves in this world were matriarchal in nature, their men were mostly just used as guards. This was mostly due to the low birthrates which made the women a more valuable resource than the men. Thus they would do everything to protect their females while also putting one on the throne.

“I am no human, mortal!”

Zhang Dong keeping to his shtick delivered a direct attack to this man’s soul. He had learned a thing or two about those types of attacks during his stay here. He was unable to cultivate anything but his own soul, through the weeks he stayed here it had increased in size exponentially.

These attacks could not damage the outside shell which was the body but were devastating to the mechanism that kept it working, the soul. If someone was unable to protect themselves from a soul attack they would be paralyzed. Their body would stop functioning and they could even die if the connection was broken.

All of this could be done by putting your soul against another. These attacks had a large risk to them, they could damage the user’s soul which would cause a large backlash. A backlash was more volatile than being damaged by someone else's soul attack. This made this type of skill high-risk high reward. You were literally putting your life on the line whenever using it.

On the other hand, it was quite safe to use on anyone that had an inferior soul to the user. It made it quite a skill to take out many weaker enemies. This was now the case as Zhang Dong had to crank up the output. The other guards tried surrounding him but found themselves on their knees instead.

“Beatrice, control your spirit!”

The one shouting out was Prince Ludwig. He had quite the angry expression on his face, probably still angry about how Isabella tossed him to the side. Now he had to cling to Sakura’s thigh in hopes that his father gave him some assets that he lost.

“Silence! Before the Queen!”

Two elven women stepped out from the side. They were wearing white robes with some strange golden runic patterns. Each one had a staff, at the end a large shining gem that was radiating magical power. They slammed these staffs onto the floor to produce some kind of magical effect.

Zhang Dong felt like he had overdone it a bit with his Emperor act but luckily this magical attack was soul-based in nature as well. Because he was someone with an oversized soul with no one in this world matching up to it, it was quite ineffective.

These women mages expected their warriors to be set free from the spell that Zhang Dong produced but instead they saw it being repelled back towards them.

“How is this possible!”

They gasped while taking a step back, both of them perplexed at their magical attack not working.

“Who is that man, is he part of the hero party? But there were supposed to only be four!”

More people started arriving in the throne room. It was clear that Zhang Dong’s little soul attack had brought everyone’s attention to him. He looked unperturbed but deep inside he wanted to cry. They only came here to get help from the elves, have them lend them a few flying ships and a couple magicians.

The elven mages were really good at barriers like the one they constructed here. If they wanted to enter the demonic continent they would need the help of the elves to open the path. By how things were looking getting out of here in one piece had become the biggest concern.

“Silence mortals, you dare attack this Lightning Emperor Leigong!”

Zhang Dong decided that he might as well give it his all. He had already been quite disrespectful so there was no going back. Apologizing at this point would only show weakness and he still could use his soul attack against these weaker soldiers, the biggest problem was the Elven Queen.

She was at about the same level as the human king, trailing behind by a small amount. She would be able to defend herself against his soul attacks due to him being in his powered down state.

‘Can this be salvaged… should I tell the girls to get ready for a fight…’

He was slowly thinking that they might have to strongarm the elven faction into obeying them instead. If the diplomatic talks broke down this would be the only thing that remained. They still needed their knowledge which could also be gained by reading their secret texts. Before he could make a decision though he felt something coming his way.

The elven queen looked in his direction while squinting. She had remained silent for the whole predicament but it looked like she wanted a piece of him after her guards had failed. If she directly pitted her mana against his then he would surely lose but luck was on Zhang Dong's side.

‘Wait is she… these elves sure like the soul-based attacks...heh well come in if you wish.’

It was a direct attack against his soul world. He wasn’t sure if the Queen was just trying to test him after seeing him perform his own soul attack but he was glad that she did. Just like with the Vice-Principal before he sprung his trap. If it came to defending against such skills, there was no one who could out soul his soul.

“What!?”

The beautiful woman found herself in an open grass field. The sky above was clear with no clouds and everything looked peaceful.

She knew that she was just clashing against the unknown human that was in the hero party. There was no information about someone of that caliber so she thought that she could easily subdue him and force him to show respect. Even the heroes remained respectful but this rude man never even kneeled.

Now she was concerned, the path outside was blocked and she knew that her soul was somehow pulled into this dimension by this person.

“Who are you? … What are you?”

She shouted out with all her might as her voice echoed through the open grasslands. Her mind began connecting the dots while trying to piece everything together. There weren’t many beings in this world that were above her in might. She was already close to being a thousand years old and she had seen it all.

She was there when the previous heroes were here. She was there when they battled the previous demonic lords and there when the demon king was forced to retreat. Even then she couldn’t recall anyone that could do something like this.

“Who am I, Little one do you really need to ask?”

“This energy…”

The whole place began to rumble and the sunny sky began to become cloudy. Storm clouds approached and the wind picked up. Thunderous lightning collided with each other while the ground began to split apart. The elven woman was unable to access any of her magic, falling down on her posterior was the outcome.

“You have a lot of gall to address me in that tone of voice, mortal.”

The lightning bolts started shooting down from the sky onto the splitting earth. Soon it was like a torrent of plasma energy just descending from the sky, forming a humanoid figure.

Zhang Dong took shape as a being made from lightning energy. His face was somewhat distinguishable but he looked like a being completely made out of electricity. The huge electric giant looked down to the elven queen that was trembling down on the ground.

“S-spirit King? N-no Spirit Emperor!”

Her eyes bulged after seeing the form that was before her. This giant made from lightning was clearly giving off a strange mana signature akin to beings from the astral realm. Elves were beings close to this realm and mostly made contracts with nature spirits. Zhang Dong had shifted this energy slightly so that the elven queen would indeed think that he was a real spirit.

“I see that you have realized.”

Spirit Emperors were the highest form that a spirit could take in this world. They were beings at the very top of the pecking order and also very rarely seen. Not much information was out there about these beings which made it easier to fool others. The only consensus was that they were more powerful than anything that could be produced on this planet.

It was unheard of that a Spirit Emperor took shape amongst the mortal people. They usually only gave out some blessings like the weapons that the heroes possessed. At most they could be summoned to deliver one devastating attack, sometimes at the cost of the summoner’s own life.

“Please great spirit emperor, forgive me and my people for being so narrow-minded. Punish this mortal but please show mercy to my people.”

The woman was quick to drop down to her knees and to prostrate herself. Due to the soul interception, he could tell that she was sincere. She was mostly concerned that Zhang Dong could wipe her people out of existence.

‘Well that went better than expected, this will probably save me so much time!”

He chuckled inwardly, it was time to have a talk with this lady. After this event, he was sure that they would do anything that he required of him.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 310

*Thump*

The elves looked as their Queen slumped forward in her throne and then face-planted on the ground. The exchange in Zhang Dong’s soul dimension only took a couple of seconds. Back in the real world, it looked like the Queen was staring at him for a moment before face diving into the floor.

“Protect the Queen!”

“...”

“Stop, I’m fine…”

The beautiful woman raised her hand up into the air while her face was still on the ground. She stood up in an instant while having a bloody nose. This was quickly healed without even needing an incantation. The guards were still confused about what was happening and the party of heroes was in the same boat.

Only Zhang Dong and the elven Queen knew what was going on. After giving the old woman a scare in his soul dimension he let her soul go back into her body. He did not put any soul locks or curses behind like he did with the Vice-Principal.

He wanted to seem as a magnanimous spirit Emperor and not like a despot. The other elves might choose to attack or not work with them if something like that happened.

The Queen looked at him without much of a change to her expression. The bloody nose vanished along with the blood after some kind of healing magic was cast. It was more akin to the regenerative arts that his own Zhang clan liked to perform than to holy element healing.

She advanced forward towards where he, Beatrice, and Isabella were standing. The girls were down on their knees but he was still standing. The guards parted ways for their queen that was slowly walking towards him. The woman was wearing quite the flowy dress similar to cultivator robes. There were even some small forest spirits lifting it up from behind her and keeping it from being scratched up on the floor.

“My Queen what are you…”

The elves expected the Queen to order an attack or something close to it. Instead, they saw her lowering her head in front of this white-haired man. The man nodded as if this was something natural, the other just stared at the strange sight of the elven queen bowing before an unknown person.

“Silence! Pay your respect to the Spirit Emperor, you all are being disgraceful.”

Soon everyone was down on the ground and kneeling before him. His face didn’t change as he just waited.

‘Haven’t had a full throne room kneeling before me ever since I did that one lecture…’

“You may raise your heads.”

Only when he called out did the elven queen listen. Following her example, the other elves did the same. The members of the royal family went googly-eyed at the scene before them. In their eyes kneeling before Zhang Dong was akin to them kneeling before Beatrice, a low Baron’s daughter.

“I will let this transgression slide this time, now I think we have some things to discuss.”

“Yes, great spirit.”

The members of the royal family could not believe Zhang Dong’s tone. Even less that this powerful elven monarch was fine with it. The moment she called him a spirit emperor the other elves started to shake in their boots as well. This was mostly due to this race being quite close to astral beings due to their roots.

They came from the world tree, which was also rumored to have been created by some kind of ancient spirit emperor. Now they had one before them, one that could be at the same level as their ancestor.

‘Good, this speeds up things…’

The rest was history, Zhang Dong asked for their library and then absorbed all of their knowledge. The elven magic was mostly following the nature element and was quite extensive. The knowledge that they had gathered was superior to what the humans had, at least to the one in the magic academy. If the royal family was hiding something in their castle could be a possibility.

Takeshi and the others were relegated to background characters while Zhang Dong and his two summoners got all the attention. They all were wined and dined by the beautiful elven males and females while he was back doing his thing. After absorbing all of this knowledge from the elven library he needed some time to digest all of it.

With it, he would probably be able to push his own barriers to the next level. The elves specialized in them, defensive ones and even ones that could lock people up for thousands of years. If he ever needed to seal an evil being that was hard to kill he would be able to.

“Please Queen you must not!”

A few days later the hero party and Zhang Dong were back on the flying ship. With the biggest change being that they received a massive ship from the elves. It was apparently made from the trunk of the world tree and would be able to receive hits from a demon lord class monster.

The two magicians that stood against him were now holding back the elven queen. For some reason, the old woman wanted to come with them. Her people weren’t so keen on this as they needed their monarch that was also the best mage here to stay behind. The queen was the key piece of their protective barrier, without her the demons would be able to slip in unnoticed.

The two were now holding her back as she wanted to join the party to go against the demon scourge. After Zhang Dong corrected some of the deficiencies in her spell-casting she started acting like a devout disciple. She probably wanted him to fix more of her spells, just like an old cultivator finally finding a good master to follow.

“Hey, Mr. Leigong the elves really like you… I thought you were a married man?”

Beatrice and Isabella looked at him with scorn. He had been seen wandering out at night to go teach the elven queen a thing or two. The girls imagination went into overdrive and came to a conclusion that he was having an affair.

“It’s not like that, you two idiots!”

He shouted at the two girls while shaking his fist.

“Great spirit, let us follow you instead of our queen.”

In the end, the two elven women that were the queen’s trusted guards went along for the ride instead. The queen’s reason won out over her desire to learn more. With these two in tow and a full elven team of warriors, they departed from this kingdom.

‘Next stop the dwarves!’

Now that he had the elves on his side it was easier to control the situation. The elven ship was many times larger than the human ships that were now trailing behind them. He was also able to banish the royal family members from getting on this particular flying vessel. Though this only made the heroes a bit cranky as they enjoyed the companionship of the others.

Takeshi even decided to remain on one of the other ships with his princess. Zhang Dong didn’t care enough to play chaperone. He had explained everything to the youths beforehand but their hormones were getting in the way. The only thing he could do was hope that they wouldn’t go too far with their romance.

The journey continued and they soon arrived at the dwarven kingdom or its entrance that looked like a giant active volcano. Smoke and lava were coming out from it but there were also large statues of dwarven warriors and a large gate.

This large gate would lead to the land of the dwarves. They were a peculiar race that liked to live underground or burrow into large mountains or in this case a volcano. There they would dig for metals that would then allow them to create their contraptions.

They were known for being a race of craftsmen that spent most of their lives tinkering away. The flying ship technology was invented by this race, they also created a vast array of golems. The hero party here was in the need of better equipment and repairs. The weapons from the dungeon were nice but they still lacked compelling armor.

“So, this is the entrance into the Underlands.”

Beatrice commented from the side while bouncing with anticipation. Isabella also looked quite interested in this place they were going to. The two were still only young girls that haven’t really been able to see the outside world for themselves quite yet.

“So it is, think the dwarves will be as cooperative as the elves? Do they revere spirits perchance?”

He asked while not being too sure. If the dwarves were like the elves it would help Zhang Dong on his journey quite a bit.

“Those uncultured dwarves have no respect for that what is holy.”

One of the elven mages chimed in while narrowing her eyes at the large structure below. It seemed that the small drunkards and the tree huggers didn’t get along that much. One race loved nature while the other used it to their advantage no matter the cost. They lived underground where the sun didn’t shine, without it things like plants were rarely seen.

“Is that so… this might be a problem.”

Besides their outlooks on life, there was another problem with this race, they had no monarch that could rally them together. Zhang Dong was only able to speed things up as he had forced the respected monarchs from the human race and the elven race to act. On the other hand here there were many underground cities and many people trying to be the next Dwarf King.

“Let’s go to the old capital, probably the most influential people will be there.”

The biggest city down below was right here in this very volcano. This was also the plan that they agreed on. Even if they didn’t have the help of the majority of dwarves they could get some from this city. It was apparently very modern and if they could just get another ship and some golems it would help in the future battles.

Zhang Dong was hopeful that the others wouldn’t need to act and that he was enough to defeat the enemies. However, in case that there were too many enemies to handle he needed his people to at least be able to defend themselves while he took out the bosses.

“Let us descend, we will need to switch to the smaller boat to get through that gate.”

Everyone nodded and the giant Elven ship descended downwards. The most important members of the crew would be switching to a smaller boat while going underground. Even though they were going below earth the dwarf craftsmen made enough space for flying contraptions like this boat to maneuver there.

Soon everyone descended into the cavern below. After showing the guards some credentials their identity as emissaries and heroes was cemented. The large gates started to open, it was as if the two huge statues were opening them up for the party to see.

‘Hope this is the last stop… I might be running out of time…’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 311

“Ugh, what’s that smell?”

“Think that’s motor oil?”

“Motor oil?”

Beatrice asked not knowing what Zhang Dong was talking about. The hero party had ventured into the underground city of the dwarves called Kalburim. This was supposed to be the capital of innovation.

It looked quite steampunk-inspired. Which made things uncomfortable as placing a city filled with steam and smoke underground wasn’t the best option. There were large vents that funneled all this smoke outside into the volcano above. Apparently, the volcano wasn’t even active but it was this city that was generating all of the heat and smoke to run it.

Zhang Dong looked at all the strange contraptions that this place had to offer. There was even a tram system going through this huge city, even something that looked like uni rails on the ceiling.

The thing that stuck out the most were the rock and metal golems that were wandering through the city. They were mostly carrying heavy objects with a dwarf walking in front. When Zhang Dong focused he could feel that these golems were using some kind of internal mana engine to run. The dwarves that were in front of them always had some sort of control item with them that was sending signals into this engine.

‘Interesting…’

These golems were similar to puppets that cultivators created. He had even fashioned some life-like variants when he was on a crafting spree. The way these golems were constructed was different but also similar in some places. They didn’t seem to be as intelligent as the puppets he used to make and also quite bulky.

‘I’d need to get my hands on the schematics, they look less advanced but that mana engine looks useful, with a few tweaks it could expand the life of a puppet.’

“It's something from the spirit realm"

He replied to the motor oil question.

"So, when are we going to meet the council?”

“They should have the meeting ready for today.”

The one replying this time was Isabella. She had ordered some of the people from the Duke house to go ask around. From The information that they had the dwarves were in the middle of some internal struggles.

Their king had died of old age and it was time to replace him. In contrast to the monarchs of the humans and elves, the title of dwarven king wasn’t hereditary. Anyone with enough resources and power could try to get this position if they met some prerequisites.

First of all, they needed to belong to the noble cast. Just as the humans the dwarf kingdom was split into noble houses and common workers.

It was kind of silly how these dwarves decided on their new monarch. As it wasn’t the individual strength that was important but what they could create. They would actually use the golems to fight in a tournament, the winner would be crowned the dwarven king.

Zhang Dong wasn’t really interested in this tournament as he just wanted to get the help of the dwarves in attacking the demons. There was a council of the main houses that was still able to make a decision.

He was hoping that they would lend him some ships, golems, and cannons that this race was famous for. The fight for the throne wasn’t something that he was interested in, there was no reason for him or anyone from the hero party to get involved.

“Great, let us get this over with then.”

Regretfully the party of young heroes wasn’t as interested in waiting as he was. This was a once in a lifetime fantasy world for these youngsters but for him, it wasn’t anything out of the ordinary. The cities back in his own world were larger and more beautiful than what any of these could offer.

Thus the party split up where the members from the royal family followed after the four heroes like little ticks. They were continually praising them just as they were ordered to. Anyone from the outside that took a second to think would know this but these youngsters were blinded by the beauty of the royal line.

“Are you sure we should leave them alone…”

Beatrice said while being concerned. She was glancing at the two sisters that were being led away by the green-haired prince and his older brother.

“We could try but I’m not sure if that would amount to anything…”

Zhang Dong could try to pry the pink-haired princess or her brothers away from Takeshi and his three friends but he feared that they would hate him for it. He could see that they were already succumbing to their lust by this point. It was as if the higher levels were magnifying their desires and making them more irrational. He was afraid that if he stepped in a fight would break out between them and they would need to put the whole expedition on hold.

“I’m not sure we should leave those heroes alone for too long...”

Isabella chimed in from the side while glaring at old moss head. She was the one hit the most by her old fiancé’s infidelity. She was the one that knew him the most here, the young man had a silver tongue and knew how to speak to girls his age. She was afraid that he would charm the heroines in time, making them his puppets that he could control.

“Well, if it gets out of hand I will act, till then let us give them some space. Sometimes the best way to mature is to make your own mistakes.”

Zhang Dong knew how young people operated as he had a childish personality. He knew that if a young person didn’t go through a given experience they would have a hard time learning. Adults could warn them as many times as they wanted but not many youths would adhere to that advice. They needed to burn their hands on the stove first before they would believe that it's hot to the touch.

“If Mr. Leigong thinks so…”

Isabella nodded and all of them moved further into the city. They need to get the accommodations sorted out as they were diplomatic guests from the other races. They had a certain immunity in this city as no one would want to anger emissaries from two other powerful races. The danger of war was always looming.

They had a group of well-dressed dwarves take them to a large hotel-like building. They even rode the uni rail through the city that let them behold its glory. It was about the size of the human capital which was also not even close in scope to Zhang Dong’s Spirit Spring City.

The group ended up in a somewhat lush-looking hotel suite with room for the most important members. The people that weren’t part of the hero party would need to wait in their ship outside. Zhang Dong’s group consisted of Beatrice, Isabella, the two elven ladies that the Queen lent them, and a few bodyguards from the Hohenberg household.

The people with Takeshi and the others were a few levels above them in this hotel right at the top. With them were various soldiers from the royal guard as the members from the royal family needed to be protected.

Just like before this part of the party wasn’t taken all that serious. The focus was on the four heroes and the royal family members that were accompanying them.

“I guess you two can practice your breathing…”

The two girls nodded as they were waiting for word to reach them. The council needed to give them an hour that the meeting would be taking place. At least that is what was supposed to happen but after waiting for many hours no word reached their ears.

“Did something go wrong?”

Zhang Dong called out to Isabella who had one of her bodyguards ask for the meeting. The person in question was also in this room. He shook his head and also apologized but he repeated what he knew. The noble dwarfs told them to wait while they organize the meeting and when they did they would come looking for them.

“Did they lie to us? If so for what reason?”

Zhang Dong asked Beatrice along with the other people in the room.

“As expected from dwarves…”

One of the elven women commented from the side while frowning. The other elven mage also nodded, it was clear that these two races didn’t see eye to eye. From what Zhang Dong could tell this was due to elves being in tune with nature while dwarves liked using it without caring for it. Pollution and destruction of forests was the least they were ready to do to create their massive golems and machines.

“Is the Hero party still here?”

He asked as he had left towards his own soul dimension and began cultivating his soul again. The idea of the dwarf nobles pulling a fast one on them didn’t cross his mind. He decided to come out next to Beatrice to perform a small scan.

‘Hm?... most of them are there… but Takeshi is missing along with some of the guards…’

The three girls were there, he could feel their unique mana signature. The most important member from the hero party wasn’t there though.

‘This feels fishy…’

“Hey Beatrice, Isabella lent me some power.”

The two girls looked at each other and nodded. They weren’t sure what Zhang Dong wanted but they trusted him enough to know better by this point. They held their hands together and started channeling their mana. In just a moment the two were covered by a thin layer of golden light.

Since having time to train this soul skill they had grown accustomed to it. It didn’t need to produce a large light show anymore and they could use it sparingly.

Zhang Dong’s eyes glowed in golden light as he sat down in the lotus position. With thee increased energy he would be able to cover most of the city with his spiritual sense. He did so in hopes of finding where Takeshi had gone.

With his enhanced senses he could really take a good look at this city. It was really mostly built out of rock and steel. Steam and smoke everywhere while the dwarfs were either busy with work or getting drunk at one of the pubs.

He went a bit further in, finding where Takeshi was wasn’t all that hard as he had a unique mana signature. He found him in a large far away building and he was standing in some open hall with a couple of the royal family members.

Zhang Dong could feel that there were some old dwarves there in a circle looking down at the group of humans.

“Why would they…”

“Is something wrong Mr. Leigong?”

“It would seem that our companions have begun that meeting without us…”

“Oh no!”

Beatrice replied at this revelation.

“I bet they wish to strike a deal without us being involved!”

Isabella added from the side. It seemed that the people from the royalist faction didn’t like that he was gaining so much status. He had the large elven ship and the Duke was also on his side.

“That might be the case… we should go pay them a visit before it's too late.”

The group soon departed, if they would make it in time before an unfortunate deal could be struck remained to be seen.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 312

Zhang Dong along with his two golden-haired summoners rushed to where this secret meeting was taking place. Apparently, his side was not informed for some reason or another.

He was more inclined to believe that the people from the royal family pulled some strings instead of the dwarf side. This race of people didn’t really interact with him in anyway shape or form before this so there shouldn’t be any animosity between them.

‘They probably want to keep us from gathering any more power.’

For him, it was a race for time. He wanted to defeat the demon lords, get the cube parts and then go home. For the humans living here, it was different, they probably saw him as someone that could affect the status quo.

From the perspective of the royal family, he could be someone more dangerous than the demon king. He already showed that he could handle the human monarch and the elven queen.

What would stop him from taking over the world after they were done with clearing up the demonic beings? What was to stop him from doing it even before he faced the demon king? This was probably what the human King and his children were worried about now. They were on the very top of this world and would without a doubt like to remain in this position.

“Halt! The council meeting is in session, no one is allowed to enter!”

A group of heavily armored dwarves cut off their path. They had quite the peculiar-looking exosuits. It looked like they were inside of metallic golems but with tiny heads. This head part belonged to the soldier that was in this mechanical suit of armor.

“Make way for the Spirit Emperor!”

The two elven mages saw the group of mechanical golems blocking their path. They had large two-handed halberds in their hands and were blocking the way. The two women found it rude for these people to be addressing Leigong in such a way. The two were instructed to protect and follow the instructions of this Spirit Emperor by their queen. They intended to do that, even if they would need to fight.

“No wait, let us talk this over…”

Zhang Dong put himself between the battalion of dwarven defenders. They looked like they were riding some primitive mechs which took him a little bit to process. He couldn’t let a fight break out, the royal members would just use this as a pretext to have him removed from this city.

“If the Spirit Emperor commands, it shall be done.”

The two women bowed their heads at his request and moved to the sides. The group of dwarves didn’t move out of the way which meant that Isabella would need to take care of this. She had one of her men move forward and present their case.

“You are with the heroes?”

The commander of these guards stepped forward and they began figuring things out. They had all the paperwork that identified them as part of the hero party.

“The council meeting is close to being over, was there some kind of mistake? I fear we aren’t allowed to open the doors before the meeting is over...”

The man gave the papers back to the group but there was a problem. The meeting had already started. Inside were the most influential people from this city and they were all rich and powerful nobles. They couldn’t just barge in at this point, these guards would not let them. Zhang Dong didn’t blame them as they were only doing their job.

“How could they do this to us?”

“This is unforgivable!”

Beatrice and Isabella stomped their feet on the ground while outside the large building. They were mad about the royal members not telling them about the meeting more than about the dwarves not allowing them to venture forward.

‘It’s fine… I’ll just go take a peek instead…’

He smiled and moved a bit to the side with the girls while sending them a telepathic message.

There was not much that they could do to get inside without making a big scene. It would not be hard to blast their way inside but then they would probably be banned from the city. He feared that if that happened it could take god knows how long to get everything sorted out inside.

“Okay, this will be enough girls.”

The plan was easy, he just needed some more juice from his two girl sized magical batteries. The range he could operate in had increased ever since the two had gotten stronger. He had also learned many spells and incantations that would aid him in this task.

Zhang Dong’s body flickered and soon he was invisible to the naked eye.

“Just wait here and I’ll see what those chuckleheads are up to.”

Beatrice and Isabella just waved at the floating voice while holding hands. They and their guards were sitting in a nearby cafe while Zhang Dong floated as a mana cloud towards the building where the meeting was taking place.

He might have looked like a regular person to the people here but his body was made from mana particles. These particles could take any shape that he wanted, even make themselves invisible.

While utilizing some of his knowledge he made himself undetectable to any living being or machine. Even with their advanced dwarven technology, he was able to get past the guards. In this shapeless form, he squeezed through the doorway and arrived inside the large building.

Inside there were even more guards, these weren’t in huge mechanical suits but in more traditional-looking armor. They were patrolling the halls but were unable to see or feel Zhang Dong’s presence.

‘It’s in there…’

He flew towards Takeshi’s unique mana signature and arrived at the wide-open area. This place was the large room he saw where the dwarven nobles were looking down below at the humans. The sword hero was there along with a couple of members of the royal family.

“Eight hundred thousand coins? I will offer one million and ten of my best bottles of wine!”

‘Hm?’

A loud sound of a hand landing on something rocky was heard by him the moment he slipped into this room. It seemed that the dwarves were shouting at each other and also bidding on something.

He glanced at who they were looking at and it was Takeshi. He and the others were just there smiling while looking between the dwarven nobles.

“A million? You are really going all in, you’re not afraid that your house will go under if this so-called hero doesn’t win?”

Zhang Dong looked at the person that was talking. It was some old fart with a long white beard, he was looking at a slightly younger old fart.

“You think I’m stupid? You just want the hero as your champion yourself!”

‘Champion? Oh no, are they really going to do this now?’

If he was in his human shape his face would be showing a frown now. Previously he did find out that the dwarves had a peculiar way of picking out their king. This would only come into place if they couldn’t come to some kind of agreement.

They were clearly unable to go through with that. Instead, they would go with option two, getting the king's position by trial by combat.

This didn’t mean that the person that was hoping for the king’s position would be battling himself. No, the dwarves didn’t pick their kings by strength alone, they picked them by their resourcefulness.

The candidates had to use everything to their disposal to get the best possible champion for themselves. These champions would fight in a tournament and the one remaining would be crowned king.

‘Why does it always have to be a tournament…’

Takeshi was taking center spot, apparently, these people wanted him to be their champion. He was the sword hero and also the strongest from the party if you didn’t look Zhang Dong’s way.

‘But… can he use one of those things?’

Zhang Dong was referring to the large mechanical suits that the dwarves used. The champions wouldn’t actually be using their bodies to battle, they would be using huge robot-like suits of armor that the dwarven craftsmen prepared for them.

These were quite similar to Mechs that he saw in some anime shows back in the day. Just like in the shows the pilots were quite important and could shift the tide of battle. The dwarven mech suits also used their users' mana to fuel themselves along with the mana engine.

He was only here in spirit form so he didn’t intend to disturb this hero auction. The whole thing continued until one of the old nobles was able to seal the deal. Having Takeshi as their champion didn’t mean that they had the win in the bag but from the point of view of these dwarves it was very probable. The legends concerning the heroes were widespread so the trust they had in them was immense.

‘How can I salvage this situation…’

While thinking he continued to glance around the room. He could see the dejected faces that all the other nobles were showing. They truly believed that the person that managed to get this hero as their champion would be the winner.

“This meeting is over, the Tournament of Kingship will be taking place in a week’s time, everyone please prepare!”

He floated around while not knowing what to do. Soon the place was being cleared up and he started going back to the girls. Now was the time to make a decision, if Takeshi won the tournament it could become problematic. He was entangled with the pink-haired princess and could grow a big head. It would be possible for the royal faction to start stalling and time was not something that he wanted to waste.

‘What should I… wait what’s that?’

While returning he noticed something, this large building was quite old but he felt a peculiar aura close by. He was attracted to it and decided to change directions. After slipping through some guards he arrived at a large area filled with books and scrolls.

‘Basics of golem creation?’

‘How to produce the best alloy for your golem.’

This was apparently a library filled with dwarven knowledge, knowledge that could be used to craft golems or Exo suits. If he wasn’t a transparent cloud of mana he would be grinning now. A plan was formed in his mind with which he would soon go through.

‘I bet not all of those nobles were able to get good champions… I think some poor sob will be very lucky…he he he’

The mist descended onto the library as he started to absorb all the knowledge that was in here. After combining it with his understanding of making automatons from his previous world he would fashion something that no one could beat.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 313

Thondin looked at the large mechanical contraption that was before him and scratched his head. He started recalling how he ended up in this situation in the first place.

He was the oldest son from the Hillmane household. His father was already too old to compete for the position of a king and he didn’t really want it either. Their noble house was considered to be on the lower end of the high noble families and no one was really considering them to win or even to participate.

Out of necessity, he was there during the meeting and his house would be bringing over a champion just so they wouldn’t lose face. Even though he didn’t want the position of the king his father that was on his deathbed pushed him towards it. His plan was to not stand out and just lose during the combat portion.

At least this was what he intended to do but fate had something different in store for him. After the meeting was over and the hero left with the winners he had stayed to discuss some business with the other noble dwarfs. It was a good opportunity to foster good relations as all the influential families were here.

Then the strange feeling washed over him, he felt like someone was watching him. Even on the trip back home, it felt like there was something in the air. He asked his bodyguards to check but no one could find anything so they just continued.

Back at home, he went over to his old father’s bed chambers to disclose some information about his new business ventures. The old man was more interested in the heroes and the tournament where the king candidates would be gathering.

After a slow conversation and him lying about him taking this tournament seriously, he left the room. Thondin only used the bare minimum on the golem that his side would be using as he didn’t want to get his family into financial problems. From his perspective, the power-hungry idiots could just fight for the position of the king.

In his eyes the family business was more important, he never thought that they had a chance of winning in the first place which made this the correct way to progress. With that, his family would be out in front while the others would put themselves in debt and overspend on their golems.

His well-thought-out plan didn’t come to fruition as after leaving his father’s bed chambers they heard a rumble. The guards were alerted to this and everyone rushed inside only to see his sickly father standing upright and filled with energy.

At first, they thought it was some kind of miracle, with a trembling voice he called out to him.

“Father… how can this be…what is that?”

While in a confused state he finally noticed that his father wasn’t alone in this room. There was a small creature of about twelve inches floating around and giving off a golden light.

He wanted to order his men to capture it but was stopped by his father. With him back in the picture Thondin was put in the backseat once more. His father was still the one in the position of power as he had never given it up. Only when the family head died would the position be passed down.

“Halt, this is my saviour!”

The old man replied when asked about this being's origins.

“Saviour?”

Thondin asked while fearing that this small being could be a demon in disguise. There were rumors of such beings offering contracts with the people of the races. They would grant magical power, riches and even heal people at some cost. Mostly the person would give up their soul or give information to the demons involved.

“I know what you are thinking my son, but this is not a demon, it’s a friendly spirit that is a part of the Hero party!”

“Greetings mortal, you may refer to me as Lightning Emperor, Leigong.”

Right after his father finished speaking the small humanoid gave his name. This was a well-known name in this world by now and was associated with the twin summoners that had defeated many demonic beings. Thondin also knew that they were in this city at this moment along with the party of the heroes.

“Leigong?”

“Show some respect boy, he cured your old man!”

Thondin was hit on the back of the head by his own father that had surprisingly a lot of strength left behind. It was as if he had never been sick, to begin with.

“Now give me some food!”

Things went by fast as his father took over. The two golden-haired girls that were the supposed twin priestesses arrived soon after. They were all allowed into the dining room with his father and himself.

“Thondin, The Lightning Emperor will help us achieve victory in this coming tournament, you will be the Dwarven King!”

Thondin after hearing this, promptly spit out the red wine that he was drinking.

“Me? The king?”

“Yes, I’d do it myself but these old bones don’t have much life left in them. I can at least see this through while I have the chance!”

The old man’s eyes shone brightly as he talked about putting his son on the throne. This would be a great honor for his own house. His name would be remembered as the father of a dwarven king, immortalized in the history books.

“H-how would the honorable Emperor help us? The tournament will be starting in less than a week.”

“Don’t worry young one, just show me your machine and I’ll bring you victory!”

The small appearance of this Leigong had shifted into a tall white-haired man after the party of people arrived. He looked a lot more imposing than he did before and was radiating magical power.

“Thondin, show him your golem. The costs don’t matter, give them all the resources that our house can offer to make it the strongest golem the world has ever seen!”

He wanted to cry as he specifically used the least amount of coin to have the golem built. Now his father wanted to bankrupt him by spending all of their money on this venture with no future.

“Well, what are you waiting… go! There is no time to lose!”

After being forced to go into the building where the combat golem was stored he was met with stares of disdain. The stare was coming from this Emperor of Lightning. He had gone through the golem that he prepared and had apparently looked through the outer shell.

“What is this? Who put this nonsense over this last-gen crap? This won’t do at all!”

Leigong shouted out while rubbing his chin. Thondin knew what he meant as he had gotten a cheap old model of a golem and made it look next-gen. The outer shell made it look modern and strong but the power that it could output would be far behind the competition that spent a fortune on their models.

“We need to remake the internals… replace these joints… update the mana engine… this could take a while…”

He could hear the spirit mumbling while looking over the large battle golem. After moving around it for a few minutes he arrived at where Thondin was standing.

“I have looked over the schematics here, I’ll need these, please bring them over within two days.”

When he looked at the list of parts that this Leigong spirit wanted his eyes almost popped out of his eye sockets.

“Orichalcum and adamantium?... Spirit silver… how many liters of mana fluid?”

The items and materials that were listed here were all from the top shelf. If he bought this all he would have to expend most of his estate's reserves. This was not something that he could allow to happen.

Due to this he hatched a scheme of stalling, if he told them that he couldn’t get the materials they would not be able to go through with the golem renovation. This plan didn’t go into fruition either as the white-haired spirit did something peculiar.

Leigong started to shine in white before splitting into many round balls of light. These balls of light then turned into miniature versions of himself similar to his previous chibi form. They looked more humanoid in shape and had better proportions than the old versions.

There were about a hundred of them, they all started moving towards the large golem and taking it apart while also working very fast. It dawned on him that this was how this spirit was hoping to hasten the changes on the machine. He could split into many smaller versions of himself that could customize this battle golem in just a few days.

“Okay, let us go get those materials then.”

One of the smaller versions appeared next to him while floating. He started sweating while rolling up the scroll with the list of items. It seemed that he would not be able to stall him as one of the small Leigongs would be going with him. A few members from this side of the hero party also stuck close. They all made sure that he got all the expensive stuff that Leigong wanted.

After two days he was looking at an empty treasure room that only had a couple of golden coins left. It all went into the blasted battle golem that he wasn’t even being allowed to see. His plans had already been ruined by this point and if they lost during the tournament the only thing left would be to sell those golem parts for some profit. He had no trust in this spirit but was forced due to his father recovering from his sickness.

Time continued to go by and no one was allowed to enter the building where the combat golem was being reconstructed. All that the people could hear were thunderous sounds as Leigong was utilizing his lightning to construct this golem. Only at the crack of dawn before the tournament started was the machine finally completed.

“This should do it…”

Zhang Dong looked at the ‘golem’ that he reconstructed. It was a lot less bulky than what the dwarves liked to build due to him implementing some puppet technology that he was familiar with.

“Now let us perform a little test girls, fire it up!”

The thumping sounds of something were heard by the people from this noble house. Thondin and his father awaited outside the closed building while the golem moved towards them. They were shocked by the sleek appearance of this combat golem, it was not a design they were very familiar with.

Zhang Dong being himself had taken inspiration from the many mech-focused anime he had seen. The golem was mostly white with its feet having a red tint to them. The chest part was blue at the top with red at the abdomen area. This machine had clearly a humanoid shape, the head part looked like a samurai helmet with wide yellow fins coming out of the forehead.

In one hand the golem had a large shield while in the other he was holding a tube of some sort. When activated this tube would turn into a sword of light akin to Zhang Dong’s thunderlight sword skill.

“It’s time to have an old-fashioned robot battle…”

Zhang Dong’s voice could be heard from the robot's head as it moved forward. First, they need to perform some tests and then the time for battle would be upon them.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 314

Zhang Dong performed a grasping motion with his hand. Instead of seeing his own hand form a fist a large one made from metal did it for him.

‘Good, the response time is far greater than what the dwarven golems can output…’

The large golem that he created was now moving around while he was piloting it. There was no cockpit for him though, he was actually spreading his mana molecules through the whole large robot. It was as if this golem was his own body that he could more freely around.

“How are you two feeling? Is everything okay?”

“Yes Mr. Leigong, we are fine.”

“Yes, this is actually quite comfortable!”

Beatrice and Isabella’s voices could be heard from inside the large robot’s chest area. In it, the two girls were sitting together on two comfy seats. They were holding hands while channeling their magic into Zhang Dong. He used this mana to power this golem and to also pilot it at the same time.

Having both of the girls inside this mecha that he created was also allowed. A golem could have up to five pilots at the same time. Some of them were quite hard to control with just one person inside of them.

From the outside it would seem that having only two people on the inside would be a bad decision. In reality Zhang Dong could move this robot like an extension of his own body. The size was comparable to his avatar form so he was also used to the higher point of view.

“Will this be enough?”

Beatrice asked while looking at a monitor that showed her and Isabella the outside. There they could see Zhang Dong swinging a saber of light around. The lack of time didn’t let them produce many parts so they had to go with this generic sword and shield combination.

“Has this mighty Leigong ever let you down!”

Beatrice chuckled while Zhang Dong replied in a haughty voice. The young girl had gotten used to the way that he talked already and knew that he was mostly only being half-serious.

“I’m sure that we will win, we can’t let them win this!”

Isabella wasn’t laughing though, her face was showing a frown and her eyes were burning with passion to fight. She really didn’t want her old fiancé to get the win here. Zhang Dong was glad that he never did make any women mad at him in this way. Sticking to only one was the correct decision. He could not understand his grandfather or Huo Qiang and how they could just have so many wives.

After some tests, it was finally time to leave. Zhang Dong while in the robot walked over to the transportation vehicle that would transport this golem to the arena. While in it they would conserve their mana.

Zhang Dong had nothing to do other than meditating. Before that, he thought back to how everything came together to this moment.

After he went through all of the dwarven books that he came across after the council meeting he noticed Thondin. He had already started contemplating on a plan of action that would force him to win the competition instead of Takeshi.

He was worried that more bureaucracy would be involved and the expedition could be stalled if the royal members had their way. He needed to enter the competition but he wasn’t sure how to go about it. But at that time Thondin entered the picture.

From some conversations that he had with the other noble dwarves, he figured out a couple of things. One that he was from a house that would be participating and also that he had a father on a deathbed. This sparked the plan of action that made him create this mecha-like golem. The design was lifted from a popular show that he used to watch and was more or less a carbon copy of it.

Zhang Dong put his faith in the dying dwarf. He figured that if he managed to heal him that this person would allow them to participate in the tournament. After following Thondin and performing this task they found themselves here.

The plan was a bit lackluster but there was not much else that he could do besides competing for one of the noble houses. He was also sure to make the old man that was now back to being the head of the estate, to sign a contract. After they won, he would have his son that would be the new king give them support in their venture.

‘That kid didn’t look too happy about that part… but sometimes those ones that don’t want to be kings make the best ones…’

Zhang Dong looked at Thondin a bit and how he acted. He seemed to prioritize his own family over status and greed. This would be a good quality that a king should have. Being too stuck up while making decisions based on things like noble status and pride could spell disaster.

The golem was covered in a large thick cloth and strapped to a large trailer that was being pulled by a smaller golem. The dwarves didn't seem to have made cars yet as they were using various-sized golems for everything instead. This one looked more like a large horse made from metal and was clearly made for pulling heavy objects.

After a bumpy ride, they finally arrived at their destination. They were allowed to go in from a side entrance while the people gathered. Zhang Dong couldn’t really see the arena from outside but he could clearly hear the dwarves cheering outside. Soon the cloth was removed and through his mech’s eyes, he could finally see again.

They were in a large underground area and he could hear the sound of tinkering. Other golems were gathered here with them of various shapes and sizes. The one he was inhabiting was ten meters in height. It wasn’t as large as its anime counterpart but this was the limit of this world's technology.

If he wanted to make it larger he would need to change its shape. Zhang Dong preferred to make it more mobile and all-around strong than to go to either extreme. This coupled with his current cultivation would give the machine quite a boost in power.

This underground hangar was huge and he could feel that there was a large number of people right above them. The golems that were gathered here were divided by large walls of metal that didn’t allow others to peek at what the craftsmen were doing. These walls even had strange runes on them that were blocking out magical scanners.

Luckily they weren’t able to block out Zhang Dong that was above such little tricks. He could clearly see all the golems and their pilots.

‘Those are some exotic designs…’

He noticed that the machines varied in size, weight, and even in pilot count. It was clear that some of the participants went all in, while others that were similar to Thondin showed up with cheap knockoffs. He could tell that some of these golems were meant to take a few hits before crumbling before their enemies.

‘Can’t blame them, no use to put yourself in debt if you are convinced that you can’t win.’

Zhang Dong continued to scan the large hangar to see how many real threats there were. He spotted Takeshi’s golem and could tell that it was quite advanced. It was larger than his own model and a lot bulkier.

‘I see that this guy went all in… though not sure if putting Takeshi in that machine will be a good idea…’

He felt that due to the fast training that he put the heroes through they wouldn’t be fit to enter this competition. Takeshi might have been strong from a stat point perspective but he lacked combat experience. Even if they gave him the best golem around he could easily fall into a trap.

‘They even roped in the girls I see…’

“Mr. Leigong, they announced our number, we are going to be in the first match!”

Zhang Dong was busy scanning the area so he wasn’t paying attention. Beatrice’s voice snapped him out of it as it seemed that they would be showing off their mech right from the start.

“Is that so? Well, you two just relax and leave everything to me.”

“Sure thing!”

The two girls didn’t really have to do anything besides acting as human batteries. They had a large screen that showed them what Zhang Dong was seeing through his eyes. The compartment they were in was well protected and could be ejected outside if anything bad happened.

At first, he thought about placing both of the girls outside this robot just like when he battled the demon lords. But this proved problematic with how this golem devoured mana energy. It was quite inefficient and the two girls had to be placed inside of it to counter the drain.

He was still there so if anything happened he was ready to eject the girls into safety. Winning this tournament wasn’t worth the lives of Beatrice and Isabella. He would figure out a new plan if they lost but after looking through the golems the only one that could provide a challenge was the one being used by Takeshi.

‘I guess it’s going to be us against them. I hope they can take a loss as I’m not intending to lose’

“Okay, you are up.”

One of the mechanics that had helped them reconstruct the old golem called out. Zhang Dong moved his large mechanical foot forward and began walking. After leaving their ‘garage’ they were led over to a wide corridor. There was enough space in here to stack three golems on top of each other and five in width.

He continued walking through the dimly lit corridor while the murmurs got louder. At the end, there was a large metallic door with strange dwarven inscriptions. Before he could look at them carefully the door started to slide into the ground while revealing the light outside. The moment it opened he was greeted by many cheers from the audience members.

“Let us welcome the candidate from the Hillmane household!”

The moment he stepped out the dwarves stopped cheering. The shape of his golem was quite unique if he compared it to the bulkier models the other dwarves used.

His opponent seemed to be one of those golems. They were about the same size but the golem standing on the opposite side was wider. He was mostly brown-gray in coloring, one hand was a claw while the other one had a large spiked ball with a chain attached to it.

If you compared the two at first glance, Zhang Dong’s mech looked to be the weaker one. It didn’t look like something that could take too many hits or even deal enough damage to get past its enemy's defenses.

‘Well, time to show them my seed mode!’

Zhang Dong cackled on the inside while getting out his laser sword, it was time to show these people how a mech battle looked like.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 315

“That Hillmane household golem looks strange…”

“Yes, it doesn’t seem like they are taking this seriously…”

Two nobles that were sitting in the VIP booth conversed with each other while staring at the two large golems in the even larger arena.

Zhang Dong’s mecha-inspired golem was not in line with the esthetic perception of the dwarves here. Its design was sleeker and less bulky while also having more radiant colors of blue, red, and white. It made some of the old nobles uncomfortable to look at, some of them were even thinking that the Hillmane household was making a mockery of this serious day.

“I hope the Blackhelm house makes quick work of those fools, truly a disgrace to the noble dwarves!”

From everyone's perspective, the side Zhang Dong was fighting for looked to be not taking things as seriously as the rest. He could clearly hear some of the antagonistic shouts of the masses that were coming his way.

‘I guess I should have gone with a different design…’

The outer shell didn’t matter to him that much as what was on the inside of this machine was the important part. If he knew that the dwarves reacted like this, he would have made a more grayish golem.

“Let us begin the first match, Hillmane vs Blackhelm!”

A large gong resounded throughout the arena and indicated the start of the battle. The golem on the opposite side started swinging that chained spiked ball with its hand and began charging towards Zhang Dong’s direction. Each step it made caused the earth to rumble and the people to cheer out loud.

Then the opponent's side that hailed from the Hillmane house did something strange. Instead of using the giant shield to defend themselves, the golem threw it to the side. The light sword remained strapped to the golem's hip while it took on a strange position.

The golems palms were moving forward while its legs spread out into a wide stance. The people didn’t know what was happening as the golem looked a bit too light to be a close-range brawler.

“What are they doing… is the operator an idiot?”

The noble dwarves asked while scratching their heads. The operator was how they called the main golem pilot and in this case, it would be Zhang Dong. They didn’t need to wait long for a resolution though as the two machines collided with each other.

While charging forward and gaining momentum the golem from the Blackhelm house swung its weapon. The chained ball flew at its target with force and it looked like it was over for house Hillmane.

Then it happened, the white golem’s palm started glowing in a blew light and with amazing speed, it collided with the hardened spiked ball. Instead of the hand exploding into tiny chunks of metal the heavy ball was slapped to the side while also losing some of its spikes in the process.

This wasn’t all as the white golem moved forward and stepped into melee range. The way it stomped its foot created spider web-like cracks in the arena floor. While using the momentum of the step-in, Zhang Dong’s machine delivered a clean palm strike to the other golem’s torso. This was also backed by an energy-filled palm which caused a large amount of damage to the opponent’s machine.

House Blackhelm’s golem was sent flying while chunks of its armor peeled off. A massive palm print was embedded in the chest while the robot fell backward. The technique that Zhang Dong performed was a basic one but thanks to how this golem was made he was able to utilize the combat techniques from his own world. This golem was like an extension of his body with which he could perform most of his own battle techniques.

“Impossible!”

The nobles called out, their eyes bulging at the sight of the larger golem being damaged by just one hit. It didn’t look like the golem from the Hillmane household would be able to produce this much force but somehow it did.

“You see that you old coots, Hillmane will be victorious!”

A loud voice was heard by the nobles which caused them to look back. The man that was cheering and happy was the old head of the household that Zhang Dong had healed. He was ecstatic while looking at his side winning over a house that he didn’t like that much.

The other nobles looked in surprise at how energetic this old man was. They all heard rumors of him being on his deathbed but now he was here. The old dwarf was even throwing punches as he looked at his golem approaching the downed opponent.

“That’s it, finish him off!”

Zhang Dong could hear his ‘sponsor’ getting into it which made him chuckle inwardly. The golem that he was fighting against didn’t give up quite yet as it started to slowly stand up. It used a last-ditch attack by launching its clawed hand towards him.

The giant claw connected with his forearm while he pulled it up. The claw was still attached to the rest of the golem’s body. The opponents were now trying to pull him in for a close-range grappling battle while probably thinking that they had the strength advantage.

‘I will have to disappoint you but this golem I created is a lot stronger than you might think.’

Everyone outside expected to see Zhang Dong be pulled in and squashed by the larger golem but instead the one being pulled in was the Blackhelm house machine.

Even when it used its larger frame and legs it slid towards Zhang Dong’s golem. He was just using his hands to pull it in as if he was in a tug of war contest. The golem he was using was glowing in a dark orange light. He was utilizing another technique that increased his strength and allowed his smaller golem to win out over the bulkier model.

With one last pull, the damaged golem was lifted off the ground. Almost at the same time, Zhang Dong jumped into the air while leaving a hole in the ground. The people were stupefied by this display as jumping at this weight class was almost impossible.

A swift kick was delivered to the Blackhelm house golem which turned it into scrap metal. He could only do this as the pilots decided to eject themselves to safety. Otherwise, he would have had to lower his kicking power.

A scrap of parts descended on the ground after Zhang Dong’s perfectly placed burning flying kick. His whole foot looked like it was covered in plasma and the moment it collided with the opponent it exploded.

“T-the victory goes to… the Hillmane house! Please give a round of applause!”

The announcer called out and was met with crickets as no one expected a turnabout of this magnitude. The opponent Zhang Dong was facing was even highly rated in this tournament and not someone that was trying to lose.

The white golem lifted its arm up into the sky while making a fist. The moment it did the people in the audience burst out in cheers.

“That was a stunning show of power!”

“What is that golem design, what were those peculiar movements!”

They cheered him on as he returned to the place he came from. A lot of the craftsmen that were gathered here were already trying to analyze how this golem operated. There was clearly more to it than what met the eye. Its reduced size didn’t make it any weaker than the other machines.

Due to this, the old man that was proudly holding his hand up in the air and mimicking the golem was now being barraged with questions. All the nobles were interested in the new design and how it operated.

This was something made by Zhang Dong though and he didn’t leave any crafting schematics behind. Even if he wanted to make a profit from this golem he wouldn’t be able to do it in this way. It would also be impossible for other people to pilot it as it was made for Zhang Dong and his two summoners.

“I think that went well for a test ride, how are you two feeling?”

Zhang Dong asked while slowly walking back to their hangar. There wasn’t much damage done to the golem he made but he still needed to check it before the next battle.

“I feel fine, how about you Isabella”

“Yes, I feel like we could have continued for a bit more.”

The two girls inside chuckled at each other while Zhang Dong gave them a scan. They were his power source so after this battle he had an idea of how long this golem could operate.

‘Not that bad, the use of puppet technology and this mana engine is working wonders. I wonder if my sect could utilize this technology when I return…’

He started imagining an army of large mecha golems that were even larger than his model. With the better alloys and materials that his world had to offer he would be able to improve on this design even further.

“That’s good to hear.”

They managed to return to their garage and only heard the other golems leaving after they closed the door behind them. There weren’t that many fights as there were a limited number of golems.

This was also the only day that this tournament was taking place. Due to this people needed to take the longevity of their golems into consideration. They needed to last till the very end and if they broke between fights it was over.

This was also seen as part of the king’s test. Only a wise king would be able to think ahead in this kind of situation. While this was a nice notion in reality the one that had the best technology or most funds won.

“You two relax while I perform some diagnostics.”

While waiting for the next match Zhang Dong split into many tiny versions of himself. He started performing all kinds of tests while ironing out some battle scars. Even though he wasn’t hit even once he delivered some hard hits with his feet and hands. These spots needed to be rechecked for any breaks and then fixed accordingly.

“How many opponents will we have to contend with?”

Asked Beatrice while looking at the small group of Leigongs.

“Not that many my lady, there are only about thirty contestants in total and the fights never take that long.”

A dwarf from the household answered while the work was being performed on the mech. The two girls had some time to relax but not for long as soon they would need to go into battle again. Thankfully the other fights would be taking a while, there was enough time to rest and even see all the other opponents that they would be facing later.

Chapter 316

“Hillmane household takes the win again, let us give a round of applause for the king candidate! With this, only one match remains! Who will be our next king!”

A large white golem strode back below the arena while the people cheered. This was the semifinals and Zhang Dong’s side had managed to clear them with suffering only minimal damage and tear.

The combination of cultivator automaton and the technology of the dwarven race proved quite effective here. The only real problem was the limited time of operation due to Isabella’s and Beatrice’s involvement.

“How are you two doing?”

“W-we are fine Mr. Leigong.”

Answered Beatrice while sweating a bit.

“Yes, just one more match, we can handle it!”

Replied Isabella while also not looking especially rested. The fights started taking longer the more advanced golems they thought and Zhang Dong was also getting the hang of piloting this mech. Due to the long tournament, the two girls that were used as batteries were slowly running out of juice.

“Conserve your power, only the last match remains.”

He could only cheer them on and have them drink some mana potions. Those helped slightly but prolonged use had diminishing returns. The mana that people used in this world was connected to the soul and the longer you drained it the harder it was to recover.

Zhang Dong powered down for the time being and returned to his own soul dimension to give the girls more time to rest. While they were doing their breathing exercises outside the golem the earth rumbled above them.

The last pre-final match was taking place above them. On one side was Takeshi and the hero team, on the other some rich dwarven noble. He had seen the golem that the kids were using and it was quite a beast.

It was clear to him that the person that built this was banking on the heroes piloting it. This golem was huge and required people with high mana capacity to boost the mana engines that it was running on. While most golems only had one this possessed multiple. Clearly, they used some secrets to construct it as most golems were stuck with one engine. Adding multiple ones was dangerous and could end in an explosion.

From what he knew the household Takeshi was fighting for was called Runefall. It was the most influential family in this city and even before the heroes arrived they were said to be the favorite.

Zhang Dong even believed that this family had other backup golems depending on the pilots. Probably if they didn’t get the operators they wanted they would go with a different design. With the heroes on board, they were in the strongest position to win it all.

“Dang, Is it over already?”

There was a signal that the fight above them was over in an instant. The other house that was qualified towards the semi-finals didn’t even last a minute against Takeshi and their golem. Now they would have an hour to rest before the main event took place.

Without much to do, they waited. From the distance, they could hear some kind of large machine lumbering down through the corridor. The tremors that followed the footsteps indicated that this golem was much heavier than the rest.

The hour passed fast and it was finally time for the last bout. Only one side would be walking out victorious. All the families that had failed to achieve victory would be put through hard times. Without the king title the loss of money could not be regained, they would need to tighten their belt as it would take years for them to recover.

This was the same for the Hillmane household, but the old head of the family was already glad that his family reached this point. From his perspective being the runner-up was already an honor. Everyone would know his house name from this moment. Gaining new trade partners would become easy as their name became famous.

“Fellow dwarves, this has been what you have been waiting for. The birth of a new king! Soon we will know who will have the honor of leading our race into the future!”

The announcer started rattling on while one of the gates opened up. A mostly white humanoid golem walked through it, shield in hand.

“Let us welcome the Hillmane household, the dark horse of this king tournament! No one expected them to come this far, can they finish the deal and become immortalized in history? Or will they be a stepping stone for the true victors!”

After Zhang Dong came out on the other side the other slab of rock started sliding down. There stood quite the large metallic contraption. It was barely able to fit through the frame with its multiple legs.

“It’s no surprise that House Runefall has made it this far! Their golem innovations have been known throughout the lands by all. Will they be cemented as the greatest golem manufacturers in our dwarven history and take the crown?”

Everyone looked at the marvel of engineering that was before them. This golem’s bottom part looked like a spider. The many legs were a must to support this machine's large frame. It looked a bit similar to an Arachne-type monster that was wearing heavy dwarven armor.

The spider-like legs connected to a large abdomen on which some cannons were placed. Then it all stretched into a bulky humanoid torso that also had two sets of arms. This thing dwarfed Zhang Dong’s mecha more than a head’s length in height and was several times longer as well.

If you looked from the outside there was no possible way for the Hillmane house to win. Their golem looked to be very lightweight and built for mobility. It didn’t look that it would be able to produce enough power to damage it in the first place. That is if it didn’t have a certain cultivator piloting it.

“Well then, let the finals begin, only one champion can remain!”

The start gong sounded and the crowd cheered.

“Go Hillmane, show those pompous Runefall fools that money isn’t everything!”

“Yeah, go Hillmane!”

To Zhang Dong’s surprise, his side had garnered praise from most of the dwarves. They seemed to prefer the smaller Hillmane faction over the other to win. It was a classical David vs Goliath scenario, though he wasn’t sure if he would be considered David as he had far more up his sleeve than these people realized.

‘I should probably end this fast…’

He could tell that his two partners wouldn’t last through a prolonged battle. It wouldn’t be hard to slowly grind away on this monstrous golem. He had seen it fight and it was rather slow, most of its wins were due to how the other golems were designed.

The dwarves by nature build slow and lumbering creations. Speed was never their forte and it seemed that they fully abandoned that notion. They invested everything in power and defense. He could see a fast machine with ranged potential being able to destroy this thing in a prolonged fight.

The biggest obstacle with that plan was the limited battle area, there were no places to hide or take cover. The golems had to directly clash with each other, thus the bulkier ones came out victorious. The only one that was going against the grain was him.

Finally, the battle started off with a bang. The cannons that were on the large golem started firing while Zhang Dong dodged to the side. His shield was used this time around, it was glowing slightly and producing a thin layer of mana that didn’t let the large bullets through.

This was Takeshi’s tactic in the other fights. Spam massive amounts of bullets at his target while slowly advancing forward. He was clearly forcing a win without caring about damaging the mech in the process.

The problem was his opponent that was able to dance around the massive golem without suffering any damage. If Zhang Dong had enough energy to burn through he would have preferred to wait out till his opponent was out of ammo. Alas, he needed to charge in as he had limited time. The golem with the many mana engines would surely outlast him and the girls in a battle of attrition so he needed to strike.

Thus he used his advantage, which was his mobility. The body of the white golem started glowing in blue light. Following this light was an increase in speed which Zhang Dong used to close the gap between him and the golem.

This time he utilizes his entire kit, the sword was pulled out and activated. The energy beam sprung into life and made quick work of one of the spider legs while Zhang Dong quickly backed off. The spot that he previously occupied became riddled with holes.

He didn’t stop at only this one leg though, he mercilessly continued to attack. Slicing each leg off while evading all the enemy attacks that came his way. The crowd cheered as they were surprised by the speed advantage that the white golem had. It was as if the defensive capabilities didn’t matter at all. A speed and attack-focused golem was clearly a valid option if you wanted to go with a cheaper variant.

Due to the large golem’s limited mobility it suffered. Soon it was left on three legs that couldn’t support the increased weight of that abdomen. The cannons kept firing and Zhang Dong had to even evade a spider leg being thrown his way by one of those large golem arms.

It was clear that Takeshi wasn’t used to tactics like this. He mostly overpowered his opponents with sheer strength but Zhang Dong had used a simple tactic to get under his skin. This was done at a cost, he could already tell that Beatrice and Isabella were running on fumes.

‘It was all for this moment, time to ignite the engine and finish this.’

He did this all so that his enemy would be unable to evade his last-ditch attack. He tossed his shield towards his enemy while grasping the light sword with both hands. While Takeshi focused on the incoming bulky projectile he charged forward.

The white body began to glow in gold color. With the boost of his holy element, the golem looked as if it was made from pure gold. Arcs of lightning traveled towards the energy sword and caused it to become longer and wider while also causing it to produce more light.

Everyone was blinded in an instant, right after Takeshi’s golem batted the incoming shield to the side his vision became blurry. He could see his opponent coming and quickly reacted by swinging his own weapons forward. The large golem has swords in each of its hands, now was finally the time for Takeshi to use them.

It happened in an instant, it was as if time had stopped for everyone. Zhang Dong’s mech appeared on the other side of the arena with a missing head while kneeling down. While the large golem on the other side seemed to be undamaged.

Before the people could gasp and before the cannons could shoot at the damaged white golem a strange sound was heard. It was as if two plates of metal were rubbing against each other.

“Look!”

The golem that Takeshi and the heroes were in began to split apart as it was cleaved by Zhang Dong’s laser sword. It was perfectly sliced into two halves that slowly parted to the sides revealing the bewildered pilots inside that were now able to see the outside world.

No one was injured as Zhang Dong was sure not to aim for any living beings inside the machine. The fight was over and the headless golem stood up again, its fist raised high while the crowd clapped and cheered for the winner and birth of the new king.

Chapter 317

“Ugh…”

The sound of coughing was heard while four youths with darkened faces crawled out of a wreck of a golem. They were the party of heroes that were just defeated by something that was very familiar to them. All of them came from the country that the design Zhang Dong used his inspiration for.

“D-did we really lose?”

“Using that is cheating!”

Takeshi cough into his hand while trying to rub out the dark sludge that was on his face. He remembered the surprise when he first saw the mech that Zhang Dong created. Instantly he was regretting joining this side and being stuck in this huge golem that he couldn’t even pilot himself.

He needed to keep the promise with the princes though which he was unable to do. Now he wouldn’t be receiving that kiss as a reward due to his failure. The girls from his party also seemed distant lately this whole hero experience wasn’t feeling so good lately.

“The tournament is over, all hail the new dwarven king, Thondin Hillmane!”

While the youths were crawling out of the wreckage the dwarves had forgotten about them even being there. They were all far too busy cheering for their new king, finally after a long time of arguing there was a new king.

Even though Thondin was only the oldest son and the father was still alive, he would be taking over. While registering for this competition every side had to fill out the person that would become the new king.

This was one of the rare occasions where the leader of the household gave away the rights of kingship to a son. This was good for the Hillmane house as the younger Thondin would be able to hold on to the title for a lot longer than his old father.

“Are you okay?”

Takeshi looked up to the person that was calling out to him. He could see a rather cute golden-haired girl reaching out her hand towards him. The arena lights that were directly behind her made her look a bit otherworldly.

“An angel?”

“Heh, look at this sweet talker.”

A voice that he knew called out from the side. When glancing at it he noticed it was Zhang Dong in his smaller form looking at him. After further inspection, he also noticed that the girl that was reaching out to him was Beatrice.

“Sweet talker? I d-didn’t…”

He blushed a bit after noticing that he was staring at the girl for a prolonged time. Due to the pink-haired princess hanging around him for so long he wasn’t able to notice the other girls around him. Now after getting a good look at Beatrice he could see that she was quite charming. She didn’t have the assets that the princess had but her face was somewhat gentler.

“Let me clean you up lover boy…”

Zhang Dong called out in a mocking tone. After this Takeshi and the three girls found themselves being submerged in large bubbles of water. These bubbles quickly absorbed all the dirt from their bodies. The water then flowed back while having a dark color, surprisingly Takeshi felt rather dry after this strange spell was finished.

“Takeshi, next time you should discuss things with us before doing something like this…”

Zhang Dong said while floating back towards Beatrice.

“Otherwise Beatrice here will be very sad.”

He quickly pointed to the girl that had appeared. At first, he wanted to shout back that he didn’t need to listen to Zhang Dong, but after his attention was brought back to Beatrice again he held his mouth shut.

“Interesting…”

Zhang Dong mumbled.

“What’s interesting?”

Another golden-haired beauty appeared from the side while everyone gathered.

“Oh nothing, we should head back these dwarves will be holding a big feast for a few days after the new king is chosen. We must discuss the side of our contract and get ready to depart. I bet the demons won’t just sit on their asses and let us attack them without putting up some defenses.”

“Also you four… you need to stop trusting those royals…”

This was the last thing that Zhang Dong said before the group from the royal family showed up. The pink-haired princess was there with her three brothers that moved between Zhang Dong’s side and the Hero party.

“Oh no, Lord Takeshi are you alright?”

The girl was clearly acting all cutesy while rubbing all up into Takeshi. This was painfully obvious to Zhang Dong and the two girls that were standing next to him. Both of them had a look of disgust on their faces as this transpired.

For one reason or another Takeshi was quick to straighten up. He even gently pushed the pink hair ditz to the side while glancing between her and Beatrice.

“Oh no, I’m fine!”

Zhang Dong on the other hand just chuckled while sending a telepathic message to his summoner.

‘I think you have a new fan. Maybe you can talk some sense into him while using your womanly charm?’

The blond girl was confused and also started looking at this hero while also glancing at Zhang Dong. She also went red in the face the moment the womanly charms were mentioned. She was still someone that never even had a boyfriend before in her life.

‘Hey, what are you two doing?’

Isabella jumped into the conversation. Due to the telepathic transmission, she couldn’t hear them talking but she knew that something was fishy. What she did was hug Beatrice while pulling her away from the situation.

‘Leave her out of this!’

Zhang Dong started rubbing his head at the scene. Everything was getting pushed back into the rom-com genre. It seemed like some strange love square was being formed. With two of the girls, Takeshi and the pink-haired princess being involved. If it expanded further due to the three girls from Takeshi’s world was also a possibility. All of them were glancing here and one girl, in particular, wasn’t amused.

“Hey, what are you doing Takeshi!”

This girl was Ami who now abandoned her prince and started pulling Takeshi by the arm. The pink-haired princess did the same but from the other side. The youth in question on the other hand was still sneaking glances at Beatrice that was getting pulled away by Isabella.

‘So Beatrice really is the true main character? Is it the main character aura that is attracting so many people towards her?’

Zhang Dong thought while also being okay with Isabella winning Beatrice over. The rest of her suitors seemed to mostly have underhanded motives while this girl was a bit purer.

“Okay, I think we should go back, let us return to the hotel!”

There was a lot of talking as Zhang Dong surrounded almost everyone with a thin layer of his spiritual energy. He carried exactly six people out towards where the father of Thondin was celebrating. The four members of the human royal family didn’t seem amused as he yanked the hero party with him.

“Didn’t I tell you, my son is going to be the king!”

The old man looked quite chipper, it was hard to believe that he was someone that was on death's door just a week ago. He had his hand locked around some other old noble and the two were in beard rubbing proximity. The person he was holding hostage didn’t seem that happy about this but also unable to push away someone that was now the father of the new dwarven king.

“It’s time for you to keep your end of the bargain, dwarf.”

Zhang Dong didn’t really want to wait for too long. He got right to the point as he approached the merry man that was also quite drunk.

“It’s the spirit! I’ll be sure to make my boy build a big statue for you! Whoever said that spirits can’t be trusted should be hanged!”

The man seemed quite grateful which would probably speed things up. Surprisingly the man of the hour Thondin was spaced out. He was also here in this VIP booth. He was stuck looking down at the golem parts in the arena with his mouth wide open. It was clear that he never expected something like this to ever happen. Now he had to be king even if he didn’t like it.

“Don’t mind him, the boy will come around.”

The old man grinned while moving over to where Zhang Dong was. He gave Thondin a hard smack to the back which sent the new king tumbling forward.

“Get a grip of yourself, you are the new king, start acting like one!”

After the hit, Thondin seemed to snap back to reality. He looked at his old man and instantly straightened out. Even though he wasn’t ecstatic about this turn of events he also knew that this was a great honor. With this, his family’s future was secured. Even though the king's title wasn’t hereditary there were certain things a royal house would receive even when he died.

There was not much that Zhang Dong and his companions could do for now. They needed to wait a bit more for Thondin’s coronation. This also never went down as seeming less as people might think.

Jealousy was still there, the houses that spend all of their money now had someone they could point their hate at. Before this dwarf actually was presented his crown he was not the king. It wasn’t odd for the king candidate to be killed before they went through with the ceremony and it was also a part of the test. Only a person that survived till the end would be seen as the proper ruler.

With this, the next few days Zhang Dong and the Heroes were placed on guard duty. Now with a winner that was on their side they had something in common. Surprisingly now Takeshi was all for spending more time with their side. Beatrice was probably the main reason for it.

Due to the kids being preoccupied with each other it was on him to guard Thondin. Luckily he had vast detection skills and the dwarves didn’t make for good assassins. A few incidents happened but they were all quickly resolved by him. During this time Isabella was mostly trying to peel Takeshi off her friend.

After a few days the festivities were ramping up and the date for the coronation came. Thondin was now all dressed up and ready to take the plunge. When he was walking down towards the throne a strange sound was heard. When he looked to the side he noticed Zhang Dong holding a poison arrow that was a few inches away from his head.

The perpetrator was apprehended and this signaled the last assassination attempt that would befall this house. After the coronation was through any further acts would be seen as treason. The houses involved would be burned down and all its members down to the relatives killed without mercy. This was the law of the land and the other houses would keep to it.

‘Finally… we can finish this damn quest…’

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh while looking at the crown touching Thondin’s head. With this, his task was over and he would finally be able to leave this underground city.

Chapter 318

“Uh, finally we are leaving… I need to get new clothes…”

A rather annoyed Isabella was looking at the entrance of the seemingly active volcano. After Zhang Dong’s victory, a week had already passed. The dwarves were celebrating for a few days and everyone was drinking themselves stupid.

The young members from the royal family nor the hero party were safe from this. Everyone got drunk with the exclusion of Zhang Dong, Beatrice, and Isabella that were safe thanks to their scary lightning chaperone.

Neither the dwarves nor the humans were willing to cross his path as he had proven himself in being a great wall that could not be breached. Some of them tried, like Takeshi that for some reason or another had changed his target from the pink-haired princess and was now trying to court Beatrice.

This resulted in some strange encounters that mostly ended with Isabella shouting at everyone. With him backing her up even the royals couldn’t do anything. Their side had now both the elves and the dwarves, the golems had been brought on the large elven ship and were now part of the crew.

‘This actually looks like a competent fighting force…’

Zhang Dong thought to himself while looking through the people that were on the current ship. They were given a large battalion of golems with experienced operators. They also had many flying ships with the super large one in the middle.

This flying ship on its own possessed magic power that could rival a demon lord. It could even deliver a more devastating strike similar to the Argonaut that he made back home. Just like with his own model it needed some time to charge.

“I wish victory upon you all!”

“Thank you, my king!”

An old-looking dwarf with many battle scars on his face was saluting to his new king, Thondin Hillmane. The new monarch looked like a proper king with his crown. It looked like he had made peace with his new position and was willing to take this task on.

The old dwarf was the commanding officer that the kingdom was lending him. This man was supposedly the best man for the job. With him around, there would be no problem in organizing some strategies.

“Great Spirit Emperor, we are ready to depart.”

“Let us depart then, let us go to the dark lands, time for the final battle to commence!”

The dark lands were a dark place covered by a gloomy forest. It was a spot on this continent where the barrier between the lands of demons and the other races was thin. Through it, lesser demons were able to slip in.

It was not something that anyone was willing to venture towards. The armies of the three main races remained outside the danger zone and could only observe. Any expeditions that they attempted were unfruitful.

The expeditions were never a combined venture, this was the first time that a large force of this size would be attempting it. Together with the heroes and the famous Lightning Emperor things were looking well. Three of the five demon lords were dead and now it looked like humanity would regain its footing at the top of the food chain once more.

“Will we really be able to defeat the demon lord?”

Beatrice asked while looking out through a window that was in the large ship’s interior. They were now flying through the air on the course towards the lands that were still occupied by the demons.

“Of course we will and we must.”

Replied Zhang Dong that was awaiting this day with desperation. Some months had passed by and he was still here. Even though he didn’t want to put these people in danger there was no other way of getting the rest of the cubes.

He also wasn’t willing to use the one that was used to bring Takeshi and the three girls over. Without it, the three would be stuck here as he took it away and the teleportation array that brought them over here was not in a working condition.

“Don’t worry, just leave it to me. Takeshi might not look that reliable but he isn’t weak either.”

The heroes were also at a high level compared to the people in this world. If they worked together they should be able to take out a demon lord. What they lacked was experience but gaining it would prolong everything.

Thus he didn’t put much faith into them instead, he used the time to improve on the golem designs and also shared some magical knowledge with the elves. By strengthening his own forces he hoped to mitigate the weakened state of the heroes.

‘But still… I think it might be bad to let these kids take out a demon lord instead of me...’

Zhang Dong had a little theory that he couldn’t test out. He had taken all the corrupt cubes for himself but he believed that they might have been intended to fall into the heroes hands. Maybe by absorbing their power, the hero party would gain enough strength to be able to take on the last boss.

He feared that if they killed one or two of the remaining lords that he would lose the nuclei in the process. The question was if it was better to increase the strength of the hero party or to believe in his own power. He had stayed busy and cultivated his own soul constantly.

Its size had increased which would translate well if he ever reached his old cultivation level. He even felt that he could use it to battle against masters at the great circle level.

“Great Spirit, we are approaching the dark lands, what are your instructions.”

With him now having both dwarves, elves, and a chunk of the human faction on his side he was turned into the commander of this expedition. It seemed like things were coming together but he knew that this was just the time when something usually went wrong.

“Tell everyone to stop, I will head out and examine the situation.”

After giving the standby order everyone was instructed to wait for further instructions. The dwarves quickly entered their golems and the elven wizards prepared for battle. The other ships stood a bit behind the main elven one while they waited.

Zhang Dong in his adult form floated forward towards the dark lands. Just as they were described it was an area covered by grayish fog and darkened forest. This reminded him of the thick fog that the Cthulhu-like monster was occupying.

‘Is this fog blocking my perception as then?’

Even while he focused with all his might the fog was somehow blocking his spiritual sense. It was similar to that one time back in his own world, he was unable to peek too far. His range was at about three hundred meters in all directions. The only things that he could feel were some animals and insects.

‘These life forms… they have been altered by the demonic energies of this place…’

He could feel that the animals were twisted by the evil energy that resided in these lands. They had grotesque demonized appearances that were ghoulish in nature. Even the insects were corrupt, any stings by them would result in poisoning.

‘I guess we'll have to venture into the unknown…’

Zhang Dong returned to the ship, the party of heroes was here along with his two summoners.

“How was it, did you see anything.”

Takeshi asked with some concern in his voice.

“Yes but not much, the corruption runs deep. The fog that covers this place is filled with demonic energy; it will slowly deteriorate a person’s psyche if they breathe in the fumes. I believe that any regular person would start changing into a grotesque creature after a few hours.”

“Grotesque creatures?”

Ami flinched at that notion along with the other girls that were here.

“So, we will become like one of the royal family members?”

Isabella slid in a little joke while the other people gathered here chuckled. Lucky for them the people in question were on their own ships and not very willing to lend their men.

“Don’t worry, this ship has a protective shield that can block out this miasma. You four will be okay, something like that will be unable to harm your bodies. It will only affect untrained people anyone versed in magic should be fine.”

Zhang Dong reassured everyone that this fog would not affect them. They also had the elven flying ship that possessed a giant barrier that would not let anything through.

“Let us move in but remain vigilant, it’s still some time before we reach the edge of the barrier.”

The order to move forward was given, every ship that was here possessed some kind of magical barrier. With it out the dark fog would be unable to move in and claim any victims.

Magical barriers in various colors started to appear and the hero party entered the demonic territory. Every magical device that could detect demons was activated but due to the fog, the readings were all a jumbled mess.

Zhang Dong stood at the front of the ship while looking forward. This demonic forest spread for a couple of kilometers and at the end would be the point that they would need to strike. The plan was quite straight forward but if it came to fruition no one knew.

Most of it relied on Zhang Dong’s capabilities. Some people still had the misconception of the heroes being the ones that they needed to rely on. The ones that could see the bigger picture knew that Leigong was the pivotal point of this operation. He had already proved himself to being stronger than a demonic lord.

“Mr. Leigong…”

“What is it, you both should return to the protective cabin.”

While slowly gliding through the thick fog a worried Beatrice arrived. She was alone but he could tell that Isabella would probably be arriving soon. The two had become inseparable since becoming a good team.

“I’ve been meaning to ask you…”

“Hm, yes?”

“A-are you going to be leaving after the demon king is destroyed?”

“Huh?”

Zhang Dong almost tripped over his feet as he was asked this question. Somehow Beatrice had figured out that he was not here to stay. He had never mentioned this fact to this girl or to anyone else. Somehow she must have come to this conclusion herself.

“What makes you think that?”

“You seem awfully set on battling the demon king… as if you don’t have enough time…”

“Ah… was it that obvious?”

He was indeed rushing it, this was a half-assed plan brought on by him worrying about his family. For all that he knew they could be getting attacked by some other sect at this very moment.

“I… I was right? You are really leaving?”

Beatrice flinched back as Zhang Dong didn’t even try to hide it. He felt like at this point he owed his summoner an explanation. He felt that if she stuck to Isabella her future would be assured.

But before he could give her a proper explanation he noticed something.

“Damn, Beatrice, return to Isabella, I need you both to lend me your power… a demon lord has appeared!”

He turned to the fog while squinting with his eyes, there he felt a surge of demonic energy coming his way and there was more than one.

“Everyone prepare for battle!”

Chapter 319

“Line up the cannons… Fire!”

Explosions filled the air as many bat-like creatures filled the sky. They all came from the fog and were now trying to bring down the shields from the flying ships.

“Ghouls and Vampires, it must be the Lord of Blood!”

Someone from the elven race called out while defending the ship. Most of the members from the elven race that were here were proficient barrier mages. They were placed in certain strategic locations on the ship and fueling the mana shields with their magic.

The Ghouls looked somewhat like giant bats while the Vampires had a more humanoid shape and could float without the use of wings. The so-called Lord of Blood was slowly hovering in the background.

He looked like a cross between the two. His all-around shape was humanoid with giant bat-like wings attached to his back. His arms were elongated and his hands looked like giant claws. His skin was grayish-white which made him look like a living corpse.

His face was a mix of human and batlike features, when he opened his mouth a clear view of dagger-like teeth greeted anyone dumb enough to fight this being.

This was not the only monster that the heroes needed to face off against. The demon Lord of Blood wasn’t the only archdemon that was here. Below him, a massive being was slowly treading towards the group of flying ships.

It was the Lord of Destruction and the last archdemon that still remained. Somehow two of the mighty demons had gathered here and were waiting for them all along.

This being was truly humongous, each time one of its large elongated appendages descended on the ground, massive tremors spread throughout this dark forest. It trampled everything that blocked its way.

Its appearance was more grotesque than that of the vampire-like being. The shape that this monster took was similar to that of a spider. The biggest difference were the eight legs that instead of being fully arachnid-like had large humanoid hands.

The creature looked like three massive humans fused with each other. The front consisted of just the chest part with its arms extended. It had three heads that consisted of only mouths and no eyes. The eyes were instead embedded in its strange fused torso and were constantly blinking while looking for new enemies to attack.

Above this massive creature and the Lord of Blood Leigong the Lightning Emperor was floating. He was now glaring at the vampiric lord before him, his body already covered in golden radiant holy energies that caused the lesser vampires to flee.

“I don’t think you will let me through?”

“You shall not pass filthy astral being, this will be your grave. I will absorb your might and the king will descend to cover these lands in the blood of the filthy mortals!”

The demonic lord entered the monologue stage. Zhang Dong was familiar with this defect that these demons had. Thanks to this he had ample time to power up and think about a good plan of attack.

While this monster that he was facing looked to be the more speedy arial type, the one below was clearly a slow tank. With it being stuck on the ground it was safe to leave his flying army to take care of it. He had already passed on the order to engage it from afar with a kiting strategy. If everything failed the dwarves were to utilize their golems and try to stall it till he was done with this monster. The heroes were also going to help but only with range support.

After being cooped up in the elven and dwarven countries Zhang Dong hadn’t had the opportunity to let loose. This overgrown vampire lord looked like the perfect sparring partner to release his frustrations and stress.

Even then he waited, the moment the monologue was over the monster charged up and attacked. It was very similar to the one the lord of pain fired off. The monster’s mouth opened up and a beam of crimson energy flew forward.

Zhang Dong didn’t dodge but instead extended his hand forward. His finger started glowing in blue light. A set of pentagram-like magic circles extended from the spot his finger was pointing at. There were ten circles and each one was larger than the previous.

The red beam of dark light collided with the outermost ring and shattered it into many tiny lights. It continued forward while causing all of the rings to evaporate into nothingness. When it passed the sixth one it stopped, unable to travel further before blinking out of existence.

‘These magic spells are the real thing.’

This was actually one of the spells that he learned from this world. Together with his own cultivation knowledge, he was now able to utilize some of the magical skills the elves used. Due to being in this magical world, using mana attacks was more efficient than sticking to his spiritual energy-based attacks.

‘They also lower the strain on the girls…’

He pointed out with his finger once again. Behind him, magical circles of similar shapes and sizes started to appear. To non-mages this wouldn’t look like anything special but to the experts, this was something mind-boggling.

“Take this, mass elemental arrows!”

With a twitch of the same finger, a surge of arrows made from various elements descended on the large vampire monster. There were thousands of them, their colorful lights filled the sky and rained down on the flying archdemon.

The demonic lord covered his whole body in its giant webbed wings and surrounded himself in dark red energy. He was quick to notice that he would be unable to dodge this attack, instead, he decided to enforce his defenses and block it.

With a more stationary target, the many magic arrows had a point of focus. From rain, they turned into a flood of magical energy that descended on the encased demon. The black sphere that formed around the demon became bathed in rainbow-like light and vanished within.

‘I don’t think it will be that easy?’

Zhang Dong thought while his attack continued and finally subsided. He was greeted by the Demon Lord of Blood, or at least half of him. His wings were damaged and half of his body seemed to have melted away during the magical downpour.

It might have looked like he was done for but in a matter of seconds, his whole body started glowing red. From the damaged parts of his body blood started gushing out. This blood quickly reformed into his lost body parts and formed a complete form again.

‘He is a bit stronger than the other demon lords…’

It was clear after the exchange that this monster’s main forte was the regenerative ability. The other demon lords could regenerate fast but not this fast. He didn’t worry though as he didn’t quite use his usual trump card against the demon. This trump card made going against these beings easy from the start.

“Foolish Astral being, my body can not be seriously damaged by the likes of you! Now die!”

“Is that so? How about this though?”

Zhang Dong clutched his fist together and a bolt of golden lightning appeared in his hand. Without giving the monster much time to feel this new spell out he threw it at him. The attack produced a thunderclap while descending on its foe.

This time around the monster’s black pearl-like eyes bulged out in fright and he quickly propelled itself to the side as it attempted to evade this attack. This bolt of energy was not something easily dodged and it connected with the demon’s leg.

This appendage was then quickly sliced off by the monster itself. It knew that this attack carried holy energies in itself, the cut of leg crumbled into dust almost instantly while the cut of wound regenerated into a fresh leg.

“You’re a bit smarter than the other demons… but also less resistant…”

Zhang Dong was a bit surprised at how quickly that leg disintegrated into dust after taking the hit. The other demon lords didn’t succumb to the holy energies as fast as this one. He wasn’t sure but this monster was a vampire. Vampires seemed to be quite weak against flames and holy energies alike. It seemed that this monster had high regenerative abilities but was also super susceptible to the type of energy that he exudes.

“Well then… try to evade this…”

The same massive amount of magical circles was produced, this time around instead of the various colors of the rainbow the magical arrows were golden.

“You… lower being!”

The Demonic lord of Blood looked to be panicking after seeing the magical arrows again. He didn’t bunker up this time but instead spread his wings widely apart. Many dark crimson magical circles of heresy magic appeared behind him. It was a very similar spell to his own with the difference of the different dark coloring.

In a flash, a battle of holy vs evil commenced. The many magical arrows of Zhang Dong connected with the multitude of bolts of crimson. The demon was over his head though as the golden arrows continued on their trajectory even after bumping into the demonic crimson bolts.

Soon the overgrown bat found itself running away from the holy arrow attack. Whenever it got hit it would slice off its body part that was affected. Even with the continued rain of energy, this tactic seemed to be working for it as it was able to survive right till the end. Its body sliced up and regenerating even now.

“I will bathe in your blood, you damn astral creature!”

“Yeah... yeah…”

The demon lord glared at Zhang Dong but was only greeted by his after image. The Lightning Emperor on the other hand appeared behind this creature while holding a massive sword of light in both his hands.

With a practiced swing, he cleaved the monster into two perfectly symmetrical halves. From the spot that he had sliced it the creature’s body started cramping and burning apart. He was sure to inject as much holy energy as he could but even then he knew that this might not be enough.

Before the body crumbled into dust a part of it escaped. It looked like a pitch-back heart that was slowly beating and spitting out some dark fumes to mask its trajectory.

“Do you think I was born yesterday?”

He was waiting for this to happen and he pointed down with this finger. A bolt of energy that was hovering above the clouds and out of sight descended onto this very heart. It collided with it while causing a massive explosion.

Zhang Dong had already faced a multitude of demonic beings in this and in other worlds. They always had some underhanded way of playing dead and escaping. So he made a backup plan to strike it down when it was most vulnerable.

‘One down one to go…’

After grabbing the cube fragment he turned to the massive demon lord that was to the side. It was in the process of being pelted by the ship’s magical cannons and also the people that were inside.

‘But maybe I won’t even need to act this time around…’

It didn’t seem like this demon lord had anything going for itself besides its huge size. It was like a sitting duck against the many flying ships that kept their distance. It could only throw trees and massive boulders while also firing beams of dark energy from its three mouths.

Which were mostly deflected by the elven barrier technology and also with a little aid of the heroes that were using their own ranged spells as support. It seemed like the path forward would be open and they would soon be facing what was on the other side...

Chapter 320

“Hey.”

“Hey…”

“Is something wrong, you look a bit down?”

Isabella called out to Beatrice that was leaning against the railing of the large elven flying ship. The battle with the two remaining demon lords was now over. They were resting right outside the barrier to the demonic continent.

After Zhang Dong had taken care of the Demon Lord of Blood, the larger Demon Lord of Destruction went down with ease. There was no need for Zhang Dong to get involved as Takeshi and the rest of the heroes were enough.

The large monster only had size but was clearly not very intelligent. It was unable to contend with all the firepower that the people of the races threw at it. Takeshi only needed to utilize his magical sword to slice off the monster’s head after it had been weakened. The whole battle took a while but it wasn’t that dangerous thanks to the flight advantage that they had. Zhang Dong was sure to snatch the last cube fragment before it was absorbed by the group of heroes instead.

Now the elves were making preparations to get this barrier out of the way. The dwarves and humans slowly set up the perimeter around here to block out any demonic monsters that might want to disturb them. The fog was still there and it was thick. Even though the demon lords were dead, that didn’t mean that the lesser demons wouldn't try their luck.

“Oh it’s nothing, just thinking about the future, everything is going so fast. It feels like the summoning ritual was just yesterday, then Mr. Leigong appeared...”

Beatrice lowered her head and slumped against the ship’s railing, it was clear to Isabella that was right next to her that something was wrong. The girl decided to place her hand on Beatrice’s shoulder as she moved right next to her.

“It’s going to be fine, we’ll be fine. I’m sure that Demon King will have no chance against your great spirit!”

“I know that… it’s just…”

Beatrice gave out a sigh while looking out in a random direction, there she saw the dwarven golems moving some magical equipment closer to the barrier. This barrier looked like a giant mirror, it reflected whatever was on their side. Due to this, it was impossible to know what was on the other side. The possibility of monsters being there was quite high.

“It’s going to be fine, we are going to make it through this together!”

Isabella placed her hand on Beatrice’s while moving closer, she could clearly tell that her friend was getting emotional but she wasn’t sure why. Beatrice looked at Isabella’s hand that was placed on her own and then up which caused the girls eyes to meet.

“You know, I used to hate you…”

“Oh....”

Isabella didn’t pull her hand away and Beatrice didn’t seem like she had anything against this treatment either.

“I wasn’t the nicest person before, this journey opened my eyes up to many things. I used to think that people were below me, that nothing else mattered than noble status.”

“I remember how angry you looked whenever Prince Ludwig gave me attention.”

Beatrice replied while chuckling a bit. The two girls thought back to their old relationship, if it wasn’t for their common dislike for what the prince did they might not have been friends now.

“Well, that idiot did one thing right.”

“Oh, and what would that be?”

“He opened up my eyes…”

Isabella started leaning up towards Beatrice, the two girls were looking into each other's eyes. Time seemed to slow down for the two, it was as if all the noise disappeared and only the two remained in place.

“Beatrice?...”

“Huh?”

The two finally snapped back to reality and looked to the side. There, a Takeshi with a confused expression on his face was standing.

“What were you two…”

He asked as Isabella jumped back as her face was really close to Beatrice’s.

“Oh, she had some dirt on the shoulder…”

Isabella coughed into her hand once before moving to the side. Beatrice just nodded while laughing nervously.

“Is there something you wanted, Lord Takeshi?”

“Oh, The elves were asking for Leigong’s help. He seemed to go away after the battle between the demon lords.”

Zhang Dong returned to his soul dimension to conserve energy. He was taking his time to cultivate so he didn’t really notice what the two girls were doing. Beatrice knew this as well, whenever Zhang Dong cultivated he needed to be called out several times before he noticed.

“Ah, I’ll call him over now.”

With a little crackle of thunder Leigong the Spirit Emperor was out and about.

“Hm… what’s with this mood? Did something happen?”

Zhang Dong was greeted with uncomfortable silence. Beatrice and Isabella were blushing for some reason, their heart rates were also through the roof. After a quick checkup, it didn’t seem that they were affected by any kind of illness.

“N-nothing happened, the Hero just wanted to have a word with you Mr. Leigong.”

“Alright…”

He removed himself from the scene, him being there seemed to make everyone even more uncomfortable. His thoughts were more on the mission before him as this was almost the end of the journey.

“Great spirit, we have made the preparations, we can open up a gap in the barrier but it won’t be enough to get our ships through…”

“Oh, is that so? Let me take a look.”

He floated over to where the magical devices were placed. Many dwarven golems were stationed outside with their cannons pointed at this very spot. This was the section of the barrier where all of the known demonic beings came from.

Now with the eradication of the five archdemons, the people of the races could take a knee and relax. Even if the demon king wasn’t destroyed they future was assured as the demonic armies could not advance into their lands.

Some felt that invading the demonic continent wasn’t a smart idea. No one knew if any more powerful demons resided on the other side of this barrier. It was unwise to poke the hornet’s nest but Zhang Dong needed to go forward. The last cube had to be there where the last boss was. He was now in control of this expedition so even when the princess protested they were quickly silenced by the others.

“It does seem that the entrance size will be limited…”

After scanning the mirror-like barrier he could see that the elven assessment was true. It seemed that even if he was in his most powerful state he wouldn’t be able to destroy this barrier.

The entrance was about two meters in height and one meter in width. It wouldn’t even allow any of the golems to pass through just regular human beings.

‘It looks like this was purposely made like this… Probably to have a small team of heroes enter. I wouldn’t be surprised if the barrier closes instantly after Takeshi and the others go through it…’

He didn’t like the looks of this. There was a big possibility of not being able to turn back if something went wrong. It didn’t look all bad though, all of the demon lords were slain and he had recovered the cube fragments himself.

Sometimes in situations like this, the old boss monsters would return for another fight. He had their power sources though so this was an unlikely scenario. Due to him being here things had changed, the possibility of the demon king on the inside being weaker than he would normally be was also high.

He was banking on this being true, nothing in this world had really been a challenge to him. The girls were constantly pushing their own mana capacities up and he was also getting stronger.

‘I think I should go in there alone…’

Even with that, he didn’t feel like he should endanger the girls or anyone that came with him. He would not risk other people's lives to get what he wanted. He would rather try getting home with the current number of cubes than have Beatrice or Isabella pay the ultimate price.

“Okay listen up, I need you to do something…”

With this, he called out to the elven magicians that came along with him. Now was the time to use all of the extensive knowledge from both of his worlds.

“I came to serve, great spirit!”

“Good, get everyone, I will announce the plan. Have all the ships come together, we will need to take them apart for this to work. Also, get me some paper to write on.”

He rubbed his chin while thinking about how they would be progressing. Within an hour he had all the people of the races gathered. Beatrice, Isabella and the party of heroes were here. The members of the royal family were also here but they kept their distance.

“The entrance to the demon continent is far too small for a large force to enter. Thus I have decided on…”

“Yes, we will gladly go in!”

Before Zhang Dong could proclaim his plan Takeshi jumped forward with his sword raised. Zhang Dong could see the youth sneaking glances at Beatrice while trying to seem gallant and heroic.

“Be quiet you idiot.”

Before this could get out of hand he received a smack to the head.

“None of you will be entering the demonic continent, I alone will face the demons.”

“You alone? We know that you are strong, but how will you face the demon king alone and without the help of your summoner?”

The one asking the question was one of the older princes. The other people gathered here also started mumbling with each other. Everyone knew his strength but they knew that he required Beatrice and Isabella to power him constantly.

“Don’t worry about that, even you will be able to help out, we will do it like this…”

With that said Zhang Dong took out a large piece of parchment that had a strange spell formation with many magical runes on it. This was of course a greater version of the spell formation he utilized during the fight with the first Archdemon that he faced. He expanded on the design which would allow him to draw his power from even the ship's mana engines.

“That is?”

“This is how I will defeat the Demon King, now listen up...”

He quickly explained the gist of his plan. Just like before Beatrice and Isabella would need to sit in the middle of the formation while everyone else was used as sub energy sources. This time around though there were proper powerful mages and machines he could draw his power from.

For some, the plan seemed too good to be true. Sending in a summoned spirit to take out the demon king while everyone stayed behind and was safe sounded outlandish. Most of the people and soldiers here were ready to give up their life for the cause but it seemed that they wouldn’t get a chance for that.

“W-why were we even summoned here if it ends like this…”

Takeshi grumbled while sitting down, he was still hoping to show off his fighting form in front of the ladies.

“Isn’t this fine? We’ll be able to go home if this is over.”

Ami commented while trying to calm down Takeshi. The people from this world were already working. The ships were being taken apart for their mana engines and the golems as well. Zhang Dong had the last say here so the plan would be going through.

“Playing hero isn’t all fun and games Takeshi, leave it up to me. Sometimes you should rely on the adults.”

Takeshi looked a bit down, probably not finding that he wouldn’t get to be the big hero this time around.

“With that, I’ll be leaving the girls up to you. I bet the demons will figure out this plan sooner or later and send a strike force over. Protect them with your life while I’m gone.”

He gave Takeshi a small smack to the chest which seemed to reinvigorate the youth.

“Leave it to me!”

“Okay, let's get this over with!”

Chapter 321

“So this is the demon continent?”

A man radiating golden light entered through what looked to be a crack in the mirror-like barrier. This rift in the demonic barrier quickly mended itself as if it was never there before.

‘Good… I can still feel the connection even with this barrier here.’

He had examined it beforehand, it seemed to only bounce the energies that were from this world. His soul energies were something slightly different, thanks to this and his connection to Beatrice he could be powered remotely.

On the other side were the whole group of dwarves, elves, and humans. They were all gathered together in the grand formation that he created. This formation was even absorbing the demonic fog that surrounded the forest along with any mana that came in contact with it. It then routed this energy towards Beatrice and Isabella that powered him.

‘They aren’t using their whole power now… but I’m already in the nascent soul stage…’

Zhang Dong picked up a larger rock and crushed it with his hand. He felt a lot stronger than he ever felt before since coming to this world. This was much closer to his original power level but was still somewhat behind.

‘Nascent soul early-stage… maybe slightly less.’

After stepping forward he felt that something was off with this place. The demonic energies weren’t all that strong. He expected to be attacked by armies of monsters that were waiting for his arrival but instead he was greeted with silence. When he spread his senses he could feel some monsters hiding but they wouldn’t even pose a serious threat to anyone above the core formation level.

‘Hm, what’s that?’

He suddenly felt the demonic energy spike higher when he examined further into this demonic continent. It seemed that the dark mana was gathering in one certain location. With this in mind, he headed forward, taking his time while going on foot. It didn’t seem that anyone had seen him entering this place, the demons might have actually not been as prepared as he might have thought.

After taking some quick strides forward he started examining his surroundings. He was in a dark forest, all of the light was coming from a large purple moon that was handing in the sky. There were no old texts describing the demonic continent, this barrier had been here for quite a bit and what was on the inside was long forgotten.

‘I guess that’s the spot?’

After taking out some kind of flesh-eating plant with a little lightning bolt he came out to a clearing. There in the distance, he saw it, a massive dark castle that stretched all the way up into the clouds.

It was dimly lit and there was only one path heading towards it. It wasn’t much of a castle beside a few towers here and there. The rest looked like it was carved out of the mountain it was on. Everything was spiked and there were some window openings that were glowing in purple.

When he focused on the path leading up to it he could see some monsters patrolling around. All of them had three eyes and their skin was dark crimson like the demons he met on the other side. These demons were much larger and clearly stronger though, none of them were there to hide their presence.

‘If I take the long path I’ll have to fight my way through all these demons…’

He felt that this was the way this place was structured. The heroes would probably need to fight their way up to the summit. From down below he could even see a large open balcony at the very top. It seemed to be the last level and probably where the demon king resided.

There were many aerial monsters flapping their wings around this castle. They were there to probably keep the hero party from using any flying artifacts to hasten the journey. Regretfully for the demons, they weren’t dealing with the hero party but a cultivator that had long since mastered the art of flight. A creature that required wigs to maneuver would be quite inferior to something like the flight technique that a nascent soul cultivator used.

‘I guess I’ll be skipping the tutorial…’

Before moving forward he used his connection to Beatrice to look at what was happening on the human side. There he could see the formation that they build working nicely. There didn’t seem that the demons had taken notice of any of this.

‘Beatrice, I will be advancing towards the Demon King’s fortress.’

‘Mr. Leigong… please be careful.’

‘Don’t worry, you just sit tight and don’t worry about anything. Leave this to this Grand Lightning Emperor!’

He could feel that Beatrice was acting strange lately. The closer they got to the endpoint the more gloomy she became. There had to be a proper reason for this but he wasn’t sure. His focus was on the task at hand, after the demon king was defeated they could always have a conversation about it.

‘Okay… let me try this the slow way this time around…’

While ducking behind one of the trees he activated his old disguise technique. His body got larger and lankier and his face and demeanor changed. In a matter of moments, he turned into a certain large vampire that he fought not so long ago. He chose this form as it did possess flight capabilities.

With his new disguise now on he took up into the air and headed towards the large gates. Thanks to it he was able to recreate the original demon’s blood energies. When the lesser demons looked his way they didn’t see anything out of the ordinary, they even bowed after realizing that he was an Archdemon.

He used his flight to get over the massive gate that led towards this giant mountain-high castle. This wasn’t as much of an outlandish sight to him as he came from a world with much larger structures.

Behind this gate, he saw more red demons. Some of them were patrolling around but it didn’t seem that the defenses were taken that seriously. The protective walls didn’t have any lookouts nor any siege weapons. It didn’t seem that these demons were afraid of any counterattacks from the humans.

‘Strange… I expected a welcoming party. Do they not see the people of the races as any kind of threat? or is there something else going on here...’

It felt strange, all of the demon lords have been bested in battle by him but it didn’t look like the devils here cared that much. Most of these monsters looked bored out of their mind, most were even leaning up against walls and sleeping.

‘Does this have something to do with this world being similar to a game?’

If he looked at it from the perspective of this being a game-like world then it did make some sense. Unless the heroes entered the designated area the demons wouldn’t be ‘triggered’ to act. He was perfectly disguised as one of them so they weren't reacting to him much.

He looked up to the large balcony at the very top of this mountain-like castle. While floating up he was again ignored by the flying creatures that were here.

‘If this world is a game… what does that make my own…’

Zhang Dong started to slow mid-flight. The world he was inhabiting had similar issues to this one with the biggest difference being the genre. The people there mostly did act like their counterparts in the novels that he used to read.

Young Masters with no thought for others, their parents not even worried if their offspring offended some old monster that could flatten their whole clan with one snort. A strict power-based structure where the one on top was revered as a god.

While his thoughts were wandering towards these questions the face of his daughter and son appeared before him. His strange stressful feeling washed over his chest and took him over.

‘No… I must focus.’

He shook his head and pushed his concerns to the side. There was no time to have an existential crisis right before attacking the last boss. It was time to end this and go home, his family was waiting for him.

With a burst of speed, he propelled himself up. The other demons still didn’t pay attention so he was able to arrive right at the top. His foot touched the edge of the balcony and he was finally able to see what was behind it.

This balcony took out quite a bit of space, more than a football field. To the side, there seemed to be a staircase that headed down. This was probably how the heroes were supposed to climb up here without the ability to fly.

The ground was made from uniquely shaped slabs of obsidian. There was a certain path laid out before him from slightly lighter slabs pointing him forward. Many huge pillars of hard rock guided his gaze towards the throne composed of bones at the end.

‘Is that the Demon King?’

On this throne composed of human skulls and various other bones sat a man. His legs were spread apart and he had a bored look as he rested his head on his fist. The person sitting on it was fully hidden behind a dark and spiky set of armor. The only thing that made him look alive where the two purple glowing flames coming out of the helmet's eye sockets.

When Zhang Dong’s eyes met with this man he could feel a small amount of pressure but for just a moment. It was similar to his spiritual sense.

“Why have you come here, being from the astral realm?”

A strong demonic voice escaped from this being’s mouth which sent slight shivers down Zhang Dong’s spine. He had hoped his ruse would work for a bit longer until he was able to get closer for a fatal strike.

“I see, it won’t be that easy then…”

He didn’t stop while turning back into his original form. Bright light filled this dark world as his form was revealed. The Demon King that he was seeing before him that seemed bored straightened himself out while also covering his head.

“Wretched light…”

The demon stomped his foot on the ground which caused a strange dark barrier to appear around him. This barrier absorbed all of the holy light that Zhang Dong was giving off and somehow contained it.

“Begone from this world!”

The King let out a burst of demonic energy that headed his way. In retaliation, he did the same with his holy energies. The two opposing forces clashed with each other and canceled themselves out.

‘Beatrice get ready.’

Zhang Dong called out while charging forward, it seemed that this monster was indeed stronger than the Demon Lords he had battled. He knew that his opponent was still hiding some of his capabilities before he got serious he would go straight for the kill.

The Demon King reacted rather quickly. He grasped a large obsidian mace from the side and quickly delivered an attack. Zhang Dong’s sword collided with this mace, golden light washed over the darkness which tried to extinguish it. The two combatants found themselves being forced backward by the ensuing shockwave without a victor.

‘This might actually take a while…’

Zhang Dong looked at his hand that was slightly shaking. Some of the dark energies were wrapping around his sword of light even now.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 322

“So that’s the Demon King? He looks strong…”

A small group of people were looking at a slightly blurry crystal ball. In it, they could see the Demon King dressed in black armor clashing against Zhang Dong’s light sword. They could see the battle from his point of view thanks to this magical device that was created by him.

These people were the group of four heroes that were sitting outside the large formation that was created to fuel Zhang Dong during this fight. The four were left outside in the case that the demons attacked them. Only if Zhang Dong sent a message that he needed more juice would they enter into the formation to give him more.

“He looks like one of those dark knights, but much bigger.”

They could tell that Zhang Dong was much smaller than the person that he was fighting. The mace the monster was holding looked at least two meters in length and the Demon King was easily swinging it around with one hand. Each strike caused the platform the two were fighting to tremble and also caused the video to be quite shaky.

“I hate shaky cam footage…”

One of the girls commented while squinting a bit, it was quite hard to make anything out.

“Sakura please take it more seriously.”

Ami scolded the youngest girl while trying to get her to pay attention.

“Yes, Mr. Matthew is just trying to get us home, thanks to him we were able to get this far.”

Yua the older sister petted Sakura while keeping an eye out for any demons that could have attacked from outside. She was all for leaving this place, the strange people from the royal family were quite pushy and she stopped enjoying their presence after a while.

“Home huh?”

Takeshi placed the crystal ball down while looking out into the fog. He on the other hand was not so sure about going back. Like most young men in his position, he was hesitant to give all this power up. He was finally getting attention from beautiful girls and respect from others that many young men dreamed of.

“You don’t want to go back to your family?”

“Well… I…. I don’t know…”

He replied truthfully as he was not sure what the right choice was. Matthew had disclosed his real name with the group as they all came from a similar or maybe even the same world. He had promised to get them back home but also that he would give them a choice. He told them that he had no right to make the decision for them and that he could see why someone would like to remain in a world like this.

“Wait… what’s that…”

Before a proper conversation could happen Ami saw something.

“There is something coming from the fog… get ready guys!”

The party got their weapons ready. They weren’t the only ones on defensive duty as the ships had been positioned to act as walls. On them, the cannons were all manned by the minimal number of people required.

Soon they saw them, a small army of demonic beasts emerged from the fog and charged in a blind rage towards their encampment. They were greeted by cannon fire and by various magical spells.

“It’s just as he predicted, luckily for us we are prepared!”

Takeshi smirked a bit as he saw one of the monsters stepping in a certain spot. The moment it did its body was engulfed in a large fireball. Zhang Dong had ordered the dwarven craftsmen to place all of their mines around the ships.

“I don’t think they will hold them off for long…”

Ami replied while looking at all of the explosions that were happening everywhere. That was the problem, the monsters didn’t seem to halt their advance. When one of them exploded two others took their place and charged as if they were in a berserked state.

“Damn how many are there…”

Takeshi flinched a bit as due to the thick fog that was still there they couldn’t really tell how many of these demons there were. They could only wait and try to last through this wave while not allowing them to touch the magic formation.

The four heroes jumped into the fray themselves soon after. The monster hordes seemed endless but it was their task to defend the people fueling Zhang Dong. If the monsters were allowed inside they would easily massacre the people that were put in a trance-like state.

“Wretched cur, tremble before my might!”

“You guys sure like to stick to your script, don’t you?”

Zhang Dong dodged to the side as the Demon King swung his mace. The mace that connected with the obsidian slabs on the balcony trembled but somehow resisted it.

The two had been fighting for a few minutes and Zhang Dong was trying to feel out his opponent. He was glad that he decided to leave the girls out of this as this monster was far stronger than he anticipated, quite close to the nascent soul level of power.

‘Close… but not close enough that is…’

After his evasive maneuver was successful he saw his chance to strike. His body turned into a streak of golden lightning that appeared to the side of this armor-wearing monster.

Zhang Dong’s fist was surrounded by an aura of golden plasma and it lodged itself into the Demon King’s side. A sound of bent metal was heard by him as his fist connected with his opponent.

The Demon King was sent flying to the side after the well-placed liver shot. His armor in the spot started to crumble apart while the holy energies invaded the unprotected insides. Like many times before his holy energies proved the bane of any demonic being. Even this Demon King wasn’t immune to this Dao that he had enhanced with the soul cultivation.

“Arghhhh.”

The monster cried out in pain as it slammed into one of the giant pillars that were placed on this very balcony. This wasn’t the end for it though as this seemed to anger this monster more than cause damage.

The dark armor began rearranging itself into place as a dark aura covered Zhang Dong’s opponent. It looked like no damage had been done to the monster but he knew otherwise.

His holy energies were now causing widespread chaos inside of his opponent's body. The only way to get rid of them was using up a lot of saved up mana. This was the real truth when fighting opponents with regenerative capabilities.

These types of powers always put a strain on the body and would not last forever. The biggest problem was just how much reserve mana this Demon Lord had. He himself was running on borrowed time, the longer this battle lasted the less energy Beatrice and her helpers would send to him. Thus each hit had to count.

Head, heart, solar plexus, the liver, and even the genitals. He aimed for all the critical locations that a humanoid body would have. Punch after punch rained down on his opponent that sent him crashing into more of those large pillars. After a certain point, he could tell that the monster was having a hard time healing its wounds.

With each hit, its four-meter large demon body started to shrink. It looked to not be able to sustain its full-powered form anymore, shrinking as it conserved energy.

Zhang Dong didn’t really use any flashy moves this time around. It was a slow grind and methodical beat down that caused slow long-lasting damage that piled up on top of each other. Only when the chance presented itself did he go for the last hit.

“Let us end this, hand over that cube.”

He put both of his hands together while producing a blade of light. This blade of light was quite condensed and had an actual sharp edge to it. With the help of his swordsmanship that was backed by his sword heart, he sliced forward.

The hit came almost instantaneous without giving the Demon King much time to react. The whole place rumbled as along with the demon’s head the tip of the castle-like mountain was cleaved.

‘Was that really it?’

As the tip of the castle was sliding down to the ground and making a lot of noise, he approached the monster’s body. He had severed this being’s clean off and the moment he did he could feel its demonic soul start to dissipate. While approaching he could still feel it trying to heal itself but soon even the body started to turn into dust.

As he got closer he could see the demon’s body shrinking in size. Its armor was the first to crumble away into particles of dust. He was aware of how these things worked out, thus he kept a fighting stance while looking around. Mostly at this time, the demon would go into his second more powerful form or the actual real last boss popped out from the side.

But even though he waited and waited nothing seemed to change. The whole body of the demon crumbled into dust while leaving his armored helmet behind. It was a bit strange that the body withered away before this head but soon it was its turn to disintegrate.

‘Is the cube in the head?’

A certain energy signature started coming off from the head. He could feel that the last nuclei was there and it was indeed resting in the demon king's severed head. Zhang Dong had also checked his map previously and he couldn’t see any dark spots that were hiding anything away. This seemed to be it, the last part of the puzzle that would allow him to return home.

“Huh… why does he have that guy's face.”

The metallic helmet finally evaporated into dust and revealed the face under it. It was of a three-eyed monster with a tint of red to its skin. This wasn’t the odd part, its face was similar to a person that he had met before. It was someone from the human side who caused Zhang Dong to space out for a moment.

Due to this little blunder, he was unable to react in time to what happened next. The head exploded revealing a large crimson crystal that was a lot larger than the ones that the demon lords had. This crystal shot off into the distance almost instantly when it was revealed and headed towards the barrier between the two continents.

“Shit…”

He snapped out of it and gave chase, the crystal went right through the thick obsidian plates of that balcony it was on. Almost instantly after this the whole castle began to shake and crumble as if this crystal was keeping it together.

‘It’s going towards the opening I came from…’

The flying monsters reacted to him wheezing by in his human form and gave chase. Luckily they were limited in their speed and started trailing behind. He wasn’t really able to contact the people outside as Beatrice and Isabella that he was connected with were still in the soul resonance trance.

“Get back here!”

While inserting more energy into his flight technique he bolted forward. The monsters behind him started to trail behind even more and he wasn’t even looking at the demon’s castle crumbling away into nothingness.

Almost instantly he and the crimson gem collided with the thin exit to the other side. The crystal stopped for a moment but in a matter of seconds, it managed to pierce its way to the other side. He as well collided with this opening and had to force his way to the other side yet he did it much faster than this gem.

When outside he reached his hand out, the red demonic crystal was right there. After going through the opening it lost some of its momentum. This was the best time to grab it so he propelled himself forward.

His fingertips touched the crystal and he was quick to start the absorption process but then it happened. He felt some kind of sharp pain. It was as if a thousand tiny needles were being pierced into his heart at the same time. This caused him to flinch while the partially absorbed crystal sped away into the distance.

“W-what…”

He instantly clenched his chest while looking to the side, there he saw it. A large man, his face covered in scars and wearing the Duke of Hohenberg crest. His hand was holding a long sword, this sword pierced through the chest of a golden haired girl...

Chapter 323

An older man with a somewhat gray beard and scars all over his face was glancing over to a pillar of light. He could see two young girls holding hands together with their eyes closed.

He turned to the other side, there explosions and sounds of monsters being killed greeted him. The whole place was a warzone with many lesser demons trying to get to them. Everyone was busy with the fight so he was sure that no one would block his way towards his mission.

The man’s armor had the crest of the Hohenberg of Dragonridge noble house. He continued advancing while thinking about what he was about to do. His feet stopped directly before the golden light that signaled the beginning of this magical formation.

The man had observed other people entering this circle and after a short time, they would succumb to it, becoming nothing more than batteries. He knew that he didn’t have much time but with his skills, he knew that it was possible.

“Please forgive me but this is all for the house's future!”

From his side, he pulled out a somewhat strange-looking lacerated dagger. Its shape was unusually bent and it gave off an eerie light. The spirit was on the inside, battling with the demons and that is where it would remain.

His instructions were clear, kill the girl when the possibility presented itself. The old man didn’t believe that this demon king hunting plan had any merit. Leigong would be trapped in the demonic realm and the five demon lords were gone, there was no reason to fight anymore. The only thing important was that the kingdom remains peaceful and that his noble house survives.

He took a step towards the magical circle that was not made to repel humans. After the first step forward he began his charge. This was all done while being unaware of the red crystal that flew through the previously closed opening to the demonic continent.

The familiar feeling of flesh being pierced filled his hands as he delivered the killing blow. The girl before him didn’t even know what had happened. Her body slowly slumped forward against the lady that this man was sworn to protect.

“It is done…”

“What did you do!?”

The old man turned to the voice, there a maddened Leigong was seen charging. Before he could react two hands grasped his head and lifted him up. He could feel massive amounts of energy getting injected into his body that instantly went limp.

His body lit up like a Christmas tree and his screams filled the air. His hands and legs promptly exploded into chunks of charred meat before he was tossed to the side like a puppet with its strings being cut.

“Beatrice…No...”

Zhang Dong acted fast, after taking care of the old man he started injecting his healing energies into Beatrice’s body. The dagger was pushed outside while he was able to mend her heart back into shape. His advanced cultivation level at this moment allowed for him to use more advanced techniques but even then there was something off.

“Something is wrong… her body is healed… but her soul is crumbling apart…”

It was a bizarre thing, normally a soul would not receive direct damage or crumble before the body fully gave out. He reacted fast so the damage was minimized, the blood flow returned to normal but for some reason, the girl was not waking up.

“B-beatrice? W-what’s going on?”

Due to Beatrice being taken out of the grand formation, Isabella also found herself regaining her senses.

“I don’t know… we were betrayed by one of your men…”

Zhang Dong glanced to the side, the man that he roasted was close to being dead. His body was almost all black.

“Why would you do such a thing…”

“I…. I did it for the… l-long live house Hohenberg of D-dragonrige…”

Zhang Dong gritted his teeth. While pointing with his finger at the dying man.

“What did you do to her, what is this dagger! Answer me!”

“It’s too late… it’s the soul slaying dagger… p-please forgive me lady Isabella…”

Isabella looked down at the bloody dagger on the ground and picked it up before speaking out herself.

“N-no… this dagger belongs to my father… it can kill a summoner and cut their connection to their summoned beast instantly… it was purposely made to kill summoners…”

“Cut the connection?... is that why…”

Zhang Dong could feel it, he was being pulled away into his soul dimension. He was losing his connection to this world and even Bob his AI was raising an alarm.

There was also the problem of the demonic beings surrounding the whole encampment from all sides. He was somehow maintaining his form thanks to this formation but his power was being diminished. If he didn’t mend Beatrice’s soul before it faded away, he would be forced to leave this realm. He would be fine in his soul dimension that was between the worlds.

‘I need to mend her soul but…’

Zhang Dong had a lot more knowledge of how souls worked now but it might not be enough in this situation.

“Bob… can I mend Beatrice’s soul with my own…”

His first idea was to lend her a part of his own overground nascent soul. His cultivation level would regress slightly but this would be something that he was willing to do.

“The probability is… 0%... the user's soul is not compatible with the souls of the residents of this world. “

This was something that he was aware of, even if he wanted his soul that was being rejected by this world was no good. Souls were also different, even close family members would mostly not be compatible with each other.

‘There is only one person here with a comparable soul to Beatrice’s but…’

He looked to Isabella who was crying. Beatrice was surrounded by a thin layer of golden light that was slowing down the decaying process of the soul slaying dagger. There was a possibility of healing when he used Isabella but there were also huge risks. He would be risking her life in the process that would probably shorten both of their life spans.

“Please Lord Leigong, save Beatrice! There must be a way!”

“I…”

Zhang Dong hesitated, he knew that these two were close friends, maybe even more than that. He knew that if he proposed the healing procedure that the young girl would instantly agree.

Before any decisions could be made, something else occurred.

“Bravo…”

A sound of clapping echoed through the whole battlefield. The group of defenders and heroes that were fighting the swarms of monsters was surprised by a strange occurrence.

The monsters stopped in their tracks and started backing off while the fog dissipated. The loud sound of clapping then intensified and brought all eyes to a certain man. He was floating up in the sky, this was someone that a lot of people here knew well while others to a lesser extent.

“You...”

Zhang Dong looked up to the man that was floating their way. He had met this man before and even then he never liked him.

“Father came to save us all!”

Ludwig the prince cheered while holding a bloody sword up that was covered with black monster blood.

“The king? What is he doing here?”

Takeshi and the others weren’t as ecstatic to see this person arrive. There was something strange going on, the man was just slowly floating forward with a strange crimson gem right next to him. The monsters were also parting to allow this man to land on a spot in front of the makeshift base that was created for the defense.

“Father? Ah yes, I guess this shell is your father.”

“Get away from him, that’s not the human king, it’s the true Demon King.”

Zhang Dong called out from the distance while glaring at the person from afar. He knew this fact after battling the Demon King on the demonic continent side. The face that the monster had was strangely similar to the one that this king was wearing. It was clear to him that the Demon King that he faced was some kind of clone and the real one had already been living among the humans.

This was clearly some farce, all of the demon lords could have easily invaded the human lands and taken them over. There was no way that the people of the races would be able to resist them. Not when the supposed strongest person in the lands was actually the Demon King in disguise.

“The Demon King? How is that possible?”

“Demon King? No, the Demon King died by the traveler’s hand already, I’m something else entirely.”

While saying this the ‘King’ looked to the crimson gem that was floating next to him. The stone started moving towards his hand and slowly entered his body through it.

“Stay with Beatrice, I’ll handle this.”

Zhang Dong floated up into the sky and towards this new foe that he was not familiar with. The man that was supposed to be the king was acting off-script.

“Did you call me the traveler?”

“Ah yes you, why are you still here? You got what you wanted, you don’t need to be here, no?”

The two looked at each other from afar. Zhang Dong was taken aback by the words that were spoken.

“The traveler?”

“Yes, traveler. Why are you still here, there is nothing more for you to gain. Do you wish to receive the last nucleus? You don’t need it to leave this world, you should have enough.”

The king continued to speak as if he knew who Zhang Dong was and what his main purpose was. He wasn’t wrong, with the current cubes that he had absorbed he would be able to go home. This would only be possible if he didn’t send Takeshi and the three girls home though. Without the last nuclei that this fake king had absorbed he would need to utilize the one that he received after the dungeon collapsed.

“You look surprised. I thought you knew more but it seems that you don’t…”

“Shut it! We don’t have time for this, call back those demons. We don’t have time for this.”

He looked from the corner of his eye to where Beatrice was. Isabella was still crying and holding her hand while he was slowly losing his connection to this world. His power wasn’t decreasing as much but if Beatrice’s soul faded away he would just disappear from this planet altogether.

“Oh? So it wasn’t an act? Do you really care for these creations? Why would someone that managed to escape the system have feelings for these things? Are you still not aware?”

“Shut up, what are you even talking about? Call back those monsters and give me the nucleus! I don’t have time for this”

Zhang Dong’s face contorted into rage as he approached the true Demon King. There was no time, he needed to act. If he defeated this person then surely he would receive the cube.

“This won’t do, you have broken the cycle. The world needs to be reset, I am unable to go against the system, everything must return to zero...”

The king proclaimed while his body began to turn crimson. His body started expanding and he revealed his true form, one battle was over but the next one was upon him...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 324

The human was no more, it was replaced by a shadowy figure that was ever-expanding. Ten...twenty...fifty… the ground rumbled as the many monstrous creatures flew towards the darkness within.

The mirror-like barrier that protected people from the demonic continent started to break. Many thin spider-like web cracks appeared before everything shattered into pieces.

People gathered here gasped out of fright but instead of an army of demons attacking them a massive surge of demonic energy flew towards the growing demon king. In this dark light, Zhang Dong could see many of the creatures that he had seen before.

‘He is absorbing all of the demons from the demon side?’

Everyone backed away, stunned by what they were seeing. The human king that was the strongest man alive was the actual Demon King and now he was revealing his true form.

His children were here, they all dropped down to their knees with their eyes looking at the creature that was their father. Was he a demon from the beginning or did he replace him through the years? While the royal family members were having an identity crisis their father’s form started taking shape.

Before Zhang Dong and everyone else stood a giant being. It was similar looking to some of the previous archdemons. Its body was darkish red and he had quite a bulky humanoid-shaped demonic body.

Around the forehead area, there were many protruding horns that surrounded a crown made of flames. Its face was truly demonic and the usual three eyes that the demons from this world had were there. From its spine and shoulders, massive spikes were expanding, and where its abdomen should be there was a secondary face with quite the toothy mouth.

It was quite gigantic with hooved legs and a long spikey tail. The moment its transformation was complete a certain lack of any other demonic being could be seen. This monster somehow absorbed all of the demonic energies from this place along with any demons that were here.

“The cycle was broken but the cycle must continue!”

The demon roared while everyone grasped their heads. Everyone was forced to the ground with the exception of Zhang Dong. He could tell that this was some kind of strange attack that only affected the people from this world which he was not a part of.

“Damn, what is that bastard even talking about… what cycle?”

Zhang Dong grasped the air with his hand and a golden bolt of lightning appeared in it. After a short charge-up he chucked it towards this demonic being. The spear of light made a beautiful arc and headed right towards the massive creature’s head. Before it could connect it collided with some kind of dark barrier of flames which it couldn’t pass through.

“What?”

Zhang Dong saw the holy energies being erased by this barrier and the demon not suffering any kind of damage. He could still feel that this was a demon being like all the rest of them before it. It was just many times stronger than them, even than the early stage of nascent soul that he was in at the moment.

The monster didn’t even flinch but before it advanced forward a large amount of magical energy headed its way.

“Don’t forget about us!”

Takeshi shouted out while all the other people with ranged capabilities throughout various of their attacks at the large monster. The golems used large cannons, the elven mages combined their mana to form a large lance of pure magical energy, and even the people that were in the taken apart ships used their weapons to fire away.

The large monster’s whole frame became bathed in fire and explosions. Even though it was so huge its whole body became covered by all of this magical and technological energy.

Zhang Dong didn’t just remain in place either. He noticed that this monster wasn’t taking a step forward but neither was it backing off. It was clearly showing off like every evil enemy that thought that they were superior. This critical lapse in judgment was something that these boss-like monsters had and he would use it to his advantage.

“Takeshi, lend me your sword!”

In a flash of lightning, he appeared next to the hero that was performing some ranged slashes with his sword. Even before the young man could reply his sword was snatched away by Zhang Dong that quickly flew towards his enemy.

This was the strongest weapon that he could use and even though it wasn’t quite of the heaven grade it would have to do. Zhang Dong’s strongest attacks applied to swordsmanship, with his power fading fast this would need to do.

Together with his sword heart, he put everything he had into his swordsmanship skills. He grasped this longsword with both his hands and pushed all of his soul into it. He needed to destroy this demon down to his very being, damaging its body would not be enough.

Zhang Dong’s body glowed once more but the glow soon faded as the golden light shifted towards the hero’s sword in his hand. He pushed it up, holding it above his head. The light that he produced pierced the clouds above and revealed the shining star that lit up this planet.

“Sever…”

The demonic being suddenly moved its hand but it was too late at that point. Zhang Dong cleaved forward, both his hands moved down in a clean slicing movement. The moment the sword was pointing down the attack had gone through and it shattered into many tiny pieces, unable to last through the massive amounts of energy he was pushing into it.

The explosions that were covering the creature's body were pushed to the side. It was a clean cleave through the middle of the monster’s body. It was a clean hit that managed to pierce through the demon’s defenses and even its large hand that he threw forward to defend itself.

Earth parted beneath the monster and a giant fissure that went on for kilometers was created in the wake of this attack that Zhang Dong put all of his power behind. A massive shockwave tossed everything to the side of this parting earth as the ground rumbled. The earthquake could be felt by anyone on this continent and even reached up to the elven island.

Silence ensued as the monster's body started parting. It was a clean-cut that produced two symmetrical parts that were now opening up. While these two sides continued to part, Zhang Dong could see a large crystal inside, it was even bigger than the one that he received from the fake demon king.

“I...is it over?”

People stared at the monster and as it continued to part. It seemed that the monster had been dealt a critical blow but it wasn’t so.

“The crystal…”

Zhang Dong eyed that corrupt gem and quickly flew towards it. There was something wrong, even though the monster was falling apart before his eyes this gem had not been sliced by his attack.

“I have to commend you on your perseverance, traveler.”

A voice escaped from this gem and it sounded like the late human king. In a flash of light, the gem radiated power, a power through which Zhang Dong was sent flying backward from where he came from.

“Alas, you don’t belong to this world anymore. Your connection to it has been cut, you can not harm this body!”

The red gem began giving out dark red light. Many strange dark tentacle-like whips shoot out from all directions. They embedded themselves into the large red demon's body and quickly started pulling it back together.

At this time Zhang Dong’s body collided with the ground and he started bouncing like a ball. When the dust was cleared he found himself in the middle of the encampment, almost at the same spot from where he took off.

‘What the hell, that should have been enough to kill it...do I need to be connected to a summoner to harm it?’

He wasn’t sure what this was about but for some reason, this world would not allow him to kill this being. It seemed that only a person that was directly born in it would be able to achieve this feat.

‘Is this some countermeasure about people from other worlds?’

If this theory was true, then even if the Hero party got strong enough they would not be able to kill this monster. Maybe that’s how this whole thing worked, the demon king would just play dead and regenerate itself later to play this game once more.

It would lie dormant in the background allowing the heroes to win only to return later to do the same. For what reason this cycle of demons vs heroes continued was still unknown to him. One thing was clear, this demon here was not playing around anymore. The farce was up so now it needed to eliminate everyone that saw through its scheme.

While the red gem was pulling back the body together everyone else resumed their attacks. Even though they were connected no damage was being done. This was obvious as the monster was clearly something that was at the nascent soul level and close to its maximum.

‘What should I do… what can I do?’

Zhang Dong looked tired standing up but the moment his foot had to support some weight it crumbled into tiny mana particles. He fell forward on his face and he finally noticed it, his body was fading away. The energy that he was left with had run out, soon he would fade away and be forced back into the soul dimension.

There was no real danger that he himself was in. He had enough energy to flee this world and this demon here would probably be unable to follow him to the space between worlds that he resided in.

He needed to make a decision as well, due to him losing his connection to Beatrice he would need to leave immediately. That would mean that he would need to leave everyone here to die. There was no time to send the four kids back to Earth, nor could he save anyone here with no energy left. Making another contract with someone else would also not give him enough power to defeat this demon.

“Leigong… please...I’ll do anything… just bring her back…”

Zhang Dong snapped out of it and looked up. There Isabella was holding Beatrice in her hands and still crying. The girl had not moved from the spot at all and remained by the side of her close friend.

“Bring her back?...”

There was a way to do this, but it was a gamble. He was not sure what would happen if he fused these girls souls together but at this point, there might have been no other choice.

While crawling towards Isabella with his upper torso still in place he thought back to how things played themselves out. He had made many mistakes, he was hasty, he didn’t think things through and how they would affect these youths. There were several things he could have done to prepare but he chose his family over the people in this world and now these two girls would have to pay for it.

“There is a way Isabella but…”

“I don’t care, just bring her back!”

Zhang Dong nodded while giving out a sigh, the reply came fast and without any hesitation. He could only answer this resolution by reaching out with his hand towards Beatrie’s forehead and touching it with his index finger...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 325

“Cold...everything...so...cold…”

A naked girl was floating around in a dark place. She was curled up in a ball as she tried to conserve the warmth but the more time passed the colder it became.

“D-did we do it? Are Isabella and Mr. Leigong okay?”

….

Beatrice remembered a haughty spirit that she met. He was sometimes overbearing while other times quite peculiar and hard to get along with. There was a certain light radiating from him, she knew this as their souls were connected with each other.

Then there was her new friend, a girl that she used to envy. Somehow the two were connected thanks to this odd spirit. Along their travels, the dislike turned into a friendship that she thought could last forever.

This only increased her anxiety, she knew that this wouldn’t last. Her spirit was pushing them forward and she knew why he wanted to leave. At the end of this journey, the only thing that was connecting her to the new friend would go away. She would lose two of the people that could be relied on.

She didn’t make it seem obvious and the spirit never asked about it. The world was relying on them so she pushed her selfish thoughts to the back of her mind. If everyone else was happy that would be enough, she was used to it.

“Leigong? Isabella? Who are they? I don’t remember… I just want to sleep… It’s cold…”

Soon the old memories started fading away, even when she tried to remember they weren’t coming back. The bright light that was brought into her life started fading away and she started losing herself in this void.

….

….

“There you are…”

A voice called out to her, it belonged to a man but who was he. She felt like this was someone that was close to her but she couldn’t recall. The girl could barely open up her eyes but when she did a radiant golden light filled her blurry vision.

“I’m sorry that I’ve made you wait... “

She could feel sadness coming from this voice. The light continued to get closer and soon she felt warmth returning to her body once more.

“Are you ready?”
“Yes.”

She could hear another voice that belonged to a girl. This voice was also very familiar even more than the one that belonged to the man.

Then she felt it, someone was right next to her. The girl opened up her eyes and saw a bright smile before her. A smile that she was very familiar with, it was her friend that was dear to her.

“Isabella?”

“Yes, don’t worry, you’re not alone…”

Zhang Dong looked at the two young souls before him. They were floating between his palms, he could feel that Beatrice was regaining her lost memories thanks to being in close proximity to someone that she resonated with. This wouldn’t last for long so he needed to act fast.

“I need to start… please forgive me.”

“It’s okay Mr. Leigong.”

Isabella replied while looking up to the giant made of lightning energy before her. The giant hands that were hovering between them moved together. Soon a strange feeling washed over both of the girls as everything faded to white.

Zhang Dong looked down at his hands, in his left he was holding a small wisp of light that was slowly fading away. In his right, he could see a much larger orb that was radiating warmth.

He slowly brought these two lights together while focusing. The larger ball of light that constituted Isabella in soul form slowly made contact with Beatrice’s fading one. Soon the two light sources started to intertwine while the corruption subsided.

The darkness that was dimming Beatrice's soul started fusing itself with Isabella’s. It looked like a yin and yang symbol that was battling for supremacy. The darkness was trying to push its way towards the light that was defending itself from the corruption.

This was the time to act, he used his own energies to attack this corruption by strengthening Isabella’s soul. He couldn’t overcharge it as too much would burst poor Beatrice’s soul like a soap bubble. The corruption needed to be slowly filtered out while the other soul mended itself back.

The process was working but it was slow. On the outside things looked bleak. Zhang Dong’s body had mostly evaporated into mana particles and only part of his arm remained. It hovered with its finger outstretched and still poking Isabella’s forehead.

In the background, the bombardment continued but the first casualties of this expedition started to arise. The true Demon King had reformed itself and with a swipe of its large hand, it destroyed one of the flying ships that was used as a barricade. The soldiers that were manning the cannons and flinging the spells at this creature didn’t even have time to react before they were engulfed in dark-colored hellfire.

Some were lucky enough to be close to some of the stronger combatants like the group of four heroes or the two elven mages that came along for this trip. Even then, all these people could do was defend themselves for a short period of time. Everyone retreated to the grand formation that had been broken already.

“There is nowhere to run, the cycle has been broken, all of you have to perish.”

The monster proclaimed while the large toothy mouth that was at his abdomen area opened up. Dark flames and heretic energies along with miasma were discharged into the surroundings burning everything to ash. No one was safe, human, beast, or even insects; they would all need to be cleansed in this demonic fire so that the cycle could begin anew.

The survivors gathered looked up to the behemoth. This really seemed like it was the end but before the dark flames could singe the remaining people a pillar of light shot up into the sky. Dark demonic flames collided with this light, the two forces surprisingly repelled each other with the light managing to hold its own.

This didn’t stop the demon from charging up a second attack, it leaned back and opened up both of its mouths. While holding its hands outstretched a mass of demonic energy formed in front of its body. It was spherical in shape and looked like a miniaturized sun made from dark flames.

“Perish within the cleansing flames, let everything return to the beginning.”

As the demon lord was speaking he moved this dark sun up and over his head. It continued to expand into massive proportions and ready to singe this world into nothing but ash. The people of the races could only go down to their knees while looking at the massive ball of energy.

Then from within the small pillar of light that had blocked the previous attack a man in a white robe emerged. His form was familiar to everyone here yet in his eyes there was a certain sadness.

He pointed with his finger towards the large dark ball of flames. Right in front of him, a large magic circle appeared on it, with many runic symbols and strange writing. This magical circle expanded into a certain size before it split up into another one in front of it.

These magical spheres continued to pop up right in front of each other while pointing at the demon and the miniature star it was holding. It didn’t look like the demon was agitated in any shape or form by this display of magic as it continued with its own technique.

Finally, with a loud roar, it threw this massive globe of demonic energy down on the people below it. Almost at the same moment, Zhang Dong looked up, from within his fingertip a tiny bubble of white energy emerged.

It was the size of a marble and moved rather sluggish towards the large descending ball of energy. Then when it seemed that Zhang Dong’s spell was a fluke it touched the large magic circle in front of it. In a flash of light, this circle churned with power as it activated its effect.

The tiny bead of light shot forward and dramatically expanded in size. It turned into a beam of white light that continued to increase in thickness each time it passed through another of the previously produced magic circles.

In a fraction of a second, it matched the gigantic demonic sphere of energy and collided with it. To everyone's surprise, the Demon King’s attack halted in its descent. A battle of two repelling energies commenced once again as the earth rumbled down below.

“Grab my hand!”

Takeshi called out to Ami as he held up a shield to protect the survivors. The party of heroes gave it all along with the elven ladies they produced the best shielding magics that they could.

Darkness and Light collided with each other and for a moment it looked like the dark sun would engulf the earth. But with a burst of energy, the magical circles began to turn. They span around while crackling with golden lightning energy.

The beam of white light expanded in size and into a cone shape outwardly. It engulfed the star of doom that was descending onto the survivors and started to push it back.

“How could this be… you should not have this much power…”

The demonic voice of the Demon King sounded out as it tried adding more of its black flames to his powerful attack. It didn’t seem like it was much use as he was pushed back. The golden beam of light shot up into the stratosphere while also erasing this demon's most powerful attack.

“You had your fun, but this is the end…”

Zhang Dong appeared next to the large monster that only noticed that he was hovering in front of it the moment he got there. He was now directly looking at the massive jaws of the demon’s second mouth.

The Demon King opened his gullet wide and quickly chomped towards the small being in front of it. The sword-length teeth descended onto its prey as the mouth closed around Zhang Dong’s body.

“Foolish traveler you could have left this place but now…. ugh?”

While being assured of its victory the Demon King grinned but suddenly a strange feeling washed over his body. He could feel something moving inside of him.

A large opening in the back of this demon was created as Zhang Dong shot out. He was surrounded by his holy energies and looked slightly injured with clothes cut up.

“W-what did you…”

“Nothing, I just took your power source...”

In Zhang Dong’s hand was a large darkened gem. It was radiating strange energies but soon it started to diminish in size while revealing its true form, a cube.

“I-impossible…”

Without its source of energy, the large demon started faltering. Like a deflated balloon it started to shrink down in size all the way till it was the size of the human king.

Still alive the Demon King attempted to flee but before he could even flinch a torrent of golden light descended onto his body. It singed him to ashes rather quickly while Zhang Dong watched on with vacant eyes.

‘It’s finally over… but at what cost…’

Zhang Dong looked to the cube in his hand and then glanced behind him. There, Beatrice and Isabella were on the ground, both collapsed while holding hands.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 326

“Ahh….huh?”

The young girl opened up her eyes only to see the white ceiling above her. She still felt a bit drowsy and had trouble keeping her eyes open. She tried to move but her body was quite stiff and weak.

“Ugh… what is this?”

After managing to raise her top half from the bed she noticed something. She felt that something was tugging on her left arm. When she saw a strange golden chain of some sorts was there and it was attached to someone.

“Isabella?”

Beatrice moved her hand up slowly, the chain was only a meter long so Isabella’s hand was pulled up as well.

“Mmm?”

The other blond girl gave out a little grunt before she started to wake up.

“B-beatrice?”

Isabella felt almost exactly the same as her friend that was to her right side. Both of them were now in some kind of large and expensive-looking room. Both of them were wearing white pajamas that looked the same.

“Beatrice!”

Before the young girl could ask Isabella about what had happened she found herself being hugged. Both of them almost tumbled down the bed together after the quick attack.

Isabella started crying while Beatrice just continued to pet her head without really knowing what was going on. It seemed that the battle was over but she couldn’t recall how. The last thing she remembered was Zhang Dong fighting the Demon Lord, then everything went blank and she woke up here.

“Isabella… you’re choking me…”

“Ah excuse me…”

“What happened… what is this chain?”

Beatrice looked at her friend that’s face was all red. But when she mentioned the chain that was attached to their wrists Isabella didn’t really have an answer for it. Luckily for them, a certain person quickly appeared to answer this question.

“Good, you two are finally awake.”

A normal-sized Zhang Dong materialized out of thin air and appeared before the two girls.

“Mr. Leigong! Did we win?”

That was what Beatrice asked while also trying to get out of bed. The moment she did though a strange sharp pain appeared in her chest area which made her lean forward.

“Beatrice!?”

Isabella called out worried.

“Try not to move, your body isn’t fully healed… I’ll need to explain a couple of things to you two…”

Just like Beatrice, Isabella was knocked out during the process of soul merging that Zhang Dong performed on the two. After he managed to fuse both of their souls together his power level skyrocketed, it even reached a new height. Thanks to this he could take out that presence which was later given the name 'watcher' by Bob his AI assistant.

This was achieved after absorbing the last nucleus. The name was a dead giveaway, this person was here to watch over this world. If the people called Overseers were more akin to admins then this watcher could be something like a moderator. His power was above what the people were capable of.

From the conversation, it looked like this watcher was not supposed to act. Zhang Dong forced his hand after beating the false Demon Lord and doing it himself instead of the heroes. The balance was broken and he even absorbed all of the nuclei himself to gain more energy and information.

He did pose Bob this question, it seemed strange that the Overseers didn’t become suspicious. His AI reassured him that the signal was blocked due to his system being severed from the source. He was a person that was now outside of it while also being able to use some of its features to his advantage.

“So I died?”

“I’m sorry Beatrice it was due to my father…”

Zhang Dong started off by informing Beatrice about the initial stabbing. The wound from it wasn’t fully healed and it would take some time for the girl to make a full recovery.

“It’s not Isabella’s fault, it was probably just a ruse! Right, Mr. Leigong?”

Beatrice wasn’t mad at her friend, it looked that from her standpoint the one at fault was the man and not the noble house he was attached to.

“... Regretfully, it was something ordered by Isabella’s father… but the real culprit was the king…”

Zhang Dong looked mad when talking about the man that almost killed Beatrice. In his eyes, both he and the Duke were equally guilty of this deed. He knew that the king had given the order and also that there was more at stake than one girl’s life if he refused the order. Even then, he felt disgusted even thinking about it.

“Father…where”

“Your father? For now, he is in the dungeon, I’ve put him there, he already confessed. About this and other things...”

Zhang Dong looked to the shocked girls that probably didn’t know what to think. The Duke had also been responsible for killing Beatrice’s grandfather and with the things being like this he could be sentenced to death.

“Dungeon? W-what happened?”

“First let me talk about the condition you two are in, I’m sure that you’ve noticed the chain and armbands…”

The two nodded while pulling on the chain gently. It looked to have been made with some precious metals and there was a small lock on each armband. The chains radiated some magical power while also being covered in strange runic symbols that the girls weren’t very knowledgeable about.

“I had to merge your souls together… The soul slaying dagger’s effect proved too much for my healing capabilities. The merging process was successful but there were certain drawbacks.”

“What kind of drawbacks? Will we be okay?”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh while also moving over to the large king-sized bed.

“I won’t lie to you, I’m not certain myself. I fear that your lifespans have been lowered, by how much I don’t know…”

This was somewhat a lie as Zhang Dong knew that their lives were halved. Due to the corruption, Beatrice’s soul had to be strengthened by Isabella’s. The drawback was that the other girl’s own soul was diminished and shrunk down in size.

What was left were two souls that could not function correctly if they weren’t in close proximity. He wasn’t sure if the process was reversible, there was a small chance that with time the souls could return to their previous size. There were no cases like this recorded in any books and he also lacked the knowledge himself.

“Ah…”

The two girls reacted in silence at the mention of their lives being shortened.

“It’s all because of me… if not for me Isabella’s life wouldn’t have been shortened…”

“What are you talking about?”

“But…”

“Don’t be an idiot, it's natural for a friend to help their friend! I would have gladly done it again!”

Isabella smiled at Beatrice but then the two were brought back to reality due to the uncomfortable chain.

“This chain though…”

“Yes, you’ll have to wear it for now. Your souls have shrunk down and normally they would have ceased to be. Luckily for you, your souls are very similar so they compliment each other. As long as you remain close, you will be fine."

This was the reason for the chain being there. With time the distance would increase but Zhang Dong didn’t know if the two would ever be able to live apart from each other.

“I’m sorry if I didn’t rush this…”

He dropped his head down while looking at the two girls. The blame was on him, at least that is what he felt. Due to his situation, he was more concerned about returning to his own world than with his new partners. They were all forced to hastily push through all the dangers with a half-assed plan.

If he thought things through more, waited for the heroes to get stronger this might have never happened in the first place. At least the assassination could have been averted but now the two would be stuck together and live shorter lives.

“What are you talking about Mr. Leigong?”

“Huh?”

Zhang Dong looked at Beatrice that was shaking her head and actually smiling.

“You saved us all, didn’t you? No one else will have to get hurt now and the demon lords are no more. Isn’t that right?”

Beatrice proclaimed while looking at Isabella.

“That’s right, it's unbecoming of a Great Lightning Emperor to sulk! Everyone knew that there would be consequences, we can’t ask for more of you!”

He expected the two to cry, he even expected them to blame him or plea for help. Instead, they acted like mature adults and could see the bigger picture.

If you looked at it from the outside the expedition was a big success. All of the demonic lords had been killed and the true demon king was also dead. The king that controlled the lands from the shadows was revealed and the barrier to a whole new continent was also open.

For the common people, this was the time to rejoice. For thousands of years, they lived in fear of the demon invasion, never knowing if the barrier would fall one day. Now on the other hand they were finally free, it was time for them to reclaim this world for themselves.

“Is that so… think you two might have matured more than me…”

Zhang Dong raised his head while moving over and placing his hand on Beatrice’s head. His connection to this world was now even stronger than before. The unification of these two souls was boosting his powers.

“You should rest now, I’ll have the servants prepare some food, then we will have to talk about the future…”

After some pleasantries he left the room, leaving the two girls alone to talk things out. They didn’t seem that depressed by the fact that they would need to remain close to each other. He could even feel Isabella’s joy the moment he explained what the chain was for.

“Bob, how are those calculations going?”

“94%...”

“Good…”

The time was almost here, Bob was doing the last bit of calculations for his world travel. What was left to do was to create the magical formation through which he could send the heroes home. The same portal would also be used by him to leave this place but before that, there were some loose ends to tie up.

One of them was rotting in the dungeon below the castle they were in now. After the battle was done they returned to the human kingdom with the remaining forces. Without the king and with Zhang Dong being powered up there was no resistance and they established a somewhat new order.

Now came the real question, what would happen to this world if he left. Without him, there would come trouble. He felt that a civil war would take place now after the ruling monarch was gone. His children were there and they were not part of the system but could he leave it up to them to be good rulers?

“Well then, did you decide?”

“Ah, welcome Mr. Matthew.”

He arrived in a certain room where three girls and one young man were sitting. They were the party of heroes that weren’t able to shine much due to his involvement. After the battle, he managed to sever their connection to the system thanks to Bob and now they needed to decide.

“Will you be staying, or will you return?”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 327

“Well then… are you really sure about this?”

“Yes Mr.Matthew, we have all talked this through.”

Zhang Dong was in the human kingdom and in the capital city where he first met the King. He was standing with the group of four heroes. Takeshi and Ami were standing on one side while the two sisters were on the other side.

“I left you the knowledge required for crossing over worlds but without a nucleus, it’s not usable…”

“Yes we know but you won’t change our minds.”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh while rubbing his head. Takeshi and Ami had decided to remain in this world while the two sisters Sakura and Yua would be going back home.

He knew why Takeshi wanted to stay, a lot of young men would have done the same. The youth was now one of the most powerful people in this land and would soon become the Hero-King of this country.

With the death of their previous monarch, the country was destabilized. The other races might hold it against them that the human king turned out to be a demon. Thus the only person that could take his place would be the hero who defeated it.

Everyone agreed to falsify the information slightly. Beatrice and Isabella’s contribution would still count but the hero party would be shown to have taken a more active part as well.

After everything was settled Zhang Dong with the help of Bob tweaked Takeshi’s system. It would not be connected to the main one but he was able to keep his leveling system.

There was also the danger of the Overseers and lack of magical cubes. Luckily Bob had some answers this time around. What they left was an empty shell that would send a signal showing that this world was working as intended.

Zhang Dong wasn’t sure if it would work but not like he had any other choice. He had already absorbed all the cubes that this world had to offer.

Normally he would smack Takeshi over the head and toss him back home but there was also Beatrice. He felt it would be better if the young hero remained here to protect everyone. Even though the five demon lords were gone that didn’t mean that the entire demonic race had perished.

They weren’t as strong as before but would be more or less equal to the other people living in this world. With the barrier being gone more conflict would arise, the people would need someone as strong as the heroes.

Ami was staying mostly due to having a crush on Takeshi. The two somewhat came together at the end of the journey and the members of the royal family were forced out of the picture. Due to their father being the demon king they had lost all of their political power.

They were still just regular humans as he had checked. No one would trust them to lead the country, without Takeshi taking the king’s place there would be no peace. For now, all of them were thrown into the dungeon, at least the ones that they could find.

Some of the people from the royalist faction had already fled the capital before they even arrived to bring the news of their victory. It was clear that they would attempt some moves to regain their standing. Thus he was all for having someone like Takeshi remain here and protect Beatrice. The youth needed to work on himself but his heart seemed to be in the right place.

He only hoped that the romance geometrical figure that was created wouldn’t get out of hand. It looked like Takeshi was still interested in Beatrice while Ami was gunning for her childhood friend. Then there was Isabella that was really close to her as well, while Beatrice remained a bit oblivious to everyone’s approaches.

“Okay, everything is ready. Are you prepared?”

“Ah wait a moment…”

The two sisters moved over to Ami and the three girls started hugging it out. All of them were crying as they knew that they wouldn’t be able to see their friend anymore. Some of the people that went on the journey with them were also here. The two female elven mages, some dwarves, and also Beatrice and Isabella.

After some heartfelt goodbyes, the two stepped onto the transportation circle. This one was prepared by Bob and Zhang Dong by reverse-engineering the original one. With the cube that operated it being absorbed it was ready for activation and there was no danger of it going wrong or at least that is what Bob was assuring him of.

Zhang Dong opened up his palm and a little holographic cube appeared there. It started shifting directions as if it was made from liquid metal before settling on some symbols. The moment it did the grand magic circle activated around the two girls.

They were surrounded by a large pillar of light that pierced the heavens just like the time they arrived here. This beam connected with something in the sky and a fissure opened up, through it a city appeared. It was the same one that the girls came through and soon they were blasting off into the air.

“Are you sure they will be okay…”

“Yes, if they happen to appear in the air they have the parachutes.”

Due to the way the fissure looked, always showing a large city from far away in the sky Zhang Dong was a bit worried. For this reason, he had some of the craftsmen make two parachutes for the girls. After some studious testing and training, it was safe to place the two back home. Even though Bob assured him that the probability of this happening was really low, it was better to be safe than sorry.

The hole in the sky soon mended itself back and the two were gone back home. This was the only thing that he could do for them as going there himself would be impossible without another world tether. Even if that could have been his world of origin, his body could be long dead.

“They are really gone…”

Ami said while grasping onto Takeshi’s arm, the girl continued to look up into the sky along with her childhood friend. Zhang Dong on the other hand walked over to the two blond girls that were now strong enough to walk around.

“Are you leaving as well Mr. Leigong… no is it Mr. Matthew… or was it, Zhang Dong?”

He laughed as he had disclosed to the two that he wasn’t a real summoned spirit but a person from another world. The two didn’t really get it as even there he went by a different name.

“Call me however you please.”

“Think Leigong suits you better, the other two sound strange…”

He could only laugh about his original name sounding weirdly to these two.

“It’s a very popular name where I come from!”

They all laughed but soon the girls looked sad once more. It was time to say their farewells to him as well. He had already prolonged his stay here and waited for the two to somewhat recover. His family was still waiting for him and he had no way of knowing where and when he would arrive if he made it back to his world.

The formation here had the coordinates for the homeworld that the hero party came from but not for his. They would limit the search though but he needed to leave this world before Bob could triangulate his destination.

“Do you really need to go…”

“Yes, my wife and children are waiting for their father…”

“Father…”

Isabella dropped her head down after the word father was mentioned. Her own dad was now trapped in the dungeons. Even though it was the king’s order he organized the assassination. The only reason that Zhang Dong didn’t punish him more thoroughly was that he was Isabella’s dad. Beatrice had forgiven him as she knew that he only did it to save his own daughter but it was not something that could be easily downplayed.

Zhang Dong placed his hand on Isabella’s and Beatrice’s shoulders each. He felt their souls one last time before stepping away.

“You’re getting better, but continue to stay close to each other. Before I go there is one last thing…”

He concentrated on his own soul. It was many times larger and denser than it was before he entered this world. Even though he was trapped here he would be taking new knowledge and power back to his own world. Before he left there was another gift that he wanted to give to the two girls, now after resting they would be able to receive it.

While concentrating on his soul he started yanking. He felt the strain and horrendous pain but he continued, in a moment a tiny fragment from his oversized soul started to loosen up.

“Here, take this.”

“What is…”

The girls saw a small white bubble of energy escape from Zhang Dong’s hand and float towards them. It started out slowly but soon the bubble split into two and each of them shot towards the girls and their dantian.

“What was that energy… it feels warm…”

“You’ll see… try summoning me… both of you…”

“Summoning you, but you are right here?”

Asked Beatrice while confused.

“Just do it.”

The two nodded and concentrated on the summoning spell. They could feel Zhang Dong still there but each of them could also feel something else, there was another smaller Zhang Dong there.

“Guohhh…”

“Gao…”

Soon two small creatures appeared. One was mostly black while the other was white. The two creatures seemed the same with the coloring being the only thing that was different. They both looked like miniaturized versions of his soul beast and now they would be tied to their souls.

“You didn’t think I’d leave you without one last gift, now did you? Grow them well and they will become your greatest strength.”

The two small dragons looked at the blond girls. The white one started floating around Beatrice and dropped on her shoulder while the black one did the same on Isabella’s side.

“Dragons?”

The two were quite ecstatic after receiving the gifts which resulted in a big hug which caused Zhang Dong to rub the back of his head.

Soon it was time to return, Zhang Dong walked over to the spot that the two sisters occupied and took one last look at the new friends that he made. He wasn’t here long but he would remember this place and the people he met here.

“Beatrice, Isabella. This is not a farewell more of a see you later. I will find a way to cure you and return, until then, stay in good health you two!”

He gave the two girls a smile while waving. The last thing he saw before the pillar of light appeared was their sobbing and snot-covered faces.

‘Bob get ready, we are leaving, next stop… my world!”

“Please wait, gathering data for the interworld jump…”

The teleportation formation connected to his soul world and through it, the opening to the tunnel that went between all the multiple worlds started opening. The gap opened up and after taking one last glance at the planet he was leaving he jumped, it was time to return home!

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 328

“Hey! Come back here!”

A young woman was seen running through a forest. Her hair was messy and her clothes didn’t seem like they had been washed in weeks. Calluses had formed on her bloodied feet as she was bolting into the distance. She kept looking back while hearing angered shouts that were getting closer with each moment.

“Damn slave!”

“What?”

The girl was preoccupied with looking behind her while escaping but suddenly she heard a voice from the front. The moment she turned her face she saw a fist coming her way.

“UGhhh…”

She was struck down during her attempt to flee and crumbled like a deflated balloon onto the ground. Soon another man that was following her came out from the bushes.

“Stupid slut, making me run!”

The man looked maddened by the unruly slave and quickly took it out on the young woman. His foot was planted in her abdomen which made her tumble into some bushes.

“Hey, be careful. The Lord wanted her alive for the big event.”

“Tsk…”

The angry man clicked his tongue while going over to where the woman tumbled towards.

“Come here… hm?”

The young woman was barely moving at this point and the man grasped her arm. He leaned down to do this but while there he also noticed something out of the corner of his eye.

“Hey, what’s that?”

“Where…”

He pointed to the shrubs, there he could see a foot sticking out. The other person that was there pulled out a large saber and slowly approached.

“Huh? Did another slave escape?”

What he saw was another person down on the ground. It was a man this time, it looked like this person had been through a lot. The robe that he was running was all cut up and his body had also many small wounds all over it.

“No… is he still alive? Was this bastard attacked by some beasts?”

The man with the saber moved closer and gave a poke to this man’s foot with his weapon. The moment he did he could see it twitch slightly.

“Still alive? Must be a tough bastard but he doesn’t feel special…”

The two men looked at each other. One of them grabbed the girl and slung her over his shoulder.

“Take him, the more stock we have for the event the better.”

The other slaver looked to the half-dead man and grinned.

“This is your lucky day, you’ll help us please the clan lords.”

The man that was covered in a mix of soil, blood, and leaves was grabbed by the other man and dragged back to where they came from.

“Took you long enough, who is that?”

“We found this one in the bushes, he is half dead but should prove as a nice addition to the ‘event’, Boss.”

The two large burly men returned to what looked to be a caravan of people. There was a row of slaves all tied up in shackles with a couple of muscular men surrounding them. They were holding whips and when anyone got out of line or slowed down they would deliver punishment.

“For the event?”

An old man in a robe moved his hand over to the passed-out man. He yanked his hair up to look at his face, his eyebrow was raised instantly after examining.

“Not bad… if we cleaned him up he could go for some spirit crystals.”

This man was wearing an expensive-looking robe. His long skeleton-like fingers were adorned with many rings and gemstones. He was quite lanky and tall and was clearly the owner of this slave caravan.

“Alas there is no time, toss him in the cage with the others, we will use him. Don’t let the girl escape, if we lose her the lord will have our heads, is that understood!”

“Yes, boss.”

The half-dead man and the young woman were then promptly tossed into a large carriage. This carriage was just a big cage with a lot of shackled people in it. All of them were wearing metal collars around their necks and the same collar found its way onto this man’s neck as well.

“Young lady...”

The moment the girl was tossed into the cage a few people moved over to her.

“I’m sorry… I wasn’t fast enough… I just didn’t have enough strength and this slave collar.”

Most of the people from this cage gathered around the girl that was caught. They were all wearing similar robes with the same emblem. They all had seen better days, everyone was beaten and bruised. The food and water rations were minimal and everyone was barely holding up.

“Save your strength Lady Yanmei, there is still hope… if we can survive through that...”

An old man commented from the side while looking out through the cage bars.

“Do you really think that if we survive they will keep their promise?”

“The White Tiger Clan isn’t known for their mercy… but if they go back on their word then they will lose face... They will let us go but I’m sure their assassins will be sent soon after, that will be our chance to escape…”

“I’m sorry… if I just accepted the White Tiger Clan’s young master’s proposal this wouldn't be happening…”

“It’s fine young lady… no one expected them to poison the lord so swiftly…”

“But we need to look towards the future…”

The man tried to reassure the young lady that there was still hope but soon he looked to the side. There the half-dead young man was lying, barely breathing while also bleeding.

“Who is that?”

“I don’t know… they picked him up from the forest, I think he was attacked by some beast… an unlucky bystander…”

“Truly unlucky… he would have a bigger chance surviving in the forest than here…”

Some weak chuckling escaped from the people in this cage. They all knew that they were more than likely heading towards their demise. This person that had barely lived through the beast attack would soon meet his end as he wasn’t in any condition to survive through what was coming next.

“We should help him...”

Lady Yanmei called out while moving over and having trouble turning the man around. The man’s face was covered with dirt, blood, and grass even with that it was clear that he was quite handsome. There was no water that they could use to clean it. At most what the slaves could do was bandage up the wounds with ripped cloth parts.

Soon the trip continued and lasted a day till they arrived at a large city. The carriage with the slaves was covered up by a thick cloth so they couldn’t really see what was happening outside.

Xia Yanmei was a young lady from the Snapping Turtle clan. A month ago her life looked bright, her clan was prospering and everyone was living their lives to the fullest. Then she met him, the young master from the White Tiger Clan.

He demanded that she became his concubine but she refused. Their clan wasn’t much weaker than the White Tiger Clan but their parents told her to reconsider as they all knew how vicious those people were.

She knew that her refusing the offer was just a pretext to strike. There were already spies among them within a short amount of time her grandfather the strongest cultivator was poisoned and she was captured. A war was started which left her clan decimated, no one knew how many members were still alive or even if there any remained.

No one would come to help out. This was a fight between two small clans that didn’t account for much. Even this city was at the sidelines of the empire. Not many bigger factions showed up here and even if they did no one was counting on any help.

“All of you get in!”

The sound of a rusty metal door closing was heard by the captured clan members. They were all forced into one cell that clearly didn’t have enough for everyone.

“Is this the end…”

“Are they really going to do this to us?”

“Calm down everyone, there is still hope!”

“What hope? We are all doomed… we will all die tomorrow!”

The people from the Snapping Turtle Clan lamented while pushing against the metal bars. They would learn the hard way about why they shouldn’t be doing that. After a few seconds, the person that was yanking on the metal bars found himself being shocked. He dropped down to his knees with his hair standing up, not dead yet unconscious.

“Idiots, don’t touch the bars if you know what is good for you!”

The guard that was on duty laughed after seeing the first person being shocked. This wasn’t the first time a slave did this, he could never get enough of seeing people get electrocuted.

Xia Yanmei slumped against the cell wall and slid down onto her posterior. She curled her knees up all the way to her chest while hugging them. Everyone was dead tired, the lamenting and cursing stopped as no one had enough stamina to keep up.

“Is this really the end… father… mother…”

Tears started pouring out of her eyes while she tried not to sob. If she knew that this would be the outcome she would have accepted the proposition. Even then there was no guarantee that her clan would be left alone. In this cruel world, only strength prevailed and the weak were snuffed out like candles in the wind.

“Ugh…”

She heard a grunt to the side, the man that was dragged along with them was still here. She placed her hand on his forehead and could feel that he had a fever. There was not much that she could do for him though. No medicine herbs, no water, and no food. The only thing she could do for him is to place him in a comfortable sleeping position with her lap as a pillow.

“This is the real world huh...”

The girl lived a sheltered life so this was a first. The man before her looked weak but he was still struggling to survive. She wished that he would manage but even if he recovered, tomorrow his death would be assured.

During the night she couldn’t really sleep. The man continued to mumble strange things while tossing and turning. He mentioned a few unknown names of people and families that she had no idea about.

“I… I need to go b-back…”

He continued to mention these words while stretching out his hand as if he wanted to grasp something. She could only grasp it instead, the man’s grip was quite weak and she couldn’t feel an ounce of cultivation in him. The only thing she could think of, was him being crippled or just being one of the unlucky mortals that walked this world.

“Get your asses in gear, it's time for the big show!”

An obese man with yellowy teeth greeted them in the morning along with many guards. It was time to go towards their demise, still a little bit of hope remained as they were led through a corridor. The man that she spend the night nursing was pulled along, it seemed that he was close to waking up but not like the slavers would give him much time to recover.

When outside she was blinded by the bright sunlight and cheering people. All of them were led up to the outside, their shackles were quickly removed and the doors they came from closed behind them as they found themselves in a large arena, the people around them calling out for a good show and blood.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Also a new voting feature!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 329

‘Ugh... what’s going on…’

‘Where am I?’

Zhang Dong slowly opened up his eyes, his vision was blurry and he could feel himself getting dragged by someone. His arms were spread and two people were supporting him from each side while treading towards some destination.

He tried to remember what happened after he crossed into that interworld tunnel once more. Slowly it started to come back to him. The moment he jumped through that fissure he was flung into it once more. Not much had changed since the first time he came there with one tiny difference, this time he knew of Bob’s existence.

During his stay in the previous world, he gathered up many cubes which he used as energy sources. These he used to triangulate his home world’s location. His Ai activated and the search started while he tumbled through the tunnel.

This place was bright and from time to time he could see flashes of other worlds. Some were similar to the one he came from with knights and wizards, others on the other hand seemed bizarre with strange creatures living in them.

Bob finally came through and was able to find the way back home. This would use up all of the conserved energy that he had stored behind. The moment he gave Bob he okay he felt a strange pulling sensation yanking him in one direction.

It wasn’t anything pleasant as he was flung through this tunnel just in the opposite direction than before. The speed kept increasing and the worlds that he was able to see before became just a blurry mess.

He could barely stay awake as he slammed into some kind of wall. Instead of another fissure opening up, he felt like a piece of meat getting pushed through the grinder. It seemed he was forced here by Bob’s triangulation, the rest was just a flash. He felt his flesh and soul being ripped apart and he was unable to keep himself awake as he passed out.

‘Did I make it back? … Why do I feel so weak…’

While trying to ascertain his location he felt a cool breeze and some light hitting his face. There was a sound of a gate sliding open before the walk forward continued. He was soon let down to the ground by the people that were carrying him. Soon shouts of many people made his hurting ears ring.

‘Bob… what’s happening…’

‘System rebooting please wait…’

His inquiry was ignored and when focusing on his system screen he only saw a small pixelated hourglass slowly moving around. It seemed that while passing through the world’s barrier the system used up almost all of its energy. It might have even saved his life from the way he felt. He was barely alive and there was another big problem, he couldn’t feel his cultivation.

‘It’s gone… it’s all gone?’

Nascent soul, core formation, foundation establishment, and then Qi condensation were the realms he was familiar with. Now on the other hand he could not feel an inkling of Qi in his body, it was totally dry as if it was used up during his journey back here.

“Uff…”

He felt his face hitting some dirt, the people that were helping him previously moved away. Zhang Dong could feel that there was a small group around him. They were standing close to each other while the shouts of the audience continued.

‘Is this some kind of arena?... why would they carry me here…’

Not knowing where he was and why he was here he started to panic. Without his cultivation, he wouldn’t be able to handle even a teenager that had some Qi in him. The only thing bringing him back to reality was the small hourglass on his system window.

‘Wait… maybe it's not fully gone…’

He realized that his system was still there, it was just rebooting. When it came back on he might be able to recover all of his cultivation or at least some. With a plan in mind, he stopped squirming and tried to assess the situation.

His body was in a world of hurt, it was burning up due to many small cuts that have not yet healed. Someone had clearly mended him somewhat back to health. There were cloth bandages around his chest, arms, and legs.

Soon he could also see that they were all quite dirty and dark from his blood. When his vision became less blurry he could finally see his surroundings. He was indeed in some sort of large arena, there were many people looking at them.

‘... the clothes… they are similar…’

The first thing that he noticed is that the people were wearing robes. The dress sense was identical to what he was used to in his old world. He was also not getting any warning signs about not being tethered to this world so it was probable that he had returned.

“Xia Yanmei, you should have taken my proposal, now you will die like a dog!”

He heard a haughty voice from the distance, it was backed by cultivation so he could hear it clearly. This tone, this way of speaking, it was something that he was familiar with. When glancing up at the person that was speaking out, one thing sprung to his mind.

‘A young master… I did make it back! Now I just need to make it out of here alive… what is this about anyway...’

It was time to listen in, maybe he was even in his own territory. I this was one of his subservient clans they would surely help him out. The biggest problem was his cultivation level though, if he said that he was the United Element Sect’s Patriarch while having no power to back it up they could just slice his head off.

“Please young master Dai Rong, show mercy, my clan members have not done anything wrong…”

“They have done nothing wrong, you say? They are related to your Snapping Turtle Clan, that’s enough to make them guilty!”

‘Snapping Turtle Clan?’

“Please, the White Tiger Clan and us can still coexist with each other it's not too late…”

'White Tiger Clan?'

While the young girl named Xia Yanmei pleaded for the lives of her people Zhang Dong noticed something strange. The clan names were not what he was used to. Normally they were run by families, so the clan named White Tiger Clan should have been the Dai clan instead. The Snapping Turtle would have normally been the Xia clan.

‘Did I end up in another cultivation world… or is it just some far away province…’

There were a few possibilities. One was that he was in a similar world to his old one but it wasn’t quite the same. Another option was that he just ended up in some faraway land where the naming sense was just different.

With that thought in mind he calmed down, the first thing was to get out of here. The conversation continued between the two sides. It looked like the girl refused to get married to this young master type and he saw to it that her clan collapsed. This was quite the overreaction but it was in alignment with what a young master would do in his old world.

“Enough, you had your chance, now someone else has taken your spot!”

The young man named Dai Rong was hugged from the side by a jade-like beauty while laughing. The girl called Xia Yanmei just dropped her shoulders as it seemed that there was no way of talking her way out of this.

“But, I’m a magnanimous lord, you will have your chance of surviving. You just need to stay alive and you may live as a slave for the rest of your life!”

The young master laughed while dropping back onto a large chair. The girl that was with him landed in his lap and also started laughing. The two were in some VIP booth with other people in it, some were old and some were young and no one felt familiar in any way.

“Begin!”

The signal was given but Zhang Dong still felt terrible. A large gate opened up in the distance and something walked out. It looked like a silverback gorilla with strange white stripes running over its dark fur. There were three of these beasts there while the group that Zhang Dong was part of consisted of about twenty people.

“Thunder apes? Aren’t those as strong as a middle stage Inner Aura practitioner?”

‘Inner Aura realm?’

A big question mark appeared above Zhang Dong’s head. He had never heard about a cultivation realm like this one before. The notion that he was pushed into another world altogether was a possibility and without his system going online he could not ask Bob to confirm this either.

“What will we do…”

“W-we must fight, it's the only way… look there are weapons there!”

The young lady called out to her people and pointed to a pile of weapons that was in the middle of the arena. It seemed that these people had left them some items to protect themselves with. Soon everyone from this clan rushed to the middle to pick up those items while also leaving him behind to his own devices.

He finally decided to get up as this was no time to play dead. Even then he felt like he was about to cross to the other side as standing up was already hard enough.

With all his strength that he could muster he forced himself to stand up. Now he was finally able to get a good look at everything and everyone. The group of twenty people was holding onto some rusty swords and spears. It was clear that these items would not do much to their opponents.

The trio of monsters beat their chests loudly while releasing small amounts of electricity. Soon a small skirmish between the cultivators and the beasts broke out. The people from the Snapping Turtle Clan used the old weapons but they snapped apart or didn’t have enough sharpness to do much damage to the monster apes.

“I’m scared…”

“Huh?”

Zhang Dong looked behind him. There he saw another group of people right up against the wall. It was composed of children, the elderly, and women. The group of twenty people that was fighting the monsters was clearly protecting this equally large group of non-combatants.

Then it happened one of the monsters spotted the people in the distance, him included. It broke out of the fight and started charging towards the people that could not protect themselves.

He found himself between a rock and a hard place. The monster was charging towards him but he was the only thing standing between these kids and their death.

Without thinking much he took up a battle stance, the monster charged quite fast and swung its large fist towards his position.

He knew that if he got hit, he would die. Even though his body was beaten up and tired, his eyes were still working. He predicted the trajectory of this hit and slipped to the side before it arrived there.

While the creature was confused about missing the weakling before him a fist descended towards its face. It burrowed itself into its cheek and did absolutely no damage. The monster didn’t even flinch while Zhang Dong felt his knuckles almost breaking apart.

The maddened monster raised its thick arms up into the air and started beating its chest like a drum. Electricity started shooting in all directions while hitting Zhang Dong straight on. He was sent flying by this small shockwave to the side, the monster snorting as if it just took care of some bug.

‘...External energy source detected… absorbing energy… system reboot complete…’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and vote!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 330

Name :

|

Zhang Dong

Affiliation :

|

Zhang Clan, United Element Sect

Spirit Points :

|

0

Cultivation Base Qi :

|

Qi Condensation [ 4 ] [ True Divine Golden Lightning Qi Scripture ]

Cultivation Base Body :

|

Qi Condensation [Early Stage 0%] ( Bronze Body)

Techniques :

|

True Divine Lightning Path Cultivation Art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...

Dao :

|

Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting...

Other :

|

Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes...

‘W-what is this…’

Zhang Dong staggered forward and onto his knees. He was now looking at his status screen that he stopped using after achieving the nascent soul level.

‘System has been rebooted.’

After getting jolted by the large gorilla he heard that his system was finally restarting. The moment it did he felt power rushing back into his body. He thought that this meant that his nascent soul cultivation would be restored but it wasn't so.

The feeling subsided quite fast while the system gave him a new red alarm. There was a big prompt with 'insufficient spirit points to restore cultivation' before him.

‘Bob, what is the meaning of this? What happened with my cultivation? Is this even my old world?’

While rubbing his forehead and trying to get past the headache he consulted his AI.

‘This is the user’s homeworld. An error occurred while passing through the world barrier. To protect the user more energy was required.’

‘More energy? Did you use my cultivation as the power source?’

‘That is correct.’

‘Great…’

He finally stood up and looked at the situation before him. This was apparently the world that he came from, it was also giving off the usual cultivator vibes but there was something strange. Zhang Dong felt that the spiritual energy was very similar but somehow different.

The monster gorilla that was moving towards him was also a bit peculiar. After the exchange, he could tell that the way this beast cultivated differed from the beasts back home. Before this question could be answered, he needed to get out of here.

He was weaker than ever, even when he popped up in the world of summoners he wasn’t this weak. He did have superior cultivation methods so that did put him on a higher tier than anyone at his own level. Even with this, he would not be able to defeat a foundation establishment cultivator at the early stage.

“GUAHHHhh.”

‘Damn it’s coming… middle stage Inner Aura, was it?’

He focused on the creature that knocked him to the side with an electric shock. Luckily for him, he cultivated lightning. This left him immune to all lightning-based attacks that were weaker than his own DAO. He could even absorb the energy and use it to cultivate, which put an idea into his head.

“Hey ugly...what are you looking at?”

With a swift kick, he sent a fist-sized rock flying towards the Thunder Ape. The beast was hit right on the nose but didn’t flinch, the rock was unable to cause any damage to this strong monster.

It did make the monster mad though, its eyes homed in on him and it started beating its chest once more. Small arcs of electricity started appearing on its large frame and it charged forward.

This was just what he was aiming for but he also needed to figure out how well he could handle this ape.

His opponent was quite fast all things considered. It jumped into the air when it was about ten meters away from him and raised its massive muscular hands up. Zhang Dong jumped back almost instantly while covering his face.

When the creature connected with the spot that he was previously on those two massive fists struck the ground. The earth cracked and small bursts of electricity were discharged into the surroundings.

Even though he was successful at reading his opponent he could feel that he was weaker than this creature. If he got hit by those two fists, he would have been critically injured. Then this monster even had passive attacks in the form of electricity bursts.

The moment this ambient lightning touched his body he quickly absorbed it. The energy that he absorbed felt weak, it was nothing compared to his own Divine Lightning but it would have to do.

‘I’ll need more than this…’

The little jolt of energy got his body pumping, it felt slightly revitalized but he needed more. Even though this beast was stronger than him in almost everything there were two things that it was lagging behind.

Zhang Dong jumped into the fray, which was also noticed by some of the people in the audience.

“Hey, what is that madman doing? He is trying to fight the Thunder Ape at close range?”

“That idiot, he is going to be turned to meat paste!”

A few of them cheered while looking, they wanted to see some blood but instead were surprised. The monster continued to attack but the strange man that was covered in dirt and blood kept avoiding each deathly strike. It was as if he knew where the monster would throw its massive fist and at the exact time dodged to the side.

This was Zhang Dong’s big advantage. He had already gone through many fights where his life was on the line. His mastery of predicting where his opponent would strike was something that he focused his time on. Even if the creature could take him out with one hit, it wouldn’t matter if it couldn’t actually deliver a blow in the first place.

“Hm… that movement… interesting…”

Up in the VIP booth where the young master was sitting there were other people. One of them was an old-looking cultivator with a long red beard. He was an elder that was tasked with keeping the White Tiger Clan young master safe.

Even though he found this whole event in poor taste he was unfit to comment on it. His job was to watch this young lord, if he stepped out of line he would surely be punished by the young master’s scary father.

He thought that this would be a quick slaughter, not much to watch. Now on the other hand he was looking at a peculiar young man. This man looked like he was one step in the grave but for some reason, he wasn’t giving up.

He continued to evade the ape beast's strikes with grace while sometimes throwing in some of his own attacks. These strikes were hardly effective as they didn’t seem to be able to get through the monster's thick hide nor were he able to inject any spiritual energy to damage the insides either.

‘He is getting faster and stronger…He isn’t from the Snapping Turtle Clan… where could someone like this be from’

The old man started to get worried, from what he knew a few people in this arena were just tossed in together with those Snapping Turtle Clan members. What if there was someone from a more influential clan or even sect pushed into a death game? What if that clan or sect found out about the whole predicament.

‘Am I worrying too much? What would a powerful sect member be doing here in the first place? Can he even defeat that Ape with his meager strength?’

The old man moved his head to the other side, there the group of twenty or so combatants had shrunk down to fifteen. The two remaining Thunder Apes had crushed them easily while also suffering minimal damage.

This senior had seen the low graded trash that those slaves called weapons. None of them would be able to help them through this battle. They were all useless and just bounced off the monster’s skin.

Then in the other corner was a smaller group of about ten people. It was composed of children and women. These women were all in front of their offsprings while looking terrified. They were focused on the stranger that was battling the Ape beast.

The old man leaned back in his chair and continued to look. The young master that he was tasked to protect wasn’t even looking to this side. His gaze was on the young missus from the Snapping Turtle Clan.

Even though the girl was fighting well it wouldn’t matter, they were facing off against a beast stronger than them and with low quality weapons. Then there were the slave collars that were ready to deliver a shock whenever the young master wanted. This old man didn’t believe that this young master would keep his promise of letting these people go.

Cultivation Base Qi :

|

Qi Condensation [ 5 ] [ True Divine Golden Lightning Qi Scripture ]

‘I’m getting stronger…’

Zhang Dong lodged his fist in the Silverback Gorilla-looking creature’s abdomen. It felt like he was punching a hard wall. He was then shocked by the beast’s residual electrical aura once again.

The people that looked at his fight were quite baffled. It made it seem that he was someone that didn’t want to give up. He always jumped in to attack the beast but was constantly knocked back by the small lightning bolts. They didn’t realize that this was his plan as with every shock that he took, he was gaining more power.

‘Is there a way to get more energy out of this thing at once…’

He was getting a bit tired of the goose chase. This monster didn’t use the lightning attack unless he closed in. It also had no range to speak of so he needed to constantly risk his life by getting closer to its massive arms.

It might have looked like the punches that he was delivering were useless but there was something that he was doing. With each punch, he injected a tiny amount of his spiritual energy to weaken the beast and also to find the source of its lightning.

After a few exchanges, he discovered the place where this organ was. It was somewhere around the lung area which might have explained why the Ape always beat its chest to release these shocks.

Now armed with the knowledge he could do two things, either continue his sluggish approach which was safer or go in for the kill. He knew enough about beasts to theorize that if he damaged that organ it would overload. Then it would release all of its stored power in one fell swoop.

‘I should not dwindle too long…’

Out of the corner of his eye, he could see two other large Ape beasts. They already took the lives of many and the longer he fought the one here the more people would die.

The monster charged after him once more. Its eyes were filled with berserked rage due to Zhang Dong’s constant evasions. This time though he didn’t wait for the monster to charge, instead he closed the distance himself.

His hand opened up, his fingers together. Zhang Dong began gathering Qi onto his fingertips, there weren’t that many Qi condensation techniques that he could utilize. This one would change his hand into a spear that could pierce through things like hard metal.

The monster swung its fist in a blind rage again but with a small side movement, this face only grazed Zhang Dong’s cheek. He took a step forward and was now in range to perform his attack. His fingers looked like they were covered in golden plasma energy. They were quickly shoved into the monster’s chest piercing it in one go as he aimed for the electrical organ.

The monster screamed in agony while also producing a massive electrical charge. Its organ was pierced and went out of control just as Zhang Dong had planned. The energy flowed into him and he took it all in.

Soon the arena went quiet as one of the ape beasts fell. The other two that were about to deliver a killing blow to one of the warriors there turned to the shouts of their kin. There they saw him falling down, dead and without movement.

‘One down two to go…’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, and rate!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 331

Zhang Dong felt the lightning energy rushing into his body. Thanks to his superior cultivation technique he was purifying this energy into its most potent form before absorbing it. With this gorilla-like monster now dead he had reached the 6th level of Qi condensation which put him at the halfway point towards the foundation establishment level.

With having lost most of his cultivation level he was weak and susceptible. However, there was one good thing that came out of this. With the added knowledge and the increased soul power that he achieved from the other world, he would only get stronger.

He would be now able to recreate his foundation with his own two hands. It wouldn’t be based on the system but on his own knowledge of the DAO that was more advanced than it ever was. When he recovered all of his lost power he would be many times stronger than he was before his loss.

‘It is good to think about the future but I should survive this first…’

After Zhang Dong took care of his enemy the other two Thunder Ape’s turned his way. Their friend gave out quite the cry for help after he pierced his chest.

“He killed it?”

Xia Yanmei looked at the damaged sword in her hand. Even when successfully hitting the two beasts this blade only left scratches behind. The girl might have been the young lady from a clan but she wasn’t that strong. The people that were left here were only servants that gave up the way of the cultivator a long time ago.

Now some hope had appeared, the strange man that she helped nurse to health had awoken. Previously she couldn’t feel much spiritual energy from him but now it seems that he was her equal.

She was somewhat happy while also surprised. The man didn’t seem that much stronger than her but he managed to kill one of the Thunder Apes alone. She on the other hand even when getting help wasn’t able to deliver a damaging blow that would turn the tide.

“E-everyone… let us help that stranger, he looks capable!”

The people here jumped to the side after the two remaining beasts charged at this man. They nodded at the order as this did seem like a good opportunity to turn this around. But as they started running towards this man, he turned to them and shouted.

“You should stay back, you’ll just get in the way!”

Everyone stopped at Zhang Dong’s words. Xia Yanmei in particular was shocked at the response. The man looked half dead but for some reason, he wanted to fight the beats on his own. He shouted loudly so even the people in the audience heard it.

“Is he mad?”

“He did kill that one Thunder Ape but isn’t he getting ahead of himself?”

“Another Calf that does not fear the tiger!”

The people that were previously cheering for him changed their tune. He would get his chance to prove himself though. While everyone watched from the sidelines Zhang Dong waited for the gorillas to engage in the fight.

His cultivation was still slightly below these giants but with his purified cultivation arts he would make up for it.

This time around both of the apes jumped up in the air, similar to what the first monster did. After tussling with the other Ape, Zhang Dong was now used to their attack pattern. He waited for the right moment and slid to the side while evading the large descending fist.

Even though the ground was cracked from the impact he didn’t lose his balance. A swift knee with some Qi gathered on it collided with one of the beasts sending it tumbling back. The other one was quick to discharge some electricity but it was ineffective.

The Thunder Ape that was hit was surprised by how much pain it was feeling from that flying knee it took. With the increase in cultivation, Zhang Dong was now able to deliver painful punches that would make even those Ape second guess themselves.

While the one that was hit backed away slightly the other one charged. It swung its large hands around at a fast rate while trying to hit its target. Zhang Dong could feel the wind pressure from each attack passing his body as he evaded.

Even though he leveled the playing fields he still would suffer greatly if he got hit even once. His body had lost all of its refinement and he would need to reabsorb more items. This was not something he could do now so his Qi cultivation would have to suffice.

The old man in the VIP booth continued to look at the baffling display of skill. The young man that was fighting was constantly getting stronger. He could feel the young man move on from a very low level of Inner Aura realm to the middle stage in a couple of minutes. It seems that he was getting progressively stronger as time passed.

The way that he was fighting also told a tale of its own. He was very strategic with his movements the Thunder Apes even if stronger were just dumb beasts, they could not comprehend what was happening.

They constantly bumped into each other and got in the way of their own attacks. The young man was clearly playing with them while recovering his strength. The old man started to get worried, this man was an enigma that could belong to some strong force from somewhere. He was just too good at fighting, this was not something that could be learned at a third-rate clan.

“GUOOOhhh…”

Another Thunder Ape fell to the man’s attack. A large explosion of lightning energy was discharged by the silver-haired man didn't seem to care. It was as if he was immune to pain and only looking at the leftover opponent.

It turned to a one-on-one once more. It seemed that the man was done with running as his strength increased again. He met the gorilla’s fist with his own and to the surprise of everyone the exchange was equal.

Previously he was evading blows and slipping small jabs to weaken this monster, now on the other hand the two started slogging it out. The Ape monster could not last long as it succumbed to the many blows, the last one ending up in its chest before it died.

‘This could be bad…’

The old man thought while rubbing his beard. How strong would this man be when he fully recovered, would he be able to go against him. If so would he spare him and the young master that trapped him in this arena?

He then looked at the man again and gave out a sigh of relief. There was still one thing that would protect him and the young master. The man was still wearing a slave collar around his neck, unless he reached the realm above the Inner Aura realm, he wouldn’t be able to remove that item.

“Y-you…”

His attention was brought to the side. The young lord he was tasked to protect slammed his fist into the rocky balustrade while looking at the arena. All of the apes were dead and not that many people had died.

“Who put that man in this event? I’ll have his head! He isn’t even part of the Snapping Turtle Clan, who is responsible for this?”

It seemed that the young master was sure that this was some kind of ploy. This also made this old man think, maybe someone was trying to make the young master look bad or maybe even to besmirch the Clan’s good name.

“Young master Dai Rong, you promised to let us go if we survived.”

While everyone was stupified Xia Yanmei saw this as a chance to escape. There was a promise given and with so many people present it would be a hit to the Clan’s face if they didn’t follow up on it.

“Promised? Yes, the promise still stands but you are not done yet, more beasts await! If you manage to survive I will be true to my word!”

The young master laughed while sitting down again. The gates where the apes walked through started rumbling once again as more beasts awaited.

“Lightning White Tigers! I heard they are a special breed that the White Tiger Clan has managed to produce! The Snapping Turtle Clan is finished!”

“They even have an alpha that is at the late stage of the Inner Aura Realm!”

Zhang Dong looked at the group of six tigers. Five of them were slightly stronger than the Apes he faced previously. There was also a larger one behind them, radiating power of about the Qi condensation 9th level.

‘Lightning White Tigers huh?’

He walked forward while the large group of people backed away while holding their rusted weapons. While passing next to what looked to be the leader in Xia Yanmei he spoke out to her.

“Young lady, please move back and just protect yourselves, you can leave them to me.”

“W-what? B-but there are so many we should work together…”

“It’s fine, leave this to the adult.”

He replied while charging forward, his legs started exuding static electricity of the golden coloring and to some, it looked as if he was skating on the ground.

While Zhang Dong moved towards he was thinking that he could not be any luckier. All of these beasts had electricity in them, through it he could quickly recover his power. The people here probably didn’t realize this yet and he would capitalize on this fact.

“RAWERrrr…”

The tigers growled and charged at the sole person stupid enough to engage them in an open battle. These white tigers had a small horn on their forehead, through it they could discharge concentrated electricity at their enemies, which they did.

Even when this blue energy connected with the man he didn’t falter. He looked even more ecstatic whenever one of them connected with him directly.

“Common give me more, that’s not enough!”

What followed was a strange battle indeed. The man seemed to just dance around these monsters. It was as if he was trying to force them into a long-range battle but whenever a bolt of lightning came he didn’t evade it. He continued to laugh and cackle like a madman while everyone watched, baffled more and more by this display.

Lightning White Tigers, Thunderous Green Tipped Snake, and even the Red-Bolt Devilhound was not his match.

“More give me more… this is not nearly enough!”

Zhang Dong turned to the VIP booth where a certain scared young master was looking at him.

“What are you? How could you kill all of those beasts yourself! Did the other clans send you?”

“Young master Dai Rong, we need to end this. That man is dangerous, activate his slave collar, I will get rid of him personally after he is moved back to the dungeon. We can also kill the remnants of the Snapping Turtle clan after they are gone from the city and still retain our face!”

The old man to Dai Rong’s side sent a hidden message to the young master that only the two could hear. Dai Rong’s face that had a frown on it quickly recovered as he stepped forward and started talking.

“Well done, you have won this event, as promised you will be set free!”

“Huh, it’s over?”

Zhang Dong looked to this Dai Rong with a raised brow, the people that were huddling in the back were quite surprised as well.

“But you there, you have been impudent so you need to be punished!”

Dai Rong pointed to Zhang Dong while activating a treasure that looked like a wristband. The moment he did Zhang Dong could feel the collar around his neck activating. It didn’t explode but instead started delivering large amounts of electricity directly to his neck.

“Bwahaha, you serious?”

A strange laughing sound escaped from Zhang Dong’s mouth as he lit up like a Christmas tree and then collapsed on the ground.

“Take him away!”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate and vote [New feature]!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 332

“Hey, aren’t we free to go? Didn’t the young master promise?”

“Be quiet slave, the young master gave the order for you to remain here, be glad that you are still alive!”

The slightly rusted-over dungeon doors were closed by the guards that quickly went on their way. This was the exact same cell that the people from the Snapping Turtle Clan occupied before the arena event. Now the survivors were back in it, along with the man that saved them all, Zhang Dong.

Everyone saw him being electrocuted to a crisp by the slave collar. They suspected that the young master just wanted to kill the man out of spite but after they investigated they could hear his heart beating.

“Will they really let us go?”

Xia Yanmei asked one of the elders from the Snapping Turtle Clan.

“They might… but their assassins will be not far behind.”

“Yes young missus, that Dai Rong can not be trusted, you must flee the first chance you have, some of the Clan members were able to flee! It is still possible to rebuild our clan!”

“Yes, what the old lady is talking about makes sense.”

“Huh?”

The group of people that were talking turned to an unfamiliar voice and could see the unknown man there. They all jumped back after seeing him standing up as if the heavy electrocution never happened.

“Is something wrong? Is there something on my face?”

Zhang Dong answered while dusting his already mangled clothes off slightly.

“The honorable senior is fine? But the slave collar?”

The people quickly backed away from Zhang Dong. He had left a lasting impression on these people after massacring all those lightning beasts that the White Tiger Clan was known for.

“Ah, this?”

Zhang Dong grasped the collar around his neck and started to pull on it from both sides. The item activated once more and started delivering electric shocks. The people quickly jumped back while not knowing what this senior was doing.

“S-senior what?”

“It’s fine, this has no effect on me.”

Even when he was getting electrocuted he was still able to talk as if it was normal. After a couple of seconds, the slave collar started losing its charge and was promptly ripped open from his neck.

“White Tiger Clan you say… could you tell me where I am? I don’t recall such a clan existing...”

The young master that was sitting in that VIP booth wasn’t all that strong. After a quick scan with his system, he came out at around the Qi condensation 7th level. Zhang Dong had reached the 12th level now and was already close to going beyond.

There was one old man next to this youth, he gave off the feeling of a master above the foundation establishment level but there was something strange. The spiritual energy was similar but not quite, so was also the cultivation of the people around here.

“This is the city of Xuanhai.”

“Xuanhai? In which part of the Azure Dragon Empire is this?”

First were the clan names, now the city names had a different naming scheme than what he was used to.

“Azure Dragon Empire? Doesn’t Senior mean the Emerald Phoenix Empire?”

The people in the room looked at Zhang Dong as if he was being silly. He on the other hand started sweating as he had never heard of this Emerald Phoenix Empire.

“Ah, I know!”

An old man called out from the side as if he remembered something.

“In one of the old scriptures there was an old map, If I’m not mistaken, this Azure Dragon Empire is to the far west of our Emerald Phoenix Empire.”

“To the west?... how far is it!”

Zhang Dong swooped to where the old man was and grabbed him by the shoulders. He then promptly started shaking him around while his eyes bulged out.

“Ahhh...I-I’m not sure… It was an old map, it is forbidden to talk about what is outside the borders…S-senior please.”

“Ah sorry…”

He quickly let the man go while trying to get out some more information. From what he got was that there was some vague information about the Empire that he came from but it was something that was hidden away from the masses.

“The old map showed some kind of blockade between our empires but that’s all I know senior.”

“Is that so…”

Zhang Dong tried to remember if there were any mentions of this other Empire here. The maps that he had access to didn’t show anything to the east. There could very well be some kind of wall or natural phenomenon that divided these two empires. There were some rumors about other tribes or countries existing but nothing too explicit. The Azure Emperor kept everything under wraps and only he and the top two sects had that information.

‘This at least confirms that I’m on the right planet… now I must get home…’

A weight was dropped down from his shoulders as he now knew that he was in the right place. What he needed to do now was to return home while recovering his cultivation.

The biggest problem as always was time. He had no idea how long he had been away as he already saw that time between the worlds worked differently. For all he knew, hundreds of years could have passed or maybe just minutes since his departure.

‘This empire will have a different calendar…”

There was no way for him to calculate the right time. The stars that surrounded this huge planet moved around as if they had a life of their own. This made it impossible to use astrology to determine anything. What he was left with was a general direction, he needed to go west.

“Good, there is one last thing I’ll have you do for me…”

“Y-yes Senior?”

The old man asked while he saw a hand moving towards his neck. In a matter of seconds, Zhang Dong was grasping the man’s slave collar. The old man screamed out in shock as he knew that such acts would only activate this collar of death.

“N-noooo!!.....huh?”

Even when the collar activated and he could see the sparks fly around, he didn’t feel any pain. Instead, he saw the senior before him absorb the electricity. Then when the slave collar was out of juice he just ripped it to pieces.

“Can you all line-up, I’ll remove your collars…”

After fifteen minutes or so, Zhang Dong was sitting next to a pile of broken slave collars and a bunch of prostrating cultivators. Even Xia Yanmei, their mistress, was down and asking for help.

“I don’t really have time to help you regain your clan, at most I can help you escape from this dungeon but then you will be on your own…”

“You will help us escape? T-that will be more than enough honorable senior!”

Xia Yanmei replied while bobbing her head up and down out of gratitude. Zhang Dong on the other hand grasped one of the damaged slave collars and examined it.

Slave Collar [ Broken ]

|

Common [ High Grade ]

‘This thing had enough power to contend with a Qi condensation practitioner up to the 12th level...It might be enough…’

“Could you tell me about this Empire of yours and also inform me if any trouble is coming, I must regain some of my lost strength.”

After absorbing all of that electricity he was almost ready to re-create his foundation pillar. This process was unknown to him as he arrived in this world as a core formation expert. Now before he did attempt a breakthrough he wanted to do something about his body refining.

The people followed his instructions, it was clear that he was home. In this world, if someone was considered a senior the juniors would follow his instructions the best they could.

Zhang Dong believed that the old fart that was with the young master would come for him. He would probably arrive here to either question him about his origins or just to kill him and to hide the body.

He was too much of an anomaly to be without backing. Which wasn’t wrong but his backing was in an empire on the other side of the planet. It was better to dispose of someone like him as they did already cross the line. Normally a senior in his position would not forgive such a transgression. Thus it was best to get rid of him while he was weak and defenseless.

While thinking he grasped one of the slave collars. He injected some of his spiritual energy into it which changed its color to red. Soon the people here saw the broken slave collar being absorbed into this man’s body.

‘80% in one go? not bad!’

His bronze body shot up quite fast and almost reached the middle stage after absorbing this one collar. There were many more, he hoped to attain his silver body which would really be helpful against the enemies from this Clan here.

“Don’t mind me, tell me about this city, empire and even about your cultivation...Inner Aura Realm was it?”

Xia Yanmei nodded while sitting before Zhang Dong, who was in the process of absorbing all of the collars. There were close to thirty people in this cell so he had a bit to go through.

An explanation of the current world affairs, or at least of what this small clan members knew of, started. This empire was very similar with it being divided between other powers but it was slightly different.

There were sects but they didn’t really focus as much on controlling the lands as the Azure Empire counterparts. This was mostly due to a smaller number of cultivators on this side, this being due to the way they cultivated.

While in the Azure Dragon Empire it was easy for anyone to gather Qi up to the 3rd level of Qi condensation, here it wasn’t. The Inner Aura Realm was the first one but was a lot more difficult to achieve. After examining the people here and asking about how they would be ranked he came to a conclusion.

The Inner Aura Realm at the early stage put someone at around the 4th level of Qi condensation right off the bat. This was probably why it was so much more difficult to achieve. It also only went up to about the 9th or 10th level of Qi condensation when it entered the late stage.

There was no grand circle small realm as all of the smaller realms here ranged from early to late. What they lacked in small realms they made up in larger realms. After the Inner Aura Realm, there was the Martial Master realm, which when fully mastered was at about the strength level of an early foundation establishment cultivator.

After it came the Martial Grandmaster realm followed by the Martial Saint realm. There were six in total with the Supreme Saint cultivation realm trading blows with the Nascent Soul level realm from his empire. It was a bit confusing but he believed that the power cap was the same in both empires. If not, then he might have some trouble in going back to his own side.

With less cultivator power the sects established giant secret grounds where they took disciples in. They left the ‘mortals’ to their own devices and didn’t care about anything else than cultivation. Some of them sometimes visited the cities but most of the time clans like this here only remained. Someone like a Martial Saint level cultivator would be hard to find as they were off cultivating somewhere and part of a larger sect.

The geographical and historical lessons continued for some more as he cultivated. Time was of the essence he needed to get out, luck wasn’t on his side though. He already imagined what would be happening after he left that door…

A note from Kuropon

Emerald Phoenix Empire realms:

Inner Aura Realm

Martial Master

Martial Grandmaster

Martial Saint

Supreme Saint

Saint Emperor

Chapter 333

A man with a bag over his head was being dragged through a narrow corridor. On the sides, there were steel doors with malnourished prisoners peeking out. Barely anyone was even looking through the small openings in the door, the will to live had long faded from their eyes.

The man was being dragged by two soldiers, their faces somewhat covered by pointy helmets. Both of them arrived at the end of this prison in a certain room.

“Senior, we have brought him over as you instructed…”

One of the men spoke out while he and his partner threw the passed-out person onto the floor.

“Good, is he still unconscious?”

“Yes senior.”

The old man with a red beard nodded while moving closer. In his hand, there was a sword and it looked like he was about to use it.

“I don’t know who you are, but for the prosperity of my White Tiger Clan you have to disappear.”

The man said in a monotone way while plunging his sword into the man’s chest. The man that the sword went through twitched slightly before he could feel the life leave his body.

“Hm…?”

This White Tiger Clan elder noticed that something was off. The way his sword went into the man’s body was strange. He saw him fight during the event, someone that was on the brink of the Martial Master realm should not be this soft.

He quickly sliced open the sack that was covering this man’s face. The first thing he noticed was the lack of white hair that the man at the arena was known for.

“What… isn’t this…”

The face that this now dead body had was something he recognized, it belonged to one of the guards that brought it in. The man quickly looked to the guards but only spotted one of them.

“Not showing any remorse…”

Before he could react a person grabbed him from behind. This person had a hellishly strong grip and put him in a chokehold almost instantly.

“I wanted to give you the benefit of the doubt, but you killed him instantly…”

An unfamiliar voice and a strength that went above anyone that should have been staying in this prison.

“Who are you? Do you really want to make enemies of the White Tiger Clan?”

The old man could feel the grip on his neck getting harder. He tried to activate his own Martial Master cultivation level that was at the late stage. Even when he did, he could not make the man budge the slightest.

“Enemies? Think we are long past that point…”

“Guhh...N-nooo...y-you…”

A peculiar crunching sound could be heard by the second ‘guardsman’ in this room. The strong senior before him stopped his struggles and his hands started flopping around without any strength in them.

The man that had killed this elder let go and removed his helmet. His appearance was the spitting image of the dead guard on the floor but soon it started to shift into this old man’s.

“I guess we will have to do it this way...”

Zhang Dong spoke out while now having the appearance of this White Tiger Elder. While going through the dead man’s clothes he thought to a few minutes before.

He had absorbed all of the slave collars that were in the room, this was enough to push his body refining into the silver body stage. The silver body put him on equal footing with a foundation establishment cultivator.

In these lands, a Martial Grandmaster would at most reach the power level of a foundation establishment cultivator at the great circle. This was also probably the level of the patriarch of this clan. He wasn’t that sure but it would align with how the smaller clans in his world worked.

A Martial Saint was equal to a core formation practitioner and the step into that realm would be a big bottleneck. This Clan was on the lower end of the totem pole. Thus he assumed that the enemy he would be going up against was a late stage Martial Grandmaster.

His plans weren’t to fight it out with the whole clan. They could have magical items that boosted their levels, maybe more of those beasts. It was nice to absorb all that electric energy but he could not fight a whole army, at least not yet.

Zhang Dong removed the old man’s clothes and put them on. Luckily he was wearing the more baggy robes which allowed him to fit his larger frame into them. The technique he was using only allowed him to shift his face for now.

Due to his low cultivation level, shifting his body shape was impossible. He was a bit taller than the man he replaced as well as packed on more meat. The baggy robe hid this fact slightly so he hoped he would be able to make his escape.

The man had a spatial ring with him, in it, he spotted something similar to spirit stones. Some weapons, other robes, pills, cultivation materials, and even some scriptures and manuscripts. He would need to examine them later as for now he only needed the sword that the man was using.

Spirit Steel Jian

|

Mortal low grade

The sword was your regular double-bladed design and the quality wasn’t all that great but it would have to do for now.

“H-how can I help, senior?”

While he was rummaging through this man’s belonging the other guardsman called out to him. This man belonged to the Snapping Turtle Clan. A few moments ago the two guards arrived to take him here. They were quickly knocked out and this man had the closest appearance to one of the other guards so he took him along.

The young lady that apparently came from the main family was now in charge. It seemed that she was putting her hopes on him now. Left with no way out he did look like the best option. They probably hoped that he would be enraged at the lack of respect and then the assassination attempt.

Zhang Dong didn’t fault his attackers for much. They were just trying to protect their own clan and thought this was the only way. He would not show mercy to people like this anymore though. He did not have enough strength to be lenient here, the man showed no mercy so he would not either.

“For now keep watch…”

He needed to think, the most troublesome part was now over. The elder that seemed to be the strongest person around was now gone and he defeated him without alerting the others. This gave him now the option of sneaking out of this dungeon.

No one would stop a high ranking elder and they would probably avert their eyes. The only problem would be the young master, if he ran into him, his cover might be blown.

Then there were the Snapping Turtle Clan members left in the cell. It would be easy to abandon them here and just sneak out by himself. Him getting out of the city would be almost assured if he just ignored them.

This was not how he lived his life though. This group of people aided him, they put bandages on his injured body. He might have died if they weren’t there so now he owed them.

“Hm…”

There was not much in this room, it looked to be an office where probably one of the guard captains resided in. For now, he stashed the body in a closet that had some weapons in it. He also found more keys, probably to the other cells and to the exit.

“Is there nothing else...what is that…”

There was a desk in this room, in it he found a map. It depicted this very dungeon along with some areas around it. He was versed in reading maps so he instantly spotted a few interesting things.

“There was an old sewer system that connected to this prison…”

Luck was on the side of the Snapping Turtle Clan as he found them a perfect escape route. This dungeon was built upon another structure that connected to some underground tunnels. It was time for a prison break.

What followed was a silent escape, after gaining the looks of an elite senior from the White Tiger Clan Zhang Dong could walk freely through this dungeon. Thanks to how it was built he was able to disable the guards without the others being able to notice them.

After about thirty minutes all of the guards that were on the level were out of commission. They were tossed into one of the cells without their weapons or any clothes. Those were given to the slaves that were strong enough to hold them.

“Great Senior please tell us your name!”

Xia Yanmei was now looking at the disguised Zhang Dong. The slaves that had their collars removed were now moving through a narrow hole in the wall that he made with a well-placed charged punch. It would lead them to a series of tunnels that ended at the edge of the city.

“Does Zhang Dong and United Element Sect ring a bell?”

He asked but the girl didn’t seem to know this name.

“Senior Dong from the United Element Sect? The Snapping Turtle Clan will remember this favor!”

Soon everyone had gone through the hole opening but Zhang Dong remained outside. Xia Yanmei and a few of their clansmen remained while looking at their savior. It seemed odd to them that he was not moving forward, it was as if he had other plans.

“Senior, you aren’t coming?”

“No… I need to figure out some things, this will be a good opportunity to gather some information.”

He replied while delivering a punch to the walls above this hole. The rubble covered up the escape route and would make it hard for anyone to follow after.

‘Well then, it’s you and me Bob.’

After giving out a sigh he headed up, he needed more information and that information could have been gotten in the White Tiger Clan. With his current incomplete disguise, he would have trouble moving freely. Thus before leaving there was one thing that he needed to do, reach the foundation establishment level!

He had noticed that this clan was versed in the dao of electricity. Even the doors here were electrified and would deliver small shocks to whoever touched them. With this in mind, he headed into a certain spot that he noticed on the prison schematics.

“It should be here…”

He pushed the large door open and inside he found the item in question.

Thunder Crystal

|

Mortal middle grade

This yellow crystal was in the middle of this room. It was floating around in a glass container to which many thick cables were connected to. This was this prison’s power source and the perfect item to further his cultivation.

During the breakout, he had already absorbed quite a lot of energy from the slave collars of all the prisoners that were here. This Thunder Crystal here was just the item he needed to complete his transformation.

“I’ve seen my disciples do this… it should not be that hard…”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate and vote [New feature]!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 334

“I don’t have much time… they will notice that something is off soon…”

Zhang Dong looked to the pile of disabled slave collars that he absorbed previously. Along with the Thunder Stone before him, it would need to be enough.

He was a bit surprised about how much of a bottomless pit his own cultivation had become. Ever since returning it felt deeper like he needed more to retrace his old steps. This was all due to his increased understanding of the Dao he studied and also because his soul had expanded.

With all of the energy that he absorbed from these common higher quality common grade items, he should have normally been able to create his perfect foundation pillar. That wasn’t so, he needed to go further beyond and absorb all of the energy that this prison facility had to offer.

Zhang Dong had already fiddled around with his system. There were some problems related to his cultivation. Due to it being so low most of his system functions were turned off or limited.

The map’s range had shrunk to about a hundred meters and he could not access things like his crafting abode. For that, he would need to wait till he achieved the core formation level. The teleportation function was also offline and so was his clan building window.

Without it, he could not check for his family members nor his disciples. He had no idea if they were alive, how much time had passed, and even where he was. After cultivating he needed to gather more information before deciding on his next destination.

‘I need to focus… the system is not helping me with this anymore…’

In the beginning, he mostly relied on the system, he could even spend spirit points directly to achieve breakthroughs. Now on the other hand it was all up to him but he wasn’t afraid. His Dao was supreme and he had all the knowledge that he needed. The only problem were the cultivation resources and time.

Before sitting down in front of the Thunder Stone he took out the sword that he got from the White Tiger elder. He started slicing the ground in front of the crystal, soon it took the shape of a combination of a magic circle and a formation.

Thanks to his time in the world of magic he had learned a few tricks. With this specialized formation, he would be able to hasten the process while also making it much easier. With it, there would be no wasted energy and he would be able to absorb it to its fullest.

He finally sat down in the lotus position and started to concentrate. The orange thunder crystal was radiating electrical power but soon it started to flow into his dantian. Everything became dark and he knew that the people outside might notice this.

It started to materialize as if it had always been there. A large pillar started to form inside of him. It was longer and thicker than it ever had been before, pure gold and radiating holy lightning energies.

The whole place rumbled as he opened up his eyes. Yellow light and electricity escaped from them and lit up the darkened room. The people outside heard a strange thunderclap below ground which was followed by an earthquake.

Thanks to Zhang Dong’s special formation the spiritual energy was contained to this room. The people outside would not notice that he was breaking through but he could not do much about the quaking.

‘Be formed… my prime pillar!’

He willed it into place and it formed inside of him. It stood tall like a monolith and it was just the first one of many. Around it, he would fashion even more pillars which would then be used to create his golden lightning core. Its might would eclipse the previous one just as this prime pillar overshadowed the old one.

“Whew…”

He gave out a sigh of relief after successfully going through his first major change. Due to the purity of the way he cultivated there were no impurities in his body.

After standing up he started checking if he made any mistakes and how much power he really had.

‘This… I’m much stronger… about the level of a great circle foundation establishment cultivator…’

He was a bit astonished by the jump in levels, he was only in the early stage but with this amount of power, he would be able to contend with the strongest masters in this realm. This was due to his repeated enhancements of his cultivation skills and due to the increase in his soul power.

‘I’ll absorb these later, I should go…’

After stashing the broken slave collars he left this room. They had no lightning energy in them anymore but could be used to bolster his silver body further.

“Elder, what has happened…”

Zhang Dong was quick to return above ground. Before the guards could look into the dungeon prison below he was there to block the path.

“It's nothing, the prisoner was a bit tougher than I expected, I had to use some strength to get rid of him…”

The dungeon below was reached by elevator which led to a checkpoint. They were now at this point, this room had been previously cleared out by him which raised some concern with these men.

“Elder, where are the other guards…”

“Don’t worry about them, they need to do some cleaning, now let us depart.”

He gave the older while giving the two men here a stern look. They quickly clasped their hands and headed towards the elevator. The good part about being in this world was how the seniors were treated with reverence.

Now after reaching the foundation level his disguising technique was able to shrink down his body to mimic the White Tiger Clan leader fully. Only a core formation cultivator above the early stage would be able to notice this disguise.

They all headed up and before leaving he gave the order to not let anyone descend into the dungeon for the day. With this, he would have some time to go through this clan’s library and gather some information.

“You.”

“Yes, Elder?”

Outside he found some White Tiger Clan members lazing about.

“I need to visit the clan's library, guide me to it, junior.”

“Ah… of course elder, follow me.”

The young man looked a bit surprised at the order. Zhang Dong knew that the person he was impersonating probably knew where the library was. Luckily for him, a junior would not ask any questions even if he acted a bit out of character.

“You may leave.”

The young man clasped his hands and was on his way. The building that he was led to was quite large and inside he found quite a number of scriptures.

‘They sure like to keep a lot of texts in this world…’

Even though this clan wasn’t really that big, they owned large buildings like this one. The city was also highly populated which in the magical land would be seen as gigantic. This structure had the usual oriental feel to it, with lots of dragons and qilin ornaments all over the place.

Zhang Dong’s system at least kept its knowledge gathering function but he needed to give each book a poke before it could be started. So he got to work, tracing his finger along with the book covers while moving next to the bookcases.

Most of it were just cultivation methods for the younger generation. Inner Aura techniques and a few Martial Master scripts. This was more of an open library, it made sense that the quality would be lower than what the inner circles had access to.

This didn’t matter much to him, he was mostly interested in the lay of the land. Where he was and where the Azure Dragon Empire was located from his location. After wondering for about thirty minutes he finally found what he wanted, a large world map.

‘This is different than the maps that I remember…’

He rubbed his chin while bringing up the image of the Azure Dragon Empire. It was a holographic image that only he could see. After moving it around a couple of times he was able to connect it to this map.

This Emerald Phoenix Empire’s west border somewhat aligned with the Azure Dragon Empire’s east border.

‘By the looks of it… I’m all the way here…’

It didn’t look too good, he was all the way on the other side of this country. The United Element’s Sect location was also on the edges. The traveling distance was immense and he wasn’t even a core formation cultivator so flight was not a possibility.

‘How am I going to get all the way there…’

He knew that the journey would be dangerous. This world was filled with many demonic beasts, evil cultist organizations, and people just waiting to stab a person in the back. The lack of his original cultivation was a problem, it seemed that getting it back would be the best option.

The new calendars that this empire offered also didn’t answer his question about time. His system window’s clock had also been reset along with the reboot so he had no idea about how long he was missing.

From his standpoint, some months had passed which in this world didn’t mean much. His sect still had some nascent soul elders to protect it. Unless the news of his disappearing was announced he didn’t see other sects attacking, not after he easily defeated those nascent soul elders on the sect meeting and also crushed that sword sect Patriarch.

‘I’m no use to anyone if I die… I need to at least reach the core formation level and gain access to my crafting abode.’

A plan formed in his mind, there was no helping it, he wasn’t strong enough. There were many Martial Saints that were about as strong as Core Formation cultivators from his empire. They would pose a large threat to him so he needed to be careful.

He needed to find a good place to cultivate, a place with lots of lightning energy. Then the other option was to gather items like those Thunder Stones. Luck was a bit on his side with that part as he was in a clan that studied the Dao of lightning.

It was clear to him that somewhere in the deeper regions of this clan there were cultivation resources that he could use. They had already crossed the line with him so he would not feel bad if he stole them all.

The only problem would be their strength, he felt like he should be on par with someone at the great circle of foundation establishment but that was only in theory. Was this Martial Grandmaster a bit stronger than what he believed? Only after clashing with someone like that would he know.

“There you are Elder, I’ve been looking for you, did you take care of that slave?”

While Zhang Dong was contemplating his next move he heard someone call out to him. The tone and voice sounded familiar. He just turned around while grasping his red beard, his eyes on the young man and the girl next to him.

“Mmm, it is done… Young master…”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate and vote [New feature]!

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 335

“Good work, I knew I could count on Elder Zhuao!”

Zhang Dong might have looked like this White Tiger Clan elder but he was unsure about his mannerisms. He only saw the man for a few minutes before snapping his neck so there was not much to go off of.

“How about that Xia Yanmei?”

“Don’t worry young master, everything has been arranged, they will be disposed of by my men…”

This seemed to have been the plan. This elder Zhuao feared Zhang Dong the most so he wanted to deliver the killing blow himself. The rest of the Snapping Turtle Clan weren’t as important, none of them had the strength to go against anyone close to a Martial Master’s level.

“Splendid! I’ll be sure to mention Elder’s name to my father!”

“To the lord?”

He answered while trying to sound ecstatic. Thanks to going through this library he had an idea about the power dynamics of this clan. The name of this young master was mentioned in one of the newer scripts.

His father was in line to be the next Patriarch while at the current moment the grandfather was still in this position. He was a Martial Grandmaster but was already close to 150 years old. His time was slowly coming to an end as these cultivators could reach about the age of 200.

This Dai Rong was the first son of the next in line to be the Patriarch. Due to this, it seemed that he liked to throw his weight around just like the other young masters from this world. The ‘event’ that Zhang Dong was in proved how little he thought about other people. In his eyes, this young master was already too rotten to be redeemed. Already many people had died because of him and if Zhang Dong didn’t step in there would be more carnage.

“Yes, we will return now Elder, my father has called for me, grandfather has called for a meeting! Maybe he will announce father as the new Patriarch!”

“Ah, of course, young master.”

He nodded at the young man that started laughing maniacally. The girl next to him didn’t look very taken back, she clung even more as if this young man was a meal ticket to a better life.

This was a good opportunity to look at how the clans in this empire operated. It was also dangerous, if his cover was blown he would be up against a whole clan of fighters. With his current cultivation, he was at least confident that he would be able to escape. That is if there were no Martial Saint level cultivators around.

For now, he followed after this young master, he knew that this elder was the main bodyguard but there were also a few other weaker clan members around for the ride. As they went through the city he watched as the people bowed their heads at this young man.

No one dared to meet his gaze and even the children were kept away. Dai Rong seemed to enjoy how much everyone was afraid of him. His cultivation wasn’t even that great, he was an Inner Aura middle realm cultivator. Even those apes that he fought against would be more than a match for this haughty youth.

While exploring the city with him Zhang Dong’s mind started to wonder. He remembered the world that he visited before. The people there seemed to have free will but some of them acted like a personification of tropes.

Was it the same here? Were these young men and women forced to act like this due to the world’s system? Or was this just the result of their upbringing? It could have also been a mix of the two and only more mindful individuals would be able to break free of the imposed programming.

His wife and the people around him did change somewhat after he appeared. They did become less bloodthirsty at least when around him. What would they do in a remote city? Would they revert to some pre imposed haughty programming if they met someone below them that was seeking trouble?

There was also another bigger problem on his mind. He remembered the king from that world. He was some kind of watcher left behind by whoever created these worlds. If that world had someone like that, then one could have been left behind here as well.

There was one person that fit that bill, the Azure Dragon Emperor that towered over everyone. There was also the monarch of this Emerald Phoenix Empire, it could be him instead, maybe even both he had no idea of knowing.

In that world, he was lucky enough to be much stronger than whatever the heroes were capable of. Thanks to that he could defeat that watcher in battle. In this world on the other hand he expected these watchers to be above the nascent soul great circle realm.

‘Maybe with my current soul level I could…’

“Welcome young master Rong!”

He snapped back to reality after hearing the young master’s name being raised. They had finally arrived at the meeting place. There were other young masters with their own bodyguards and retainers gathered.

‘I should focus on the problem at hand…’

He straightened out and started looking around. They were on the outside in some kind of garden, there was quite a large fountain in the middle. Around it, many youths gathered and were talking about some current events.

‘There are a lot of youngsters here, looks like this announcement will concern the younger generation…’

He didn’t think that Dai Rong would be getting the announcement that his father was becoming a Patriarch. Maybe instead he would have to contend with the other young masters for some special cultivation technique or cultivation resources.

The cultivators loved to put their younger generation against each other to thin out the herd. Only the few that remained at the end would be given proper management to advance further in life.

‘Hm… those people seem a bit different…’

In the distance, he spotted an old man with a long gray beard. He was wearing the White Tiger colors and he was walking with two other people. All of them were at the Martial Grandmaster level. The peculiar thing about this was that the two were much younger than this man.

“It’s the Patriarch, who is he with… those robes… The Thunderbolt Hall?”

‘Thunderbolt Hall?’

Even without knowing who this faction was, he had an idea. It suddenly became apparent what this was all about.

‘So… they are here to recruit the young masters and mistresses to their faction…’

This wasn’t anything new, larger sects sometimes sent out elders to recruit promising young people to their factions. The White Tiger Clan and this Thunderbolt Hall seemed to have a similar cultivation path, which made things even more obvious.

“The Thunderbolt Hall!”

The young master next to him looked at the two people that were walking with his grandfather with hungry eyes. It seemed that he also realized what this was about.

“All of you, pay your respect to the honorable seniors!”

The Patriarch shouted out after he arrived at the scene with the two Thunderball Hall Elders. One of them was a handsome man that looked to be in his mid-30s while the other was a woman of jade-like beauty. Both of them were wearing white robes, with the characteristic flowy long sleeves.

“I have gathered you all for this occasion to pay your respects to the great Thunderbolt Hall!”

Everyone including Zhang Dong bowed their heads while their old Patriarch talked. He was then promptly interrupted by one of the members from this sect.

“You don’t need to bow your heads, we can’t stay here for long and we came to do business.”

Normally it would be considered very rude to cut off the Patriarch from this Clan that ruled this city. No one could go against this powerful sect though so everyone had to keep their mouths shut.

“We will conduct an aptitude test for all the middle stage Inner Aura practitioners under the age of 19. If they manage to pass it you may join the next test for the outer Hall disciples!”

The youths eyes opened up wide as they started to sparkle. This was a great opportunity for their Clan but even more for themselves. Being part of a larger sect meant more cultivation materials, better techniques, and a possibility of reaching the higher realms of strength.

Everyone from this clan knew that they were just frogs inside of a well. Only if they were accepted by one of the larger sects like this Thunderbolt Hall would they be able to join the cultivation giants.

These sects liked to create trials for young members with high aptitude. They would go around picking them out from the local cities and clans. There was always an age limit as the older a person got the less they could achieve.

Zhang Dong was not interested in this test nor this sect. He did not have the time to dwindle here. The prison he left was empty and all the slaves were gone. He didn’t think that anyone would rush to this gathering as they did not have the prestige for it. It was safe for now but he needed to be careful.

‘I should avoid the sects for now… they probably have core formation level people in it…’

While Dai Rong was busy drooling at the jade-like beauty that was next to the man from that sect he started thinking. They would be testing all the youths and all of the big shot clan members were probably gathered in this very room.

Just as in any clan there were many people in it. He was looking at at least fifty youths that could be picked up by these two sect members. While they were busy with their tests, he was planning to slip away. He knew a lot of stealth techniques which would come in handy now.

“You will spar with each other, the winners will have the chance of coming with us…”

‘Great… they are going to host a tournament, I should have enough time to ransack this place…’

Zhang Dong smirked a bit while the White Tiger Clansmen started moving outside this area. They were probably heading to a place where they could spar. Dai Rong had long forgotten about his bodyguard that most of the time was hidden in the background. Thanks to this he was able to slip away into the shadows.

The technique he used allowed him to blur his body slightly. People that were below his cultivation level would not be able to notice him. Even the people on the higher realms would have trouble to discern him from the scenery. His hiding techniques worked even better if he remained perfectly still.

‘I should probably start with that one…’

In the distance, he saw a large pagoda building. It looked like the most important structure and was also in an elevated position. It was from the way that the Patriarch came along with the two sect members. It was probably his own house and would have the best cultivation resources.

‘I’ll get what I can and then I should leave…’

Zhang Dong’s body disappeared unnoticed by the masses, it was time to regain some cultivation resources that he had lost.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 336

Elder Zhuao or at least a person that looked like him was in the process of rummaging through the White Tiger Clan main building. While everyone else was busy cheering for the young masters and young mistresses he was busy trying to find things that had electric energy in them.

“Elder Zhuao? Why aren’t you with young master Dai Rong?”

“Um…”

Zhang Dong in his disguise was now looking at two guards. They were standing in front of a large door that led into the clan treasury. The men here were at the lower end of the Martial Master realm which was quite high for simple guards.

“Oh…actually the young master had tasked me to take one of his weapons from the clan’s treasury…”

“From the treasury?... but the young master doesn’t keep his weapons here...huh?”

Before the man could finish the sentence he felt a palm hitting his chest. The air was instantly knocked out of his lungs and he crumbled like a piece of paper on the ground.

“Elder Zhuao what are you…”

The other man pointed his spear at this elder that delivered a devastating blow to the other guardsman. Before he knew it, the same palm was descending onto his own chest. After the moment of impact, he flew towards the wall and left a human-shaped hole on it before also passing out on the ground.

‘It’s not very well guarded… they probably don’t expect anyone to do anything while the people from a powerful sect are visiting…’

He smiled a bit, this was the perfect chance to rob this place and make a clean getaway. Zhang Dong was aware of what happened during such occasions. All the big shot elders from the clan would be there and they would all watch.

They all had some promising youngsters in their own camp. All of them wanted to have ties to a larger sect, it would allow them to toss their weight around even more.

If a clan of similar strength went against them, they could scare them into capitulation by just having one of their family members be an outer sect disciple. Everyone knew that such a position was trifling but a large sect to save face, would not allow such a person to be looked down upon.

“Hm…easy…”

He moved over to the large gate and gave it a poke with his index finger. The door lit up in blue light but quickly dimmed before it opened itself uo. It had a simple low grade lock along with a protective formation. It was quite rudimentary for someone of his expertise.
The two passed-out guards were dragged inside this treasury and he closed the doors behind him. The time he had was unknown so he needed to work fast.

Spirit stones, weapons, armor, and even books were all in here. It was more of a large hall with closed windows than a treasury. Even before making a step forward, he could see that there were more formations to keep unforeseen guests away.

‘Illusory formation? Alarm formation? They even have a slaughter formation by that large pile of spirit stones…’

While slowly moving forward he started to disable every formation. The large pile of spirit stones was clearly a trap. Normally no one kept them out in the open as they were stored in spatial rings like the one that he had now.

If someone tried getting close they would be affected by the defensive formation. Even someone at the foundation establishment level late stage would not come out in one piece. While defending himself the alarm would also go off, this would bring all the elders from the clan here.

‘That’s all…’

It was time to clear this space out, the spirit stones made their way into his spatial ring. There were other storage devices here, all of them were locked but he could disable those later. All the scriptures, weapons and herbs were taken away. He had no time to cultivate or go through them just yet,

Just as he had thought this clan had a lot of cultivation resources related to Lightning DAO cultivation. None of them exceeded the mortal grade though, at most he could hope to get to the great circle of foundation establishment before reaching a bigger bottleneck. Even that was far-fetched as his new cultivation required far more to get up than it previously did.

After about ten minutes he had everything inside of his spatial rings. The one that he borrowed from the real Elder Zhuao had reached its limit. Luckily there were some more spacious spatial rings in this very treasure room.

He now had a couple of those Thunder Crystals as well as some Lightning herbs. With them as a base, he could actually prepare some pills that would produce better effects. There was even a nice pill cauldron here that he could use, it would be enough till he gained access to his crafting abode that needed him to be at the core formation level.

‘Now to get out of here… I should be in the clear…’

The two guards were left in the room with the treasures. He activated one of the formations that would force them into a long-lasting dream. With it active, they would not wake up unless someone entered this room.

On the outside, he slowly closed the door and reactivated all of the locks. He added a flair of his own, even with the person who had the key came, they would not be able to enter. They would need to either be more knowledgeable with formations than him or force their way in.

He heard some shouting in the distance, it seemed that the people were cheering out loudly. The young masters were probably giving their all in crushing each other's dreams for the future. It would not surprise him if some had prepared underhanded methods to achieve victory.

‘Would this be the place where the hero came out on top and got accepted into the prestigious virtuous sect?’

While trying to act naturaly he moved back through the corridor. The whole experience in the other world was still bugging him. If that world was made to work as a novel or game, was this one exactly the same?

The most bothersome point in this was the people here. In the beginning, he felt that it was just their upbringing. If he showed them the correct path they would see it and switch their mindset. What if he was wrong? What if these people were just cogs in a large clock and their ways could not be altered.

“Elder Zhuao? There you are, why did you leave? I need you to give me my good sword for my next battle! I’ll be facing that lowly bastard Dai Reng, he thinks he can take my spot in the Thunderball Hall!”

During his contemplation, he spaced out slightly, the young master that his persona was tasked to defend was now next to him. He was alone and looked quite annoyed, he could also spot some injuries here and there it was clear that he fought in some of the battles with the other youngsters.

“Your sword young master?”

“Yes, the Jian…”

Before the young master continued he stopped and pulled out a communication jade. Zhang Dong had one of them as well, this one was also lifted from the original Elder.

‘To everyone of the White Tiger Clan, Elder Zhuao has betrayed us, all of the slaves have been freed from the lower dungeon…’

It was a mass message to everyone from the clan. It looked like they had found him out a lot sooner than he anticipated.

“Elder Zhuao betrayed us but he is…”

Before Dai Rong could speak out he found his mouth being grasped by the person impersonating Elder Zhuao. Dai Rong started to squirm around while trying to signal for help but before he could he felt an invading force entering his body.

Zhang Dong infused the young master with his superior spiritual energy which made the young man unable to move. He quickly ducked into one of the many side rooms while still holding the youth by his face.

‘Damn, they know who I am… should I change into one of those guards…’

He started to panic a bit, changing into the treasury guards was one option but he did not take their clothes. He did not get a good look at them either and impersonating people he did not get a good look at would be problematic.

“I guess you will have to do for now…”

The young master on the other hand would be less suspicious. While everyone was looking for Zhuao, he would temporarily use this youth’s appearance and quickly leave. He could also try to overpower the elders that were gathered here.

This was a bit problematic as he could not move fast. He did not have any transportation treasures nor a flying sword that he could even utilize. How many Martial Grandmasters were here was also unknown to him. Then if a Martial Saint appeared he would be doomed.

“Don’t worry I won’t kill you… but your days as a young master are over…”

Zhang Dong had no pity for this youth. He was already over the age of eighteen. His behavior and character seemed to be cemented. Already people have died due to his actions so there would be no mercy.

Without being able to move, Dai Rong succumbed to what Zhang Dong had planned. The youth’s cultivation level was erased as his dantian was obliterated. This wasn’t quite the end as his face was next.

With other techniques that he had read about, he started to change the young master’s appearance. Dai Rong was considered a handsome young man but after a minute his facial features were average at best.

Zhang Dong did this as he couldn’t have them discovering the young man’s body while he was still here. The vocal cords were also damaged so he would not be able to explain himself to his elders. He would be seen as a commoner, nothing more than a mortal. What he could do now was live his life as a servant.

“You won’t be able to speak for a few weeks but not like anyone will believe you… Live your life as the thing you hate the most…”

With one last jolt of spiritual energy, he made the young man pass out. When he woke up his life would be over. No one would be able to recognize him, he would probably be reduced to being a slave or a servant. After being the reason for the downfall of the whole Snapping Turtle Clan this would be just the right punishment.

The robes were switched out once more and he let the passed out Dai Rong with some old clothes that had not much worth. For a final touch, he doused the youth with some alcohol. With some luck, the people that found him here would think he was some random drunkard.

Back on the outside he quickly made his way out of here, everyone was already aware of Zhuao so he expected more people to start patrolling.

“Ah, there you are, Rong’er!”

“Uh...?”

He replied while looking at a certain man that approached him. His appearance looked familiar as it was the spitting image of Dai Rong’s face just somewhat aged.

‘Oh, brother…’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord

Chapter 337

“Is something wrong Rong’er, you look a bit pale…”

“Ah no… I’m fine.”

“That’s good, I’m counting on you to win the position at the Thunderball Hall. With that, your old man’s position as the next Clan Patriarch will be secured!”

Zhang Dong in his young master disguise was about to jump out of the window while this man approached him. His true son was out cold in one of the away rooms. From what he knew, this man that was Dai Rong’s father was close to becoming the next Patriarch.

“Also, have you seen that treacherous Zhuao? He has betrayed us!”

“Elder Zhuao? No… he vanished from my side when the seniors from the Thunderball Hall arrived.”

“Don’t worry, we will find him, for now return to the central courtyard, we can’t have the seniors wait!”

“Yes, father…”

While looking for an escape route he saw more people coming. His ‘father’ ordered them to escort him to the place the test was taking place. There were two of them, all at the lower end of the Martial Master level.

Without being able to make his escape he was forced back into the large space where the ‘test’ was taking place. There he saw two youths fighting against each other, they were both holding swords that were giving out small sparks into the air. Their robes were all cut up and it seemed that everyone was taking things very seriously.

At center stage were the two Thunderball Hall elders. They seemed bored out of their mind while looking at the youths fumbling around. Zhang Dong could tell that these prospects would have not made it into his own sect even if they tried. Their form was bad and they were slow at reacting, it looked like two kids with sticks were just randomly hitting each other.

‘It would be better to just lose instantly and then run away…or should I...’

Getting involved any further than this was problematic. His disguising technique had been upgraded to an immortal level technique back when he had the points to spend for it. It would allow a person to hide their appearance even from elders two large realms above them. Only someone at the nascent soul realm would be able to see that something was off.

From what he could tell this Thunderball Hall was a sect that was similar to the old Huo Clan. Their strongest member would be someone at the Supreme Saint realm. These masters were slightly above the core formation great circle realm but not quite in the nascent soul level. If that sect even had someone at this realm was also up to debate.

‘No, I have enough items… can’t be too greedy.’

This sect probably had lightning element resources as well. If he wasn’t strapped for time he could very well pretend to be a young disciple. After gaining some trust and cultivating more he could ‘borrow’ some resources and finally head home when he gained the ability to fly on a sword.

‘I’ll just lose on purpose, can’t keep pushing my luck.’

Zhang Dong had already taken a lot from this clan. That treasury was probably not everything that they had but it probably amounted to a big chunk of their savings. The rest would probably be some trashy techniques that the Patriarch’s attained which he didn’t need.

“I...yield…”

The fight was over and one of the young masters was victorious over the other. The fight lasted for a while and was kind of a slogfest.

“Good… with this only sixteen candidates remain, continue.”

The Thunderball Hall elder waved his hand while still looking bored. He was not giving the youths any time to take a break. It was obvious to Zhang Dong that he just wanted to get this over with.

“Of course seniors… start the next match! Dai Rong, Dai Reng!”

He would be the first to begin this round, his opponent was the young master that Dai Rong was previously complaining about. By the naming sense, this was either a brother or some close cousin.

“Finally, I will be able to crush you while all of the elders watch!”

His opponent was also quite handsome with similar facial features to this Dai Rong. The biggest difference was the lack of long hair which was just at neck length. His opponent was holding a two-edged sword, similar to what he found in Elder Zhuao’s spatial ring. He had replaced it for Dai Rong’s ring for now but he did not intend to use a weapon.

“You’ve been awfully quiet, already shaking in your boots before your tragic loss?”

Zhang Dong didn’t reply much as he was trying to lower his cultivation level. If his fist connected with this kid at full strength he would just explode into chunks of meat paste. With his silver body, he could not be harmed by this youth at all, even the elders from his clan would have a hard time even giving him a scratch.

“Don’t listen to him Rong’er, show him what I taught you!”

“Be victorious Reng’er!”

His father cheered him on from the side while another man did the same for the other youth. He could feel that the two old men had similar strengths and were close in age. They might have been brothers by the similar appearance, maybe even fighting for the position of Patriarch.

“Take out your sword!”

“I don’t need it for someone like you…”

Zhang Dong replied while in Dai Rong’s form. He feared that his superior swordsmanship would be a dead giveaway. There was also the problem of containing it as he feared killing the youth by mistake.

“You dare?”

It seemed that his reply was taken as a taunt instead. His opponent’s face went red and he charged forward while Zhang Dong waited in one spot. After absorbing some of the technique books here he knew what these youths would mostly be using.

He took on a battle stance, his hands in front of him in the form of flaws. This was one of the more basic techniques that was called ‘White Tiger Palm’. It had a few forms that would not give him trouble when being performed.

“White Tiger Palm?”

Some of the elders rubbed their beards at the strange approach that Dai Rong was taking. This technique was quite rudimentary and mostly just a set of clawing and palm techniques with nothing much to them. It wasn’t very flashy nor was it good or bad in any way shape or form. It seemed to them that Dai Rong was not taking his opponent seriously.

‘I need to make it believable… I’ll dodge his charge and hit him a few times to not look totally incompetent…’

This was a good chance to lose, his opponent was some kind of rival. This meant that it would not be seen as strange if he lost to him. It was also one of the beginning matches so he could pretend to be injured and then escape.

“Take this Thunder sword!”

Dai Reng’s sword started giving off faint sparks of electricity while he performed a vertical slash towards him. He wanted to laugh at the technique's name, as the sword was far removed from being coated in lightning energy.

First, he needed to show off his own skills so at the right moment he dodged the blade’s attack. Then his palm descended towards Dai Reng’s chest. He added the minimal amount of Qi into it as the people here would be able to tell if he didn’t try at all.

‘Just a little tap should be enough…’

Regretfully the technique that he was performing was created with this Empire’s cultivators in mind. Even the slightest infusion of his superior lightning Qi into it produced a different result than he expected.

What the elders saw was a bright flash of light followed by a loud thunderous roar that mimicked that of a tiger’s. The palm connected with Dai Reng’s chest, sending him flying. The robes on his back exploded while showing some burns in the form of a tiger claw on the youth’s back.

“Reng’er… NO!”

The young master’s father quickly jumped in to save his son. He grabbed him mid-flight and started doing his utmost to remove the invading electric energy from his body. Even he, someone that was a lower level Martial Grandmaster was having trouble in doing so.

‘What the hell…’

Zhang Dong stood shocked while looking at his palm. He didn’t think that this low-level technique would react in this kind of way. His aim was to have his opponent retreat slightly before the fight continued in Dai Reng’s favor.

“Was that really our White Tiger Palm?... could it be… the Secret Thunderous White Tiger Palm?... how did the boy learn it… The technique has been lost to us for centuries now…”

The elders mumbled with each other while the people from the Thunderbolt Hall’s finally showed some life in those bored eyes.

“Rong’er… how… you didn’t even tell your old man that you mastered the Secret Thunderous White Tiger Palm! Well done!”

His ‘father’ looked quite pleased by the turn of events. Everyone was looking at his son as if he was some kind of prodigy. It looked like he had figured out the proper way of restoring an old lost technique.

‘Shit…’

Zhang Dong started to sweat and also remember that time when Beatrice was going through her tests. It seemed that unless he played dead without even grazing his opponent he could risk winning. Due to this, he decided to play it up, they thought he performed some kind of secret art so he would stick to it and retire early.

He clutched his chest as if he was in pain and went down to his knees. His face started to go pale, sweat dripping from his chin onto the ground while everyone watched in fright.

“Rong’er? What’s wrong?”

The father was quick to appear to support his collapsed son that was in the moment of faking to pass out. The plan was to now make it seem that he used too much Qi for that one attack and would not be able to continue on with the tests.

“F-father, I’ve used up all of my spiritual energy… I… I don’t think I’ll be able to continue…”

It was easy for him to fool these low-level cultivators. He was able to lower his own cultivation and his father after examining would see his son’s cultivation be minuscule.

“I’m sorry, I think someone else will go with the Seniors…”

He started to close his eyes and pretend to pass out. If he wasn’t able to continue then the Thunderball Hall would not take him.

“Rong’er?”

He could feel his ‘father’ picking him up from the ground. Now he only needed to be carried away to a more secluded room to make his escape.

“Wait!”

“Senior?”

‘Hm?’

With eyes closed, he could hear one of the Seniors from the sect approach Dai Rong’s father.

“This trial is over, we will take this youth with us!”

‘Eh???’

He wanted to open his eyes and ask what was going on. Luckily for him, the Senior from the Thunderball hall continued with an explanation.

“We have seen all of your juniors fight, none of them have the talent of this youth, it doesn’t matter that he can’t continue with the test, he is clearly the most promising of them all!”

With that, he had earned the prestigious position of Thunderball Hall disciple, his escape plans were put on hold for now...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 338

Lin Qiao and Zhou Dongmei were the names of the seniors that hailed from the Thunderball Hall. After he showed them a glimpse of his aptitude they were eager to add him to the juniors of their sect.

“Take care Rong’er!”

“Ah… yes, goodbye father…”

They were now ready to leave. Luckily the two didn’t want to stay for even a day longer in this small city. Thanks to this he would be able to finally leave. The bad part about this was that he was now stuck with these two Martial Grandmasters. He felt that he could take them in a fight but not like he wanted to start one here.

‘The journey to their sect will probably take a bit.’

He believed that these two were probably traveling on foot or in some kind of caravan. With this in mind, he could sneak away during the night. With his techniques that could hide him in the shadows, it would be easy to just leave.

Zhang Dong also did not have any malice towards these two here. They were just doing their job of picking up new recruits from the smaller clans. There was no reason for him to cause them harm.

‘If I vanish during the night, they might just think that some beast took me away while they slept and not look into it too much…’

Dai Rong was still someone from a smaller clan. Even though he was like a prince here, outside the city he would be nothing special. If he vanished and his body was not found, no one would really bother to look into it. It was just how this world was set up, danger lurked everywhere and junior members were prone to disappearing.

“Junior, let us depart, we will instruct you on the way there.”

“Yes, Senior.”

It felt strange to bow his head to this random lower sect elder but he needed to do it for now. The group of three left the White Tiger Clan main house. The original young master’s body had not been discovered and they were in the process of going into the treasure room. He was in the clear as now with the sect members around, no one would bother him in the slightest.

This didn’t stop the White Tiger Clan members from following them all the way through the city. They also made a loud scene as they wanted to know that a member of their family had made it into a prestigious sect. With this their reign over this area was secured, no clan would be able to do anything about it out of fear of retaliation.

‘Wish this ends fast… also where are we going… this isn’t the exit gate from the city…’

He expected to go towards an area where there were caravans, maybe there was another group of junior sect members outside waiting for them. These two also weren’t at the core formation level so the ability of flight should have not been something they were capable of.

Instead of the gate that led out of the city, they climbed up some kind of building. It was quite high and reached up to a hundred meters. On the top he found something interesting, it was a boat that was anchored to the building. Why was it anchored? Because it was floating around and even the wind here made it move from side to side.

“Junior you look surprised, this flying treasure is one of the many wonders you will learn to accept at your new home!”

Lin Qiao proclaimed while acting quite proud. Zhang Dong was more surprised by the fact that this item was given to these low ranking elders than the flying boat itself. It was quite small, the size of a bass boat with only four seats.

He could feel some kind of item inside of it, probably making it float. Compared to the Argonaut 1 that he created, this looked more like a toy. The man looked to be quite proud of this little thing as if it was a great treasure.

“Surprised? Ah yes, Senior…”

The woman didn’t say much, she just quickly jumped up onto this boat and took a seat. She took out a large umbrella to cover up from the sun and it seemed that she was ready to go. Zhou Dongmei gave off the vibes of that unapproachable jade beauty, even this man that was here with her was continuously glancing at the good parts.

“Get on junior, we must hurry back to the sect!”

Zhang Dong looked behind him, some White Tiger Clan members were there. Dai Rong’s father looked quite proud. He even started feeling bad about stashing his son in a room without a cultivation base.

When he left this spot this man would never see his son ever again. Though he knew that it was also this man’s fault for bringing him up like this. Even if this world was affected by some sort of programming there were ways to change it.

His own family members from the Zhang Clan changed their ways. The two disciples that he brought up could have ended up as haughty young masters but instead, they treated people as equals. The only one that he couldn’t really change was his grandfather that continued to ‘grow’ the family even if he told him not to, many times.

He hopped onto the small boat that looked more like it was meant for fishing trips and they blasted off into the sunset. The boat was not as fast as a flying sword would be, but still much faster than walking. He could tell that Lin Qiao was inserting his Qi through his legs into this boat to move it around. The rest was done by the item itself.

‘It's more similar to the flying boats from the magic world than from here…’

In his empire, it was hard for anyone below the core formation level to use such a thing. Most sects didn’t even bother to create small flying vessels like this one. It was better to just use all the resources to create a large one that could transport more people. Here on the other hand it seemed that the resources to make the boats float were easier to come by.

Now, this was a problem, he hoped that they would be traveling by something else. Maybe even camp out in the woods at night where he could remove himself from the equation. Now he was sitting next to the haughty-looking jade beauty. She did not talk and the man called Lin Qiao was quite the reverse.

He continued to babble on, explaining how lucky Dai Rong was for being accepted as a trial disciple. Yes, he was only a trial disciple; it was possible to get kicked out. From the explanation given, the young prospects would need to go through some kind of boot camp. Their physical capabilities would be tested, the ones that gave up or couldn’t keep up would be thrown out.

‘Should I just go there and quit mid way…’

The idea to remain with these two all the way till they got to the sect was tossed away rather quickly. He had already taken too long, he was afraid that the more he hesitated the more problems would spring out along the way.

‘I bet that when I get there, it will be even harder to leave…’

There were probably elders that were at the core formation level of power there. Escaping would become hard and the days could continue until finally, a chance was there. He knew that new disciples were looked down upon and not trusted. It wouldn’t be far-fetched if they all were forbidden from leaving the sect for many years as a test of loyalty.

‘The guy is slightly stronger than this girl… I should take him out first…’

They continued flying and they were now far away for him to act. Previously he thought that he needed to reach the core formation level for him to be able to travel. Now, on the other hand, these two gave him the item that he desired.

Even though he didn’t want to steal from people that didn’t cross him, this was a dire time. If he returned home and regained his might, he would reward this small sect with some treasures.

‘If I knock them both down, they won’t be able to follow me…’

The plan was easy, he would just toss the two down from this flying boat. They were strong enough to survive the fall and then could return to the White Tiger Clan city for help. He would also need to take away their communication jades to be on the safe side. If they contacted their sect he might have found himself getting chased before he could change his appearance.

They didn’t seem to suspect anything, a good palm strike to the man’s back should put him out of commission. Then only the woman would remain, if he acted fast they should not be able to react in time.

He leaned forward while bracing himself, his muscles contracted as he was about to deliver the first hit…

‘Huh… what now?’

Before he could go through with his plan he felt something, there were other people moving their way. All of them possessed similar cultivation levels to these two people and he had a sinking suspicion as to why.

“Lin Qiao… Fairy Dongmei, Are you returning as well?”

A boat with two more Thunderball Hall elders moved closer to them. Instead of one trial disciple on that boat there were two. The two boats moved next to each other and Lin Qiao started talking to the man that called out to them.

‘Fuck… can I take four of them?’

He was sure that he could knock these two down that were close to him. The other two would be a problem though. At this moment in time, he didn’t really have any aerial capabilities. They would sourly give chase the only thing he could do was to destroy the other boat.

Then another problem arose, they would notify their sect members. All of them would swarm to this place. There was nothing but open fields and nowhere to hide. If this pair of elders was so close by, there could be more of them.

‘Does this mean…’

Unless he defeated them in an instant it was very likely that he would involve himself in some silly chase. Then if they fetched a cultivator that was at a similar strength as a core formation elder, he might be done for.

Before he could make a decision he felt another power source approaching. Soon one, two, and three more flying boats appeared. Each one carried a Martial Grandmaster level of cultivator; it didn’t seem like stealing the boat was an option anymore.

They traveled for about a day, in the end, there were fifty of those small flying boats. Some were larger and carried more trial disciples while most were the same size as the one he came on.

Soon they arrived at the meeting spot, the Thunderball Hall was starting to appear on the horizon. Lightning and thunder greeted his arrival and a large white snow-covered mountain. On it he saw some kind of large tower, the lightning bolts constantly hitting its tip.

‘I guess… I’ll have to rethink my strategy again…’

Chapter 339

Boats, many boats riddled the sky like flies around the fireplace they circled around a large stormy mountain. On one of these small vessels was Zhang Dong, his eyes glued to the strange structure in the middle.

The tower that he saw from afar stretched all the way up into the clouds and pierced them. There were many lightning bolts connecting with this tower. The stormy clouds circled around it while this tower absorbed these energies with what looked to be many lightning rods.

These rods were sticking out from this tower and glowing red each time the electricity made contact with them. This long tower went down and connected to a castle-like structure right on top of a snowy mountain.

Even from here, he could tell that this storm would be a good power source. If he was allowed to enter it and cultivate, he felt like he could be able to jump right into the core formation level. For this, he would have to make his way up to the very top.

‘Is it worth the trouble…’

Was the thought on his mind. He felt like he already overstayed his welcome here. The best thing to do was to just remove himself from the equation. He could already feel that there were some people above his cultivation level and he had to hope that his disguising technique would not be seen through. It was theoretically core formation proof but that didn’t account for special detection devices or skills that the people in this empire had developed.

“Is this the last batch of disciples?”

“Yes, elder Jingyi!”

While Zhang Dong was on the little dinghy that they called a flying ship he took a note of this Elder Jingyi. He was an older gentleman with long red hair and a well kept beard that was somewhat trimmed to pronounce his jawline.

He was clearly above the Martial Grandmaster realm, somewhere on the onset of the next Martial Saint realm. Zhang Dong did not feel comfortable facing somewhat of that caliber, at least not yet.

His spatial ring was filled with all sorts of treasures that he needed to absorb. Would he have a quiet spot to take in all the weapons to advance his body refinement to the next level? The spirit stones would grant him some system points that he could also directly spend on his cultivation.

For now, he needed to wait and hope for a chance to present itself for him. If push came to shove he already knew where he would be heading.

“You have all been chosen to be trial disciples for our Thunderball Hall. This does not mean that you are part of our Hall just yet!”

This old red-haired man started talking. He gave the disciple candidates the rundown while they listened.

“You all will be tested on your potential, if you can successfully persevere through the coming weeks, you will be able to join the other outer disciples! If you show talent, you might even be able to join the inner disciples and be invited directly into the hall building!”

At the finish of the sentence, the thunderstorm in the background started to rumble. It was clear that the inner disciples were allowed to go into that tower and cultivate with that lightning energy.

Zhang Dong theorized that those lightning rods were some kind of filtering treasures. They probably contained the chaotic electric energy and pushed them into the tower. There the cultivators could use it to cultivate the lightning that was now more controllable.

There was a long-winded speech about how everyone needed to behave and how they were not allowed to leave the sect grounds for now. This is what he had feared, that leaving this sect at this moment would become hard.

Without any means of fast transportation, if one of those Martial Saint’s decided to go after him he would not be able to outrun them. There were not many places to hide around here, they were high in the mountains with only snow and rocks. On foot, he might not be able to make it down this mountain top before someone noticed his escape.

‘I should relax… It's only been a day since I’ve come here. No one knows that I’m not this young master and don’t think anyone will care unless I start sticking out.’

For now, he decided to reorganize and keep himself hidden. Maybe during the coming days, an opportunity to flee would show itself. There was also the possibility of becoming an inner disciple. Which he would probably not have much of a problem with.

If he was allowed into the tower he would perhaps be able to absorb all of the electricity that it stored. Then after establishing his enriched lightning core he would just fly away on a sword.

He had lost his old spatial ring but there were some leftover items in his crafting abode that might still be there. Though he was not sure about his old items still being stored in his crafting abode. When the system got rebooted they might have been destroyed or used up to help him pass the barrier between the worlds.

“Show the trial disciples their new quarters, then tomorrow we will start the training!”

The long-winded speech was finally over and the red-haired elder flew away on his sword. The rest of them started descending down to the ground.

The main sect building was composed of that large tower with the castle-like structure in the middle. There were also many other smaller structures and houses around it going down from the mountain top. It made it look like there was a city on this large mountain but all the people living here were cultivators.

“You will remain here! An outer hall elder will come and instruct you at sunrise, rest well as you might not have an opportunity later!”

Lin Qiao and Zhou Dongmei were quick to leave after they dumped him onto the ground. Some other elder gave everyone an announcement while pointing to a large wooden shack. It seemed that this would be the place where these trial disciples would be staying.

While paying close attention to the surroundings he slowly followed after the youths. The doors to this large shack were quite squeaky and the inside looked quite minimalistic.

“What is this? Do they expect us to live here?”

There it was, the first complaint. One of the young masters that was brought up with a silver spoon started complaining. This was only natural, after spending years and being treated like little emperors they now had to live like servants.

This was one of the tactics that the sects liked to put their disciples through. They wanted to show them that they were nothing special and only the strong survived in the end. If the young potential disciples couldn’t follow orders, they would be quickly reprimanded and punished.

This looked more like a barracks for guardsmen than something that you would expect to find at a high-class sect. It was apparent that this youth here thought that he would get something like a cultivation cave for himself. These were reserved for inner sect disciples while the outer sect disciples had to always prove their worth.

It was a similar thing in his own United Element’s sect, but the dorms that they created for them would be considered rather lavish. The prospects had to share rooms but they were only in twos and could trade in their points for better housing and cultivation resources if they worked for it.

“Be quiet, the elders have ordered us to go to sleep and prepare for tomorrow!”

Another young master called out after hearing this one complain and quickly a shouting match between the two youths was started.

‘Ah… didn’t think I’d be part of one of these…’

Zhang Dong knew what was about to happen, the establishment of the pack leader. The ones that thought that they deserved the spot would soon show themselves. This was quite natural when a large group of young men gathered. They were quick to establish a hierarchy between each other but this meant that there would be bloodshed.

“You dare!?”

“Why wouldn’t I dare! This young master will teach you the error of your ways!”

A fight began and it didn’t look like the senior Hall members were interested in stopping them. He could feel some elders in the Martial Master realm looking from afar but they weren’t doing anything. This was probably seen as part of the course and if someone got injured during it, it would be their fault.

In the process of the fight, a couple of the bunk beds that were in this large shed were turned into splinters. Soon the young master that was complaining at the start was down on the ground and covered in blood.

It appeared that this young man was part of a group of three. And the two others jumped into the fray to attack the winner. He was not alone though and soon more bodies hit the floor.

The fight was even taken outside, this was a good moment for him to look at the skills that these youths had. They were all past the Inner Aura middle stage with the strongest being at the late stage. Dai Rong would be considered quite weak and at the bottom of the totem pole if he was here.

Within an hour of fighting, there was finally a winner. It was one young master with a larger frame than the others. He was clearly a dual cultivator with both body refining techniques as well as regular Qi ones.

He was part of a larger group of five that all made it into this outer disciple training ground. By being more coordinated than the rest they achieved victory over the youngsters that were mostly without any help. Some of the more crafty ones accepted this as normal and joined this group.

Some of the more stubborn ones were in the process of forming factions of their own. There were about forty people here. Twenty of them had joined this youth group while a few smaller groups that was probably going to try to get their revenge also formed.

They needed to bite their tongues for now but they knew that in the future an opportunity could arise. With that thought in mind Zhang Dong could see the various expressions of the young plotters. Some looked quite pissed off while some others just gave up right at this very moment.

‘Is it over? Great… I think I should try to sleep…’

Zhang Dong and a couple of youths remained in the barracks without going out. After this nonsense was over he moved to one of the beds and decided to meditate. He had just created his foundation pillar the day before and he needed to be sure that it was consolidated.

“Hey, what do you think you are doing? Who said you could take that bed, that belongs to me now!”

Zhang Dong looked at the person that was talking to him. It was a person from the strongest faction, it seemed that he had seen him occupied the bed. He knew very well that this youth was just trying to pull a power move on him to assert his dominance.

“You want the bed? Sure go ahead.”

He did not care about the bed though, he could just meditate on the ground if he wanted. There was no reason for him to stick out just yet and on the first day of getting here.

“Wait! Not so fast… you have a nice ring there… Give it to me!”

Zhang Dong looked at his hand that was now being grasped by this unknown young master. This spatial ring had quite the amount of treasure inside of it and he would not be willing to just give it away.

‘Oh, boy…here we go again.’

Chapter 340

Zhang Dong found himself in a bit of a predicament. He had hoped to avoid confronting the other young testosterone-filled youths. They were all just done pumping their chests out and now ready to collect on the winnings.

The Thunderball Hall did not care about any old possessions that they brought here from their old clans. Thus a lot of the young lords here were still in possession of their spatial rings. He knew of a little technique that could mask the insides of the ring but only when it was close to his body.

If someone decided to take it away then they would see that he had quite the large pile of lower grade spirit stones in there. It didn’t seem that this youth was the type that backed down though but he would try to resolve it without too much fighting.

“Are you ignoring this Zhong Yahui? I saw you cower in fear while all of us sect brothers fought, a coward like you does not deserve any cultivation resources!”

The young man named Zhong Yahui reached out with his hand. He was clearly trying to grab Zhang Dong’s wrist to relinquish him of his ring.

Even before Zhang Dong could use his superior diplomacy skills it seemed that it was over. This young man had a certain shit-eating grin plastered all over his face. It was clear that he was itching to fight some more, he was probably one of those types.

Some youths that had been beaten up by this young master looked on from the side. It seemed to them that another one would succumb to this bullies' strength.

For some odd reason though they all felt a small gust of wind. A little bit later they saw the smirking Zhong Yahui falling down onto his face while Dai Rong moved to the side.

“Oh… he must have tired himself out during the fights… how regrettable…”

Zhang Dong whistled to himself while pushing the passed-out youth away with his foot. While Zhong Yahui was focusing on his spatial ring he delivered a strike to his neck. He was a cultivator of a big realm above these youths, doing so without being spotted was possible. His arm moved so fast that at most the others could see a blur and feel the wind pressure.

‘No one should have been able to see what I did…’

He thought to himself while trying to avoid the curious gazes. It did look suspicious that one of the stronger trial disciples had passed out just like that.

‘I don’t think they are buying it…’

The youths continued to stare at him and the passed out Zhong Yahui. They were probably not so dumb to believe that a cultivator like that would just go down without a fight. He knew what they were thinking but not like he could do anything about it now.

“What happened to brother Yahui…”

The number two from the group of victorious youths appeared out of the crowd. He was just in time to look at the passed out Yahui who he now called a brother. This was Bai Tu who along with Yahui and Wang Yating who was the strongest had taken over this group of disciples.

“Someone explain this!”

He was quick to grab someone from the peanut gallery. Now after showing his strength he was not afraid to enforce the rules around here.

“He just fell over… I don’t know”

“How does he just fall over, did you gang up on him? I guess we didn’t crush you lot thoroughly!”

The young man he was holding on was already covered in wounds. He and most of the people here had taken part in the fight for the top spot and were now covering before the might of the top cultivators here.

“Senior brother I’m not lying, he walked over to that brother there and just fell over.”

“Oh?”

The number two from the trio of young masters homed in on Zhang Dong. He had sat down on the bed now and was sitting on it with his legs crossed. Even though he just wanted everyone to go away and leave him alone, trouble was heading his way.

“You! Did you do this to my junior brother?”

For someone like Zhang Dong that was now used to being looked up to, it was hard to get used to getting talked down to. This young man showed no respect, luckily he was talking with someone that didn’t take such things to heart.

“Your junior brother? I don’t know who you are talking about, I’m just trying to meditate, the elders told us to sleep, we should listen to their wise words.”

“The elders? Now listen here you…”

This youth was apparently not having it either. While talking he reached his hand out towards the sitting Zhang Dong. Then, just like before the people in the room could feel a strange gust of wind. Bai Tu was then seen falling backward with his eyes rolling back into his eye sockets.

“They really must be tired, all that fighting must have taken a toll on their spiritual energy…”

He smiled while talking to the rest of the people in this room. Even though he was trying to hide it, it didn’t seem like this group of youths believed any of his bullshit. They started inching away from the spot that he was sitting in. One might have been a coincidence but not two of the stronger trial disciples were down on the ground.

“Junior brother Tu? Junior brother Yahui?”

It was time for the third stooge to appear. Wang Yating was his name and he did not look like someone below the age of twenty. He already had a full-grown beard and was at least two meters in height. There was a certain scowl on his face as he looked at the two young masters that Zhang Dong had knocked out.

“What happened here, you better explain everything to this Wang Yating!”

The tall young man cracked his knuckles while looking at everyone gathered here. The people evaded his gaze but soon they started pointing out with their fingers. Even though their fear of Zhang Dong was growing they still found this brute to be the scarier one.

“So it was you? How did a scrawny-looking bastard like you manage to defeat my junior brothers? Do you dare face me?”

Zhang Dong started to wonder why his infiltration schemes always seemed to backfire. The less he tried to stand out, the more people looked his way. Now, this bear-looking person was trying to start a fight with him and he was slowly starting to lose his composure.

“You want to face me?”

“Who else is there, are you scared?”

“Hah…”

He knew that he should not let himself get yanked down to this person’s level. The young man was half his age, as a proper adult, he should refrain from being too violent. However, this didn’t mean that he wasn’t willing to show the rowdy youths a thing or two.

Slowly he stood up from his spot and took a step forward. Where his foot met was where he dropped one of the juniors of this senior brother. He just used him as a stepping stone to get closer to Wang Yating.

The large man at the sight of that became enraged. This was not due to Zhang Dong hurting his junior brothers in front of him, no. By stepping on them in front of their Senior Brother he was showing disrespect to him, it was a blatant hit to his face.

“You dare step on my brother?”

“Oh, I didn’t see him there, my apologies, Ya-bing was it?”

The large youth started getting red in the face, he was clearly not used to people making fun of him. Zhang Dong knew those types well, if someone stepped on his shoe he would have them beaten to an inch of their life.

“How brazen…”

“Do you think he stands a chance against senior brother Yating?”

“I don’t know… maybe those two really were just tired…”

The other trial sect members started whispering amongst each other while Zhang Dong and Wang Yating headed outside this shack. This time around he was not planning to end it with just a quick hit but there was no reason to destroy the barracks in the process.

‘Those elders could probably feel me do something anyway, I guess I can show them some of my strength …’

Zhang Dong was slowly abandoning the notion of leaving this place too quickly. From what he could tell there were protective formations as well as Martial Masters spread out everywhere.

The formation that was protecting this sect was at the core formation level, about the later stage. With his current cultivation, he would not be able to disable it even with the help of his knowledge. He would at least need to prepare some items beforehand and for that he needed something and that something was privacy.

His plans have shifted in attaining that, if he was seen as a genius he would probably be given his own private spot as an inner sect disciple. Even some of the outer sect disciples had their own cultivation caves or houses.

There were people watching from the outside and this guy he was facing was the strongest person here. This was not the only barracks with people in it, to get the spot he wanted he would need to eliminate all the other prospects by outperforming them. He could probably use some underhanded methods but those would probably not be needed.

“I’ll beat some respect into you!”

They were now outside and everyone was eager to see what Zhang Dong was capable of. The ones that lost previously were hoping that he would win, while also trying to see if they could witness some faults in Yating’s technique that they could later exploit.

Zhang Dong was wearing one of those flowy robes that he disliked. He didn’t reply to the taunts and Yating finally lost it and charged towards him with a mad rush. His muscles expanded and his fingers turned into blackened claws.

He was using some strange body refining technique that changed his hands into deadly weapons. He did a number on his previous opponents which were full of deep scratch wounds.

Regretfully he was fighting someone much more experienced than him. Zhang Dong was sure to drop his cultivation level to appear as someone at the late inner aura stage.

Yating went in like a savage beast but he was unable to connect with any of his attacks. For his size, he was quite nimble but each time he thought he would draw blood his opponent managed to slip away at the last second.

This was all a show, Zhang Dong was playing it up to the elders that were looking. He wanted to appear as someone versed in fighting by managing to evade each deadly blow after deadly blow.

“Stop running and fight like a man!”

“As you wish.”

Zhang Dong replied while stopping in his tracks. He swished his sleeve to the side and stuck out his hand towards his opponent.

“A battle of strength, would that satisfy you?”

“Damn conceited idiot!”

Yating went red in the face but quickly took Zhang Dong up on the offer. He grasped his opponent's smaller hand and began to squeeze while trying to break the fingers. To his surprise no matter how hard he tried, he could not hear any sound of bones cracking. Instead, he felt like he was stuck in some kind of vice, unable to pull his hand away.

“Did you really think you are the only one that studies body refining techniques?”

Zhang Dong's hand turned into a silvery color and everyone could see it appear metallic in nature. The bear-looking young man’s digits were promptly snapped and the crunching sounds could be heard by everyone here.

Yating started screaming while going down to his knees, then with a well-placed smack to the neck he was knocked out cold by Zhang Dong. The other young members looked on with horror at Yating’s demise. The monster that defeated them was easily dispatched by this unknown young man, putting him at the very top of their group.

“What is this, fighting between junior members is forbidden!”

Suddenly the Martial Masters that were hiding in the bushes appeared at the scene. There were three of them and they quickly dispersed everyone. The injured Yating was carried out into the infirmary while the rest were ordered to go to sleep. Finally, the first night at the new sect was over, what the next day would bring remained to be seen.

Chapter 341

“What do you think of the new batch of trial disciples?”

“Hm… there were a few promising prospects, like that youth with the large frame.”

“Ah, the elder has a good eye, his name is Wang Yating, he is already in the late inner aura stage even at such a young age.”

“Yes, yes. He might be able to make it as an inner sect disciple if he gets the right mentor. Is the elder thinking about making him his disciple?”

Two men were walking together. One was a somewhat older-looking old man, while the second was a taller-looking middle-aged man. It was clear that the older man was a more important member of the Thunderball Hall.

“Perhaps, if he shows me that he is worth it…”

The old man rubbed his beard while hoping to snag a promising youth for himself to guide. He was only an outer sect elder and was far too old to progress into the inner sect. The only hope of getting his foot in there was to shepherd a promising disciple.

It would be quite the honor to produce a powerful member of the sect. Even if he wasn’t able to make it, he would always be his master.

He wasn’t the only outer sect elder that was eyeing the young prospects here. The sect recruitment drive happened rarely and there was a limited number of seats in the outer sect for them. Each elder could take on multiple disciples and even if one made it into the inner sect it would be enough.

“Greetings Elder Yusheng.”

These two were greeted by another outer sect member that was waiting for them. It was time to inspect the youths and send them off on the morning training. Yusheng was responsible for managing several buildings filled with trial disciples.

There were about five hundred new recruits and he was responsible for a third of them. There were two other elders with the same status as him. The three would need to somewhat contend with each other.

From these five hundred youths, maybe one or two would be selected into the inner sect. If one of these outer sect elders would be able to guide such a disciple it was seen as someone that they could brag about.

Thus most of the time, these elders would pit their trial disciples against the other ones. It was seen as a game between the elder generation, the side that had the better disciples would be praised. The losers would in turn have to contend with being laughed at and seen as failures.

“How did the trial disciples fair during the night?”

“There was a fight as usual… one of the disciples showed promise, he managed to defeat multiple opponents in his own realm.”

“Oh, is that so?”

Yusheng asked while chuckling. The first day at the sect was always like this and the sect seniors allowed the disciples to take care of things with their fists. It was a good way to see which of the prospects were fierce enough to come out on top.

The life of a cultivator was a harsh one. The masters of this sect did not want anyone that was unwilling to fight. In the future, they might need these youths to help them in combat. Keeping cowards around would only weaken the sect.

Things were slightly different for the women cultivators though. They had a separate section at the Hall and were managed by their own female elders. The men did not intrude in their affairs too much but this did not mean that they would not be asked to fight when the time came.

“Good, have the disciples line up!”

The old man nodded and the junior that he was talking with entered the barracks. He began shouting and soon the trial disciples started appearing outside. There were supposed to be about forty new prospects here but the number had dwindled by some. This was acceptable as during the night fight some of the youths would be carried away to the infirmary to mend their injuries.

Even with some of them missing there were quite a few, they would all need to meet up with all the other young prospects. They all stood at attention with one youth, in particular, standing out. It was clear that this one was the winner of the nightly rumble, he stood in the front and the other young men were afraid to look him in the eye.

“Hoh, that must be that Wang Yating that you spoke about?”

“I… That’s not him… that young man was much larger and sturdier-looking… I don’t recall anyone like this being here. Don’t worry elder Yusheng, I’ll go ask right away!”

The elder looked to the junior and was now confused. The person that was rounding up the disciples was one of the Martial Masters that was here yesterday, thus a question was posed to him. Yusheng waited for the junior to go ask while the disciples waited without speaking.

“Big news Elder! Something unfathomable happened last night!”

The junior returned and started making a fuss about the previous night. Yusheng was informed about the big turnaround and how the best prospect was now getting his broken fingers mended.

It seemed that there was a hidden gem in the rough here who could easily beat a dual cultivator at the late inner aura level. This of course made this elder’s eyes shine with hope, there could actually be a genius in his batch of trial disciples that could help him raise his status.

“Yes, his name is Dai Rong, he comes from a smaller clan from the south… brother Lin Qiao was the one that brought him over… not much is known about him or his clan…”

The junior was a bit confused as this youth was nothing special. The young man had to have hidden his potential during the scouting process.

“Dai Rong… good… keep a close eye on him, report to me later.”

The elder rubbed his chin while also skillfully handing a spirit stone into this junior member's hand. Time would only tell if this Dai Rong was truly worth investing in. The young members would be taken through some physical tests first.

While this elder was thinking about what the future had in store for him, Zhang Dong was trying to avoid his gaze. He could feel the old man scanning him from head to toe which felt uncomfortable.

The previous night he had lost his cool slightly and beaten up three youths. He felt a bit bad for them but thanks to that the others were evading him now. Some of them were even trying to kiss his ass, calling his senior brother Rong.

The funny thing about this was, that the two from the trio that he fought were kissing up to him as well. They seemed to change their tune rather quickly after getting one-shot by him. He even expected them to want a rematch or say that he was lucky by sucker-punching them. Instead, he was now the top young master.

“Is that it? They just see me as another young master… so they are fine if someone from their group takes over…”

If he was seen as some kind of commoner not even coming from a clan, then maybe they would be playing a different tune. On the other hand, he did have some status, these lesser clans were at similar levels with Martial Grandmasters being a limit. It looked like this would make things easier, at least till the next youth came along to try to steal the crown.

“We will be running today, follow me, whoever can’t keep up will not receive any rations for today!”

Finally, the physical training portion of this boot camp was on the way. The person leading them was a Martial Master. With most of these disciples being in the middle inner aura realm, they would have a hard time following after the instructor. For Zhang Dong, this was nothing but a light jog.

He used this opportunity to look around this place. They were situated on the base of a mountain with not much around them. There was a forest further below but there was a protective formation before it.

Some beasts roamed those parts and isolated this sect from the outside. It was a peculiar decision to surround the sect building by untamed beasts but it did keep the lower level cultivators and mortals away. The only way to get it was to be either a strong cultivator or have some kind of flying treasure like those boats.

‘I’d need to get closer to this formation… but I don’t think that I can disable it with my current cultivation, at least not fast enough for them not to notice me…’

He possessed a lot of knowledge in disabling and creating formations. There were certain ways of opening in backdoors to them. They would require a certain password that he would have a limited time to deduce during an attempt.

This was an invasive process and required him to use his spiritual energy. It was similar to hacking as he had a limited window and power. This protective formation was your usual shield formation at the core formation level.

Luckily for him, this training jog took him through a large chunk of this sect. He was not impressed, this place was lacking in many places.

The buildings here were shabby and the servants seemed malnourished. It didn’t seem that the sect cared about these mortals that were probably taken here by force. These people took care of things like cooking and cleaning. They were also responsible for repairing things and keeping the whole place somewhat presentable.

The group of youngsters even passed by a couple of repairs in progress. These mortals instinctively bowed their heads the moment they saw the outer sect instructor.

When he compared this place to his United Element’s sect it was night and day. In his city, most of the people were smiling while working for the future in mind. With the merit system in place they had a clear goal ahead of them and were always rewarded for their troubles.

Here on the other hand the future was unknown. Even if they gave their all they would not be thanked. The Thunderball Hall owners probably thought that it was an honor for mere mortals to work for them.

‘I hope my sect hasn’t changed since I left…’

He was a bit concerned about what trajectory his faction would go towards. There were some people that he didn't see eye to eye with. He also kept to himself not really tying himself down by sect politics. Only when the elders could not come to a consensus would he give his opinion.

‘I need to gain access to a cultivation cave… I can’t cultivate like this…’

While everyone was trailing behind he remained about ten meters behind the Martial Master. He was clearly showing off his skills while quite a few young masters had to give up while trekking through these snowy paths.

It didn’t seem that Zhang Dong would be able to get away from here at a short notice. One problem was the protective formation and the second one was the beast-riddled forest. He needed to weigh his options before making his decision.

For now, it seemed that the Thunderball Hall had gained a genius new disciple that at the inner aura level was able to keep up with a Martial Master. This, of course, brought along some problems of their own...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 342

‘Just as I thought…’

“Trial disciple… what are you doing?”

“Sorry senior, I just needed to pass the spiritual water…”

Zhang Dong stepped out from behind a tree while fixing his robe to seem as if he was peeing behind it. In reality, this was an area where the defensive formation reached up.

This was only the third day of the disciple training and he was smoking the competition. He was the only one keeping up with the instructor. With some time left before the others arrived, he moved over to see if he could pass through the protective barrier without anyone noticing him.

As he feared this was a dome-shaped translucent barrier. When he poked it with his finger it would look like rippling water and he could see its outline in the empty space before him.

This type of protective formation needed some sort of key to open up. Probably the elders and trusted sect members possessed some kind of item that let them pass through it. There was also one main gate where it could be opened by the guards stationed there.

The easiest way to get out would be to get this key from one of the elders. The two that brought him over here didn’t seem to possess one of those keys as the Martial Saint that showed up was the one to guide them all in.

Taking the key from that core formation like elder would be a difficult task with his current cultivation. Even if he managed to swipe it, he didn’t think he would be able to flee fast enough.

“I know that you surpass the other prospects but you can’t make your seniors look bad!”

“I understand, senior.”

Zhang Dong performed a little bow while feeling a bit silly. The man before him was an early stage Martial Master, even with his lowered cultivation he could take him out with a slap. He needed to act as a proper junior for the time being.

“Senior… how does one become an inner sect disciple?”

“Inner sect disciple? You should stop thinking about such things and first get past the trial period and become an outer sect disciple! You should stay grounded before looking at the heavens. ”

The man crossed his hands over one another and started nodding his head while talking. He was telling this young disciple to lower his expectations.

“You really think I’m being unreasonable, senior?”

Zhang Dong asked while moving a step forward and glancing down. There he saw a steep cliff that was at exactly a ninety-degree angle. The rocks were flat and there were not many places that you could place your hands or feet in.

When he focused on his eyes he could see some young cultivators slowly climbing up while trying not to fall. They needed to push through the ice-cold winds, shards of ice and debris falling onto their faces while they ascended this treacherous cliff.

Zhang Dong and the rest of the trial disciples were mountain climbing today. This was a good way for the young men to show off their physical capabilities. Just like the previous days, he was the first one to finish and the next best person would probably need another half an hour to get there.

The Martial Master instructor covered his mouth while coughing. He knew what Zhang Dong was getting at as he was smoking the competition. From Zhang Dong’s standpoint, it was strange if he would not be picked up by some elder after showing what he could do.

“I…”

Zhang Dong with Dai Rong’s appearance looked with narrowed eyes at the Martial Master before him. The man might have been saying the right words but he was saying them to the wrong person.

“The junior does make some sense… you show more promise than the rest. Fine, this senior will tell you the ways of attaining high status in the Hall!”

The man was above the age of thirty, getting close to forty. He was still only a Martial Master and being an outer sect disciple was the most he could attain with his current disposition. This didn’t mean that he didn’t know the ins and outs of this sect.

“The easiest way to achieve the inner sect disciple status would be to do well at the disciple contest!”

“Trial disciple contest?”

“Yes, for this you junior would need to first be taken as a disciple of one of the elders. Each year this contest is held and the top three get elevated to inner sect disciple status!”

The explanation continued, it seemed that this was a multi-purpose contest. From the way it sounded, he wondered if it would have been another tournament. It was similar but not quite, there were various ways of attaining the favor of an inner sect elder.

First was the usual way of just being a strong fighter. There was no tournament but more of a challenger type of process. Every disciple that attended could force a higher status disciple to fight them. If they won, they would take their spot.

There was a certain ranking of all the outer sect disciples. If you managed to get in the top three of those, even top ten there was a chance of garnering favor with an elder.

The decision-making process was kind of vague. An elder might not have chosen one of the top three disciples if they were a bad fit for their particular techniques.

Then there was the pill forging competition. There would be one recipe presented to the disciples and they would have to create a pill. The sect would provide all of the resources and cauldrons. If the disciples failed they would have to pay for these resources.

There was even some kind of strange competition of combative dancing for the women cultivators. It was called Terpsichore arts, by moving in certain rhythmical ways these women could enthrall their opponents. It was some kind of strange dancing art that affected the opponent's mind and left them open for attacks.

Beast taming, formation creation, and even blacksmithing were all the ways that they could show off their skills. The more a disciple stood out the better the chance was for them to advance further.

This sect was quite similar in this as his United Element’s sect. They didn’t see combat as being the only important talent. Making pills and forging weapons was just as important. A powerful treasure or a pill that raised your cultivation faster might have been even more important than combat strength.

“Can a trial disciple take part in this contest?”

“There is no rule against it, but you’d have to get permission from the trial elders. Also, the disciples need to be at least half step into the Martial Master realm, that’s why I advise this junior to stay grounded!”

This made sense as adding untrained youths to the batch would just make the whole contest longer. No one here was at the Martial Master level with the exclusion of him that was hiding his power level. It seemed that he would need to make a breakthrough before this contest started.

“That makes sense… when will this contest be held?”

“In three days, that why it’s better to give up junior. Just complete your training and be accepted as an inner sect disciple, then after a year has passed you can try to achieve the inner disciple status, with your talent you might have a chance! Even if you can't do it through the contest there are other ways, just cultivate slowly.”

The Martial Master chuckled a bit while giving Zhang Dong’s back a pat. Zhang Dong on the other hand felt like he needed to get into this contest. The other option was to continue the training which would last two more months.

After being chosen as an outer sect disciple he would still not be given his own cultivation abode. Instead, he would be shoved into an even larger barracks building and everything would repeat itself. He would probably need to beat up other sect members and then actually do tasks for the sect.

The new outer sect disciples would be hired by the mortals and the lesser clans. They would be tasked with clearing out beasts or crafting pills to sell at auction houses. It was somewhat similar to the merit system at his own guild but a bit less proficient.

In the way that even when they did great in their tasks they would not be promoted to inner sect disciples unless they did well in the next contest. No one was keeping the disciples to use underhanded tactics either.

The schemers would prosper during this year of waiting while slowly getting rid of their competition. There were many outer sect prospects that vanished during beast subjugations, swallowing poisonous pills or offending senior members.

He did not have the time to be part of any of this. The slowest way to get out of this sect would be to wait till he was an outer sect disciple. Then he could take one of those tasks of killing beasts that were outside the sect. This would probably take from two to three months.

The faster way was to get the attention of an outer sect elder. An elder like that could take him under his wing. Thus he could skip the trial period, he knew that some of those outer sect elders were already salivating over him. This would probably lower the waiting time by a month or maybe two.

This was still quite the lengthy option, the fastest way was to achieve the top of the next disciple contest.To be allowed to get into it, he would probably need to reach the Martial Master stage. The minimum was the half-step realm but he feared that being a trial disciple, he would have a hard time getting into it with just that.

“Junior what are you…”

“Senior, I think our talk has given me important insight, I must cultivate now and create my crystal mountain!”

“Insight? Crystal Mountain? How could you enter the Martial Master realm with that talk…”

The senior member continued talking but he quickly went quiet as he felt this Dai Rong’s aura spiking. It was clearly going over the later stage of inner aura.

“C-could he really be doing it? How can he create his crystal mountain with so little preparations?... It took me ten years…”

The crystal mountain that they were speaking of was something similar to a foundation pillar. The cultivator would gather all of his spiritual energy that he prepared during the inner aura stage and crystallize it. This would take the form of a giant mountain in their dantian. The larger it bevame the better the prospects of the disciple would be.

Following the creation of the crystal mountain, a crystal palace would be formed. The Martial Master would chisel away at this mountain to fashion it into a mighty palace. When the mountain crumbled and formed a beautiful castle, the person would enter the Martial Grandmaster realm.

This was all knowledge that he lifted from the White Tiger Clan’s library. He had already examined other Martial Grandmasters and Martial Masters. With his own knowledge and his superior hiding skill he just needed to mask his cultivation to look like the one from this empire.

‘I need to play it up…’

While in the lotus position he cultivated. The trial disciples that arrived at the top of the mountain looked in horror as one of their own reached the next level so easily. Other elders gathered as well to see the rise of the next genius, Dai Rong’s name was now slowly being spread through the whole Thunderball Hall, his meteoric rise was about to start...

Chapter 343

“How can this be… Is that the sacred lightning aurora and that color… golden?”

A group of Martial Grandmasters was looking up to the sky. From a certain side peak of this Thunderball Hall, something magnificent was happening. They could feel it, someone was taking their first real step into becoming a true cultivator.

People in this empire were only really considered full-fledged cultivators when they achieved the Martial Master realm. The Inner Aura realm was considered a baby step in the right direction but going further would cement them as a real master.

They were all looking at a particular phenomenon. The heavens were dancing, the clouds gathered and lightning energy crackled as a new Martial Master was born. This was truly a cheerful day for this sect as it was one of their own.

“Who could it be… was there someone from the outer sect disciples that was this exceptional or perhaps it was one of the new recruits?”

While some senior members and elders started discussing, some of them headed for that mountain peak. The direction this spiritual energy was coming from was where the trial disciples went through their training, it had to be one of them.

Elder Yusheng was one of the first ones to arrive. He was responsible for this batch of trial disciples and was quite ecstatic to see who was advancing their cultivation. Two other elders arrived soon after but were halted by Yusheng.

All three of them were standing on flying boats as none of them had achieved the Martial Saint realm.

“Stop, we must not disturb the junior disciple from advancing into the next realm!”

The two elders looked at this Yusheng and then at the person that was radiating the strange Qi. These two elders just like this one were responsible for different batches of trial disciples. The three depending on how the trial disciples did would receive better cultivation resources from the sect as well as more prestige.

Yusheng knew this, he had to protect the trial disciple while he was the most vulnerable. Even though they were all from the same sect, this didn’t mean that others would use underhanded methods to gain more power for themselves.

If these two were left along with his disciple he knew that they would try to make him join their sides. Then if he refused they might act rashly, even doing something that would be otherwise forbidden.

“Who is that young man?”

One chubby elder asked while rubbing his second chin.

“Did you give some forbidden techniques to people from outside the sect before they joined?”

Another hooked-nosed elder commented while looking at the youth that was transcending into the Martial Master realm.

“What are you babbling about you old fart? You did that a few years ago and got caught by the sect, now you are trying to accuse me with no evidence!”

Yusheng furrowed his eyebrows. The elders here were highly competitive, they did sometimes sponsor some good prospects in hopes of them achieving higher status later in life.

The sect mostly frowned upon such things as most of those youths grew up with a shaky foundation. Their rise was fast but they quickly found themselves at a bottleneck that they could not easily break.

When one used secret items and many pills to quickly reach new heights without any restraint it would mostly backfire. Thus these two were suspecting foul play and the youth before them just being another tiger with rotting teeth.

To them, it seemed that this elder Yusheng gave the youth some treasure or pill. With this cultivation phenomenon now being out in the open, the boy would garner attention. If he advanced further and became an inner disciple, Yusheng would garner more rewards.

“You want evidence? Do you really think we were born yesterday, how could this youth without a name produce the secret aurora without any help?”

“Yes, hand him over, we will check if he achieved this feat by his own merit!”

Yusheng’s face contorted from bewilderment into a rage. He knew that if he handed the youth over he could end up crippled or even worse, he might get bought out by one of these two idiots.

“You think I was born yesterday? The disciple stays here, if you don’t like that he is under my watch, go discuss it with the high elders!”

The high elders in question were people at the very top of the Martial Grandmaster level and ones even above them. The disciples could not be handpicked by these elders, they were all assigned by higher parts of the sect and these two knew it as well.

“The high elders…”

The two flinched a bit as they knew that they would achieve nothing when talking with the top members of the sect. The two stared glaring at Yusheng while down below the glow started to fade.

“He is done… he truly achieved the Martial Master level and he is not even twenty years of age!”

Yusheng turned around to make his way down to the youth that just achieved the breakthrough. He knew that the two idiots behind him were up to no good but they would not do something stupid while so many people were watching.

“Make way.”

He swished his sleeve as people looked up. The Trial disciples and the instructor were standing around this youth that achieved the breakthrough.

The youths parted to the sides while clasping their hands. By the robe that Yusheng was wearing all of them knew that he was an elder from the sect.

It was clear why he was here as he headed straight for the young man that was still in the lotus position. Suddenly the youth opened up his eyes, they crackled with golden lightning for a second before the glow faded. Even this elder that was a Martial Grandmaster flinched slightly. Even though this power was below him, its quality was far above his own.

“Young man… state your name.”

The young man before him looked up, there was a small pause but soon a very soft-spoken voice followed suit.

“Dai Rong, Elder.”

He slowly rose from his spot and performed the usual small bow while clasping his hands. Yusheng felt that something was off, he was the superior here but for some reason, he felt that this person before him outranked him.

“Ahh… disciple Dai Rong, I must congratulate you on your breakthrough, may I check for any faults?”

“Elder wants to check this disciples' disposition?”

Yusheng nodded. This was slightly intrusive but the young man before him did not have the right to refuse. He was not a disciple of any elder in particular. In a world where might made right, he needed to go along with the elder’s wishes.

“Yes, I must examine your crystal palace for flaws…”

Dai Rong nodded and Yusheng moved over. He grasped the young man by the shoulder and started to concentrate. The first moment he felt a little jolt that was a bit odd but the feeling subsided within a fraction of a second.

What he saw was a magnificent crystal mountain that reached up high. When he compared it to his old crystal palace when he broke through, then this one was a true mountain while his was more of a small hill.

“Magnificent… such talent and potential.”

What he saw was a giant golden mountain of crystals. Each person had a unique-looking mountain, some were more pointy while others were wider. The more jagged and covered with cracks it was the tougher it would be to produce a good crystal palace afterward.

This one on the other hand looked smooth and pristine. The crystals were nicely packed and without flaws, what kind of palace would be made from this he could only speculate.

‘I must make him my disciple… even if for a while… if he has the time to grow he could even become a high elder… maybe even a star elder!’

The man thought while spacing out, he was snapped back to reality only after Dai Rong spoke out.

“Is everything fine, Elder?”

“Uhh… yes disciple, everything is fine.”

The man coughed into his hand and straightened up his clothes. He then struck a gallant pose and was about to give the youth the master and disciple speech.

“Young man, there comes a time in the life of a cultivator when they have to make a decision…”

Before he could continue the two elders that were looking at everything unfold descended from their flying vessels.

“Halt! Not so fast you rat!”

“Who are you calling a rat, you oversized pig!”

Yusheng turned around, he had characteristic buck teeth and everyone knew that he hated to be reminded of it. The fat elder and the one with the hooked nose gathered around Dai Rong and didn’t even ask before examining his desposition.

“By the Patriarch… what is this… you must become my disciple!”

“Don’t listen to him young man, become my disciple instead!”

The two were quick to start arguing about who would be getting Dai Rong as their disciple. A person was allowed to have more than one master but there was a special meaning behind the first one.

Even if the disciple attained more in their cultivation than their master they were supposed to offer them respect till they died. This was also why these three foxes were salivating about the opportunity of getting this genius to be their disciple.

The other trial disciples looked on with envy as the three old men fought for one no-name disciple. They knew that he was stronger than they were but were still hoping to nab themselves a good master and advance above Dai Rong.

“Elders please calm down, I’m just trying to focus on my cultivation, I’m not sure If I’m worthy of being accepted as a disciple of any of you prestigious elders…”

Dai Rong finally spoke up. He started rubbing the back of his neck while holding his head down as if he was shy. The three elders turned to him, the youth looked quite bashful but then he continued to speak.

“But… it’s hard to focus on my cultivation with all these other trial disciples around…”

“You have a hard time focusing on your cultivation?”

Yusheng asked while eying the other two elders.

“Yes, it would be really nice to have a secluded place to cultivate… but I’m just a trial disciple, I’m not worthy enough of such a place...”

The three old masters looked at themselves before each one started shouting.

“The disciple wants a place to cultivate? You can have access to my personal cultivation cave!”

“You can use mine instead, it’s much better!”

“No, you can use mine, I’ll even lend a maidservant to the disciple to tend to his needs!”

The three started to argue once more, at this time Zhang Dong was rather glad that he dropped the facade. He was not getting anywhere by hiding his strength, thus he now decided to show it off instead.

His roots were unknown so he could just tell everyone that he was holding back this whole time. He was now a Martial Master so he wouldn’t need to hide his cultivation as much.

‘Great… I should be able to get a personal cultivation abode thanks to these greedy old farts…’

He was not planning to accept any one of them as his master. For now, he would lead them on and take part in that competition in a few days.

“Great elders please calm down, I’m really not worthy of your time. How about we do this, I’ll come to take a look at all those cultivation caves and decide on one then?”

The elders looked to themselves and nodded. If they continued like this a fight would probably break out.

Soon the trial disciples saw Dai Rong leaving on one of the boats. Their mouths were wide open as they couldn’t believe what just happened. The respectful elders fighting like ten-year-old children and the birth of a new genius. It seemed that the name Dai Rong would be spreading far and wide...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 344

“Hm… I think this one will be fine…”

“I knew the junior disciple has a good eye for quality!”

“Junior disciple Dai… why don’t you reconsider, I’m sure I could…”

“Enough with your babbling, the young one has made his decision!”

The three elders that were responsible for the trial disciples were arguing once more. Zhang Dong was now inside a cultivation cave. It was a somewhat spacious cavern drilled into the side of the mountain.

There were several others like this one scattered all over the place where elders and seniors could cultivate in peace. On the ground, there was a guard building that would watch over the cultivators and not let anyone disturb them while they cultivated.

He didn’t really care much about which one it was but this elder Yusheng seemed desperate in grooming him into a personal disciple. He felt that he could talk him into lending him this place temporarily.

The other cultivation abodes didn’t look much different than this one. The three were quite equal in all regards, this was also probably why they were so serious about nabbing him as a disciple. Not like he would go through the master-disciple ceremony with any of them.

Zhang Dong’s plan was to stay here for a few days before the competition started without even mentioning that he would be participating. If he mentioned his plan he feared that the elders would try to block him from entering it.

They would either fear him getting injured during it, thus they would lose the golden ticket out of the outer sect. Then if he achieved greatness he would just be pulled away by one of the higher ranking elders instead.

“Yes Elder Yusheng, I must thank you for letting me stay here, I think I must consolidate my cultivation for at least a week. I also must thank the other elders for keeping up with my selfishness.”

He clasped his hands and bowed before the two. It was best to at least let them have some face even when he was refusing their proposal.

“Tsk…”

Both of them clicked their tongues before turning away and leaving. Yusheng just watched at the backs of these two long-time rivals while cackling.

“Young disciple, take your time, stay in there for a month if you have to, reaching the Martial Master realm is not an easy feat! You must slowly reinforce your crystal mountain so it doesn’t show any cracks. After it is fortified you may begin the process of condensation.”

This process of condensation or compression was a part of going further beyond the Martial Master realm. In this empire instead of producing more and more foundation pillars, the cultivators would compress their crystal mountain into a smaller size.

It was a forceful process that required a lot of spiritual energy. The mountain would go through two stages of condensation, then at the third stage it would be shattered and the crystal palace would be created in its place.

This was quite a unique construction, it was similar to a core formation expert's core. If he was cultivating in this empire he would probably fashion a giant golden castle that exuded lightning energies.

Even when the Martial Grandmaster created their crystal palace successfully, they would not be able to enter it. They would need to shatter its gates before being able to fully utilize it. The further they could get into this castle the closer they would get to the Martial Saint’s level.

That was all of the knowledge that he was able to gather from the clan libraries. What would be created to enter the Supreme Saint and the Saint Emperor realm was unclear to him. If it was easier to reach those levels instead of core formation and nascent soul was unknown to him.

Saint Emperor's started out at the level above an early stage nascent soul cultivator so it probably wasn’t. But the Supreme Saint level late stage might have been easier on the other hand which was interesting.

“I will then consolidate my cultivation Elder.”

“Yes, take your time, when you are done meet me at my private home. I will lend you some of my personal cultivation methods so you can soar above the competition!”

“Thank you Elder, I will Elder.”

Yusheng smiled widely while showing off his large front teeth. The old man looked like he had won a million spirit stones. He probably expected Zhang Dong to become his official disciple after he accepted those cultivation materials.

Taking personal techniques from anyone, was already a sign of accepting them as a half-master. Then afterward there was also a ceremony of kowtowing before him, this his own disciples had done a long time ago.

‘Finally, I’m alone…’

The cultivation cave had a large thick wooden door made from some kind of spirit wood. It was sturdy and would not break even if a Martial Master kicked it with all of their might.

This door slammed behind him while he inserted some spiritual energy into a little crystal above. It started glowing in a somewhat dim light that could be adjusted.

There was a bamboo mat on the floor and some shelves here and there., not really much to help him cultivate. The only thing that was here was space for when he needed to practice some techniques.

Next to a wall was a thick metal plate with some cracks in it. It was clear that someone was practicing some palming and punching techniques on it. If he compared this to the vast facilities of his own sect, it was rather shabby.

“Well… better than nothing…”

He finally had some time to sit down and remove the contents of those spatial rings. After making sure that Yusheng went away he started taking everything out.

One pile had all the spirit stones he ‘borrowed’, another one had all the weapons and metallic treasures he could use for absorption. Then he tossed the cultivation books to the side as he didn’t have much use for them.

After leaving this place he would try to sell them off at some auction house. He could very well improve on the techniques to get a better price. The first time he tried utilizing that White Tiger Palm he made a blunder but now he had figured out his mistake.

Now he could safely inject his own slightly different spiritual energy into the new techniques and not have them kill the lower realm cultivators. Though now on the other hand he wanted to stand out, he would need to show off some flashy moves during the competition.

He deliberated on trying to get the second or third spot instead of going for the top. This would be the safer option, all things considered, he would get one of the side's high-ranking elder’s attention while not being taken as the top prospect.

‘Yeah, that’s probably not going to work…’

Another sigh escaped his mouth as he grasped one of the weapons and started to absorb it into his body. After trying so many times not to stand out, he realized that it might be impossible.

During the fights, he feared that he would fail to control his might once more and still end up the one on top. It would save him some time to just go for the number one spot right from the start. He would just prepare himself for that and not be surprised when his big plan of not standing out crumbled into dust as many times before.

The weapons he was taking in didn’t add that much to his body refining skill. It had also evolved and required more. Still, there was a large pile of them, he at least hoped to enter the late stage of his silver body after taking them all in. If he was able to get into the great circle, then that would be even better.

With that amount of body refining, he would be immune to all Martial Grandmaster attacks. Even when facing a Martial Saint he would still be hard to kill in a close-ranged brawl. His body refining didn’t only offer him more resistance, it also raised his all-around strength and agility during hand-to-hand combat.

Most fights between high-level cultivators didn’t happen at close range though. Most of them produced some grand techniques that clashed against each other. Body refinement was mostly seen as a side technique, that was used by mostly stupid brutes.

While he absorbed the metallic objects with one hand he touched the pile of spirit stones with the other.

Spiritual energy detected, do you wish to absorb it Y/N?

The system message popped up as it used to. Even back in his sect days, he didn’t use this option as much after his system changed. Without the old shop, he had lost the use for most of these points.

For now, he took in a chunk of the spirit stone hill till he had enough points to fiddle around with.

‘The conversion rate is abysmal as always…’

The first thing he did was try to raise his cultivation with the spirit points. Even while being at this lower realm the requirement was huge. The whole pile that he had here would probably at most push him into the middle foundation establishment realm.

‘Not that great with cultivation… how about…’

He picked up a pill from the side that he took from the White Tiger Clan. It was a thunder Qi pill that gave a cultivator a small amount of energy to cultivate their techniques.

While grasping it in his hand he looked at his system screen. He was pleasantly surprised that even without the crafting abode he could somewhat use his spirit stones to upgrade this pill. This would also be better than directly absorbing the points into his cultivation.

Thunder Qi pill [ Common, Middle Grade ] Do you wish to upgrade it? [ 100 spirit points ]

‘Nice…’

He gave up some of the points that he received to upgrade this pill to the higher grade. After a moment he had a perfect grade pill that was giving off a certain aura.

After popping it into his mouth he felt the electrical energies being injected and giving him some energy. It was not nearly enough for him to create a second perfect grade foundation pillar but if he upgraded some pills to a high enough mortal grade, then that could change.

‘I’ll cultivate for a day, then I must see when that competition is taking place.’

With resources in hand, he started to prepare. It would take him some time to stomach all these pills and weapons. After this was done, he needed to see how to join the competition.

From what the instructor told him, he already met the requirements as he had become a Martial Master. Now he just needed to see if there were some other requirements that he needed to meet. The competition was supposed to take place at the end of the week, which gave him a few days to prepare.

Chapter 345

Name :

|

Zhang Dong

Affiliation :

|

Zhang Clan, United Element Sect

Spirit Points :

|

450

Cultivation Base Qi :

|

Foundation Establishment [ Middle Stage 2 %] [ True Divine Golden Lightning Foundation]

Cultivation Base Body :

|

Foundation Establishment [ Middle Stage 87%] ( Silver Body+ )

Techniques :

|

True Divine Lightning Path Cultivation Art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...

Dao :

|

Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting...

Other :

|

Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes...

Zhang Dong glanced at his system screen which showed him his status. He felt like he was back to the beginning where this screen actually mattered a lot. Through the years his progress had slowed down and he focused more on understanding the Dao himself instead of blindly using this system.

It was still a great tool to be equipped with. The system was able to scan his body and the bodies of others. Thus it allowed him to prepare strategies to counter some opponents even on the fly.

But thanks to his lessened usage he was now able to cultivate as a proper cultivator. Even without the crafting abode, he was able to upgrade the pills that he lifted off his opponents. With their help, he was able to push his cultivation base into the middle stage.

If he was an average cultivator and with all these improved materials he would easily reach the great circle level, maybe even achieve the core formation-level if he really wanted to force it.

His cultivation technique had improved and paired with his increased soul power he was barely able to push it into the middle stage.

His foundation pillars expanded in number and each one was as large and girthy as the first one. With them giving him power he felt like no one below the Martial Grandmaster really would be able to contend with him.

There was nothing left in the spatial rings that was worthwhile besides the less valuable white tiger clan fighting techniques. The only use that he could have for them would be selling them at an auction house after he got out of this sect. There was not much that the disciples could trade in here and cultivation techniques were not one of them.

This sect mostly forced their disciples to abandon their old ways and be reforged in the dao of lightning. This was also why they only took in people below the Martial Master realm. Before this realm, the young disciples were more flexible.

They would look down on the ones that somehow used more unique techniques that were not approved by the sect. This was only a limit for the Qi cultivation, the one concerning the body was laxer.

His own body refining technique that made his body similar to metal was actually quite beneficial towards his lightning cultivation. It transferred and absorbed electricity quite well with the help of his Lightning Dao; he was almost virtually immune to these energies.

The only way for him to receive damage from lightning attacks would be if a cultivator's Dao of Lightning was above his own. This was not something that was very feasible as he had upgraded it past this world's set limits.

Even with the help of his system, he was unable to push past the Immortal great circle level. Was this something set up by the creator of the system on purpose or was it the actual limit of the person that made it?

‘No use worrying about it, for now, I need to focus on one thing at a time, I need more information about that contest and to sign up.’

The small mountain of spirit stones had decreased as he had used some of them to push his cultivation further. He had left some for payment, if there was a competition like this, the people that did not have any backing would probably need to give something up to participate.

He had spent one whole day in this cultivation cave and only after a week would his new ‘master’ come to bother him. Before he could be asked to become some old fart's disciple he needed to win that competition. Only then would he be allowed to enter the inner sect and try his luck at that large lightning rod of a tower.

The entrance to this cultivation cave had a large round door. He gave it a push and he could already feel that anyone below the Martial Master level would have a hard time opening this thing.

After the door swung open he was greeted by a cold breeze. The air around here was cold and rather thin, this made it a harsh environment to live for the mortals working here.

With a little step, he descended from this cultivation abode. It was quite high up as well, reaching it without good climbing skills or a flying boat would be hard for the average disciple.

On the ground, he was seen by some of the sect elders. There were a few Martial Master’s keeping watch. They were all mostly composed of older outer sect disciples that didn’t have luck in reaching the Martial Grandmaster realm.

The youngsters with more skills didn’t bother with earning coins or spirit stones this way. This was just one of the many jobs that the sect offered to their disciples. It was a meager-paying job but for the ones, with not much skill it was a way to get by.

“Greetings senior.”

Zhang Dong did a little bow before the middle-aged man before him. The man looked up to the cultivation cave that Zhang Dong left and then back to the young man.

“Greetings junior… Elder Yusheng’s new disciple?”

The man asked while looking at a piece of parchment. On it, he had all the cultivation caves written down and to whom they belonged to.

“Did Elder Yusheng call me that? I’m not his disciple quite yet but maybe in the near future…”

Zhang Dong chuckled a bit while trying to play it off. It was clear that the old man had probably told everyone that he was his new star pupil by now.

“Is that so, are you stepping out?”

“Yes, I’ve gotten a bit hungry, I also need to see some things within the sect, I’ve heard that a competition will be taking place at the end of the week…”

“Ah, Is the junior interested in seeing this year's contest?”

The man nodded, he probably thought that Zhang Dong here was just interested in seeing the other senior brothers and sisters compete.

“Yes, I’m not sure where it will be taking place…”

“It’s not hard to miss, it's going to take place at the outer sect. Some competitions will take place in the outer courtyard, while the main bouts will take place in the inner courtyard… Then the competitions for lesser professions will take place indoors…”

The man was quite chatty as he described the structure of this event. Instead of a large arena, it would take place in more open fields around larger outer sect buildings that possessed courtyards surrounded by walls and other structures.

Zhang Dong could recall seeing some of such places at the lower parts of the mountain. It looked like a small city there with all the sect buildings and places where the servants lived.

Apparently, the whole outer sect had about thirty thousand people living in it, while the inner sect had a quarter of that. Even with this disparity in numbers, the inner sect disciples would mop the floor with the outer sect ones in any way shape, or form. Quality trumped quantity here, a person even one small stage above the competition could win against a whole group.

After the long speech, Zhang Dong bowed once and headed out into this sect. These cultivation caves were drilled into the mountain so he had to walk down to enter the thirty thousand large city.

About a third of the population of this sect city consisted of servants, slaves, and even mortals. They were tasked to keep everything clean while the sect members only focused on their cultivation.

The buildings in this outer sect weren’t all that great. They were mostly made from unevenly cut rocks or something similar to cinder blocks. The weather here was rather cold so each of the houses had some kind of chimney.

The peculiar thing about those chimneys was that they were not producing any smoke. Even when the houses lit up in a light that came from firewood, there was no smoke. As he investigated further he could feel that each of those chimneys had some kind of smoke filtering treasure in it.

Thanks to this no smoke was formed which didn’t affect the already thin air. The higher-tier cultivators didn’t actually need to be heated up. He was the same, with his foundation established he would be even able to run around naked without catching a cold.

‘Doesn’t look that bad but neither is it that good…’

He would have to give this place an average score. It looked similar to his old clan before he took over but there were fewer members and lacked a whole city with millions to manage.

With this change in culture, the cultivators here probably had a lot more time to practice and reach higher cultivation levels in a shorter amount of time.

‘This should be it…’

After asking for some directions he arrived at one of the outer sect buildings. It looked like an upside-down pyramid with half of it sliced up and balancing on four columns. When entering inside he found a person at a reception area.

There was a small line in front of it and some young men and women were standing in it. This from what he could tell was the place where you registered for this competition.

‘Hm…’

To the side, he spotted a little stand with some parchments. Some of the youngsters were picking them up and moving to the side to write in them. After approaching the servant greeted him with a little bow.

“Good day sir, did you also come to register for the competition?”

“Mhm.”

Zhang Dong nodded while taking the piece of paper into his hand. The person also informed him about this being the last day for registrations.

To the side, there were some quills and ink. On these papers, a person needed to select which competitions they would be competing in.

At first, Zhang Dong hesitated but soon he started noting down all of them that he thought he would be able to win. Formation creation and disassembly, pill making, forging, there was even one for apprising that he took. The one for combat was also taken which made it five.

He wanted to stick out but there wasn’t enough time for him to go through all of the competitions. By looking at the curriculum he would have enough time to go through each one of these competitions and build up his fame.

Everything would culminate on the battle stage, he wanted to garner the attention of all the high-standing elders. With him never having luck with not standing out, he would try the opposite, hiding in the open.

‘Well… I hope this doesn’t totally backfire…’

After a sigh, he headed over to the line, in his pocket some spirit stones to pay for the entrance fee.

Chapter 346

“Good day brother Yong.”

“Greetings brother Ma, you’re in a good mood today.”

“Why wouldn’t I be? The first spot is as good as mine.”

“Hah, not if I have something to say about it!”

The young men with fans looked at each other while chuckling. There were in a large room with many strange items on small display podiums. There were large and small weapons, armor stands, pills, and even herbs.

Around these items many people stood, young disciples, while also some older men with white beards.

“Who do you think will win this competition, Elder?”

“I feel like little Yong might be victorious this time, he did study up on all those pills, it was his weak point in the last year's contest…”

“Yes, there are many various pills on this day but not that many weapons, what a keen observation!”

Two other people were dressed in more ceremonial robes and talking. They had armbands with the words ‘Judges’ written on them.

This was one of the first competitions of this year’s outer disciple contest. Apprising was done here, the young men and women would be given pen and paper. They would then be able to wander around the large hall and look at the items presented there.

Each item had a corresponding number to it, they needed to successfully appraise the items here. Giving the correct name, quality, and any fine details that could affect the price. Then they needed to try to give an accurate estimate of what it would be worth.

It was already hard to precisely gauge the true nature of the weapon from the outer appearance. Getting the correct price would require putting the items against other ones and decide where they stood on their own.

There were also dummy items placed to fool some of the young appraisers. Pills that looked and smelled almost exactly like their more pricey counterparts. Dull-looking blades made from precious metals and even gems that weren’t actually what they seemed.

“I am Elder Hu, I will be the main judge for this competition. Remember juniors, you may not touch any of the items on display, use your eyes and other senses to ascertain the true nature of these treasures!”

The elder listed all the rules for this competition which forbade anyone from touching the items. There was not enough time for everyone to look at the items separately so if anyone was spotted looking at the answers of the others by the judges they would be instantly disqualified.

The main judge here was a Martial Grandmaster level of expert. With this much no junior would be foolish enough to peek, everyone was too afraid to get kicked out. Cheating in a competition like this could even get you banned from the sect. It was not worth the risk.

“With this, the competition starts now, remember you have limited time!”

The elder said while lighting up a somewhat longer incense stick, this would make the competition last about an hour.

The young sect disciples rushed into the open hall and started taking notes. While they were busy with the competition the elders decided to have some tea. They didn’t expect anyone to return for a while as the time needed was quite short.

“Don’t you think that we should extend the time slightly? We have never had anyone fully finish the appraisal before.”

One of the old men chuckled while pouring the green tea into the teacup.

“Then we would have to be stuck in here for even longer, they must also learn how to save time and choose their battles wisely.”

The other elder sat down while taking the cup into his hand and giving it a sip.

“That is true.”

From this elder's perspective, the winner would be the one that could fully utilize their gift. Some of the appraisers were quite stubborn, they would keep examining one item for long periods of time before coming to a conclusion. There was no time for such a thing, they needed to be swift and also know how to focus their expertise.

“Oh… who is that?”

The main judge narrowed his eyes while looking to the hall where the disciples were looking at the items. It seemed that he was even scoffing and frowning.

“Who do you mean elder?”

“That young man… is he wearing the trial disciple robes? Who allowed a trial disciple to take part in this competition?”

The man spotted a certain youth with long hair scribbling on the paper. He was going from one display case to another and quickly writing something down as if he instantly knew the answer to the question.

“That young man… I have no idea… he must have paid to participate… probably still an inexperienced youth that doesn’t know his place, should I go and take him away, Elder?”

The side judge asked while standing up, if the main judge wished for it he would remove the impudent trial disciple. There was no rule against not allowing them in, but they would really have to be from some prestigious clan for that to happen.

“No wait, let us see him make a fool of himself, we can scold him after the event is finished.”

The main judge waved his hand around while going back to sipping the tea. From his standpoint, this would be a good learning opportunity for the other young appraisers. He could show how inexperienced this young fool was and make the other youths take it more seriously.

The minutes continued to pass but the main judge's eyes were drawn to this young man. He was a strange one, he went from one stand to another and quickly started writing. It was as if he knew the answer instantly and there was no chance of being wrong.

This annoyed this old man quite a bit. He might have not been the greatest when it came to cultivation but appraisal was his main profession. To him, it seemed that the youth before him had no respect for this sacred occupation.

It looked like the youth just wrote whatever came to his mind and continued to the next one without examining it further. Even the other participants started to notice him as his feet were shuffling on the wooden floor quite loudly.

Before the incense stick could burn to the half mark the youth was at the last item. The young disciple stopped for a prolonged moment before scribbling down something. The item he was looking at was a somewhat useless pendant.

“Is he really done?”

The side judge commented while looking at the young man. It didn’t take him long to spot the side where the judges were. The next thing seemed a bit disrespectful as the young man spotted the elders and started strutting towards them as if he owned the place.

“Greetings elders, I would like to present my answers.”

The young man held out the piece of paper in front of the side judge while the main elder’s eyebrows were quivering.

“You have finished?”

“Yes, Elder.”

The young man bowed his head while clasping his hands. The main judge didn’t speak out yet but it was clear that he was a bit maddened by the fact.

“Are you taking the Appraisal occupation lightly?”

“I would never do such a thing…”

“You wouldn’t? What is this then?”

The side judge quickly grabbed the piece of paper and was almost ready to throw this rascal out. Before that, he gave the parchment a quick glance and he was shocked at his realization.

“Huh?”

He started eyeballing the writing, if it was calligraphy then this youth had quite pristine writing skills.

“What’s wrong? Did he get everything wrong?”

The main judge asked after the co-judge started acting strangely. He expected his junior to berate this impudent disciple and make more of a scene. This would show the other disciples that the Appraisal profession was not to be trifled with. For some reason, he went quiet instead.

“Wrong...n-no… These are all… correct Elder…”

“Correct? Let me see that!”

The side judge quickly gave the piece of paper to the main judge that started going through the list. He was familiar with the items so he didn’t need to consult any writing.

“Physical enhancement pill, common grade… 24% saturation...price two low grade spirit stones…”

“Azure Wood branch, not yet mature… three spirit stones…”

“Mirage Dragon Cauldron, mortal middle grade…”

The judge went through everything one by one and it was all correct. The youth before him seems to have marked everything and even got the market prices right as well. With one exclusion, he had achieved an almost perfect score.

“Who gave you the answers?”

“The answers Elder?”

“Yes! Do you think that I’ll believe that some trial disciple finished this competition with an almost perfect score?”

“Almost perfect score? I’m sure I’ve gotten everything right… could you check again?”

“The audacity! Who is your master?”

“My master? I don’t have one, I’ve joined the Hall a week ago.”

The young man smiled while standing straight as if he was in the right while the elder running this competition grew angry.

“No master? And you claim that you answered everything right? The useless trinket is a three-star phoenix pendant? You want me to believe that an item at the Martial Saint level made it to this competition unbeknownst to me?”

“Oh… Elder doesn’t know about the hidden mechanism in the back?”

“What hidden mechanism?”

The man shouted loudly and also released some of his killing intent. This caused all of the people in this large hall to look in this direction. It looked like the old man was berating a junior that was just standing there with his head not even lowered.

“I can show the elder, if you don’t believe me…”

“You can show me?”

The people here started inching away, it looked like this young man would end up as a corpse soon. The Appraisal Guild leader who was this main judge was known for having quite a temper if he was disrespected.

“Haha… he can show me, fine… show me… but be ready for the consequences…”

The old man seemed to have made up his mind and the two were seen walking to the last display where a silvery pendant was placed. Some of the disciples had already gone past it as it was one of the easier parts.

“That idiot is a goner… why did he have to go and offend that elder…”

The youths moved out of the way while waiting for this scene to be over. It was still the middle of the competition so they wanted this strange disciple to just go away. He had already annoyed most of the people that were here so they were all in agreement for his punishment.

“Well, this item might look like a regular common grade pendant made from plain silver but when you insert your Qi in the correct places then…”

“Hah, then wha….”

The main judge wanted to laugh but his mouth became tongue twisted. After the young man picked up the pendant it started radiating a massive amount of energy. The pale silver exterior switched to bright red in an instant.

“T-this… it really is a phoenix pendant… and a three star one…”

“Some people might not know this, but some blacksmiths like to lock their items behind a special locking mechanism. I have dabbled a bit in blacksmithing so it wasn’t hard to notice…”

The youth smiled while handing the now ruby pendant that had turned from a common grade treasure to an earth grade treasure. This was not something that an elder like this could hope to have in his possession normally but it found itself into his hand now.

“So elder… Did I have everything correct?”

“Huh? Everything correct?...”

The judge started laughing maniacally before stuffing the red pendant into his spatial ring.

“Yes, you did my boy! I knew a talent when I saw one!”

The elder started patting the young man on his back repeatedly while laughing while the other people in the room looked with wide opened mouths.

“Could you give this Elder your name, disciple?”

“Ah yes, my name is Dai Rong…”

The apprising competition was said to have ended early. Its victor had set a new sect record and went down in history as a new apprising prodigy…

Chapter 347

“That’s one… four to go…”

Zhang Dong was looking at a little white bead that he received after being first at the Appraisal competition. Thanks to his system he was able to instantly know what the items on display were, even the ones that had a hidden function.

After he had filled out the participation form he had to pay quite a hefty sum to take part in all of the competitions. The person he gave his paper to looked at him in bewilderment and he had to convince him to let him participate.

After taking care of the formalities he had two days of free time. This he used to locate the outer sect library. Even though he was confident in winning everything, this didn’t mean that he wouldn’t do any research.

As a trial disciple, he had no way of entering this large building. This did not pose a problem for someone with an immortal level disguising technique. He just needed to find one of the elders and shadow him back to his home. Taking out a late stage Martial Master wasn’t hard for him.

The old man was put to sleep before he could even realize what was happening. He had enough time to raid the library and gather even more knowledge by tapping the scriptures. The techniques were really mostly following the lightning Dao but they were all inferior to even the basic ones that he came to this world in.

If he had his old cultivation level, this Thunderball hall would probably salivate over making him their grand elder.

Now armed with more knowledge he took part in the Appraisal competition which he won. The main judge after being given that pendant was quick to give him this bead while he himself left the rest of the competition up to the side judge.

‘They sure are greedy in this empire… but not like that’s any different than my own.’

While thinking about how that elder was trying to hide the core formation level item he moved towards the next competition. This one would be about formations.

Being a formation master was a sought-after position. Together with Pill makers and blacksmiths they made up the three most important crafting professions. Without possessing a large protective formation a sect could not function correctly.

Formations were very similar to magic circles. A formation master needed to draw them out in specific locations while also placing some formation flags at the focal points. Their Qi would also be utilized to somewhat etch the symbols into the earth. After it was done, the formation circles would become hidden.

That was also how to combat formation worked, by having the practitioners focus their Qi to draw out a smaller formation with their spiritual energy. Those were harder to produce as they required the cultivator to focus but if done correctly the formation would activate and function even while battling.

‘I guess I’m already gaining some notoriety…’

Zhang Dong didn’t turn around but he could feel that some people were following him. After he won the appraisal competition some of the elders and disciples decided to shadow him.

There weren’t that many behind him as the competition that he took place in wasn't that popular. Appraisal was mostly a side profession for people that liked to identify items than to make them by themselves.

“I welcome you to the yearly outer sect formation guild competition.”

Zhang Dong moved together with a large group of disciples while another elder in a white robe showed up. He started discussing how this trial would go down.

It looked to be some type of course that everyone would have to go through. There would be several challenges that the young formation disciples would need to pass.

There would be illusion formations, imprisoning formations, and even slaughtering formations. The contestants would move in groups and the one that arrived at the end with the best time would win.

Zhang Dong being a trial disciple that had to actually pay to get in here, would need to wait. He was dead last with all of the inner sect disciples that had less than stellar backing. This also meant that probably no one would be paying attention to his run.

‘I guess this will give me an opportunity to see how the competition was doing.’

This formation competition took place in a large cavern. The sect actually dug into the large mountain and created many corridors. The whole thing seemed to be a labyrinth with many paths and illusory formations that were there to confuse the disciples.

There was one entrance through which the participants would go in and also one exit. That was right next to the entrance, the many corridors would lead them here and the first one to come out would be treated as the victor.

There were about three hundred participants here and they would be assigned to groups of thirty people. This smaller group would then compete.

He already knew that with rules like this, it meant that on the inside some young masters would probably use some underhanded methods to get ahead. Deaths and injuries did happen from time to time but everyone could always attribute it to the slaughtering formations.

After a set time, if not all of the disciples made it out an elder would go through the labyrinth to fetch them. At that time they would sometimes find bloodied bodies, or youngsters with broken legs or trapped in an illusion they can’t break.

This was also the first time Zhang Dong could see female cultivators. The formation master profession didn’t require a tough exterior so it was suited for women with high amounts of Qi. Women in this world tended to be less brash and also better at concentrating. They also showed more promise at learning tough formation diagrams than their more rowdy male counterparts.

Thus about a third of the competitors here were young girls between the ages of thirty and twenty. The sect still had a lot more male cultivators so they had the number advantage.

With the genders mixed it brought some more drama to the table. The young men started showing off while using this as a chance. The world of cultivation was mostly one of seclusion which caused the relationships between the two genders to be somewhat rare.

Thus, most of the young men had no idea how to approach the fairy-like jade-like beauties that only got more beautiful as their cultivation increased. Cultivation was a process of bettering oneself and the women of this world focused on the external appearance over pure power.

“This Lai Zhenya will win this contest, beautiful fairy please join me for some tea after the competition is over!”

One flamboyant-looking man in a purple robe and with a fan in his hand approached one of the better-looking young women. This first batch of thirty contestants did have most of the top prospects.

The woman just looked at him without replying but Zhang Dong could spot a little smile hidden under that pale face. Another youth joined in on the conversations soon after.”

“No, I will be the one to take the fairy out for some tea!”

Soon the two started fighting and only did they stop when an elder appeared. Zhang Dong gave out a sigh while standing up against the wall. He would need to wait till these idiots were done with their runs. He was unable to do anything besides waiting.

Time continued to fly and as he had thought there were some injuries. Sometimes some of the kids had to be carried out by the elders with many bruises on their bodies. The competition was harsh and there was minimal help even from the adults. Unless they could gain something in return, it was hard to find a carrying one around.

This all reminded him of the cultivators before he took over. Luckily with him in the driving seat, his sect had stared into a more gentle direction. There was some infighting but not this bad, or at least this was what he hoped.

He mostly took on a hands-off approach, Zhang Dong was not really aware of what was happening in the outer sect area. He only created the merit system that would allow everyone to get into the inner sect. If they worked hard if they used underhanded tactics was unknown to him.

There was the part where the sect scanners didn’t allow any evil people in but there were certain ones that would try to gain the system. They were not outright evil but looking out for yourself wasn’t really considered evil.

“Okay, you are the last ones left, please go in.”

‘Finally…’

The last group was his when they were done, then the last run would take place. From each group, the top three participants would be allowed to move one. Multiplied by ten, a group of the winners would take a harder course and then only would the winners be announced.

With the group of thirty he entered through the corridor while staying a bit to the side of everyone else. After going through the threshold of the passage he could already feel it, he found himself in a large illusory formation.

This was quite the basic one, it kept the people that were affected from seeing the correct path. What the young participants saw was a cavern with three paths but there was a fourth one. It didn’t seem that any one of them could tell as they all headed into one of the other three while he waited and took the correct one.

Little did he know that this was not actually an easy nut to crack. His actions were spotted by the elders outside. They could tell that someone was able to get through one of the more difficult formations that kept all the hidden paths away from the disciples.

These paths were there so that the elders could use them as shortcuts. Only when having a specially crafted item and previous knowledge would they be able to tell the way. Zhang Dong was a special case as he was fully immune to something like mind control due to his oversized soul.

This was also why he found himself at the exit after about only five minutes of walking. He successfully managed to use all the hidden corridors.

“How could this be…”

The main judge called out in surprise after he saw a slightly confused Zhang Dong reach the exit.

‘Did I make myself look a bit too competent with this one…’

He could only shrug while looking at the previous winners, not being able to comprehend how an unknown person like him had managed to beat everyone else. The record set by some formation ancestors from many millennia ago was not this fast.

“Oh, greetings elders, is there a problem?”

He asked while smiling, now all he had to do was beat the other young masters that were resting from their previous run. They all started to whisper, all looked at him and they all couldn’t believe it. It was time to play it up and become the number one prospect that this sect had ever had.

Chapter 348

“Why is everyone making such a commotion?”

An angry-looking short old man with a stocky physique looked at a group of disciples shouting. The place they were in was below ground and many strange-looking furnaces filled with smoldering metal were seen everywhere.

“Elder! You came at the right moment, please look at that disciple there!”

“Junior elder… why are you like this?”

The old man raised his eyebrow while looking at the person he left in charge. This was one of the competitions for the outer sect disciples. This old man here was the most prominent blacksmith in the outer sect. His cultivation wasn’t great but he made up for it with his knowledge about metals and crafting techniques.

This was also the main reason that he was not allowed to venture into the inner sect part. His cultivation journey was cut short by a certain event. Without any prospects to gain further strength he was confined to the other sect even though he was more talented at the craft than some inner sect elders.

He was required to stay at this competition even though he thought that his skills could be better used elsewhere. Nothing ever happened here and the bad form that all of the blacksmithing disciples had just made him more cranky.

Thus most of the time he left at the start of the competition and returned later when it was mostly over. This year was the same, no one really showed promise and there was even some strange trial disciple buying their way in. Maddened by this fact he decided to get something to eat while the youths competed.

To his surprise when he returned there was some kind of uproar. The usually quiet peanut gallery was talking with each other while glancing in a direction of someone.

“You’ll have to excuse the disciples and other seniors but we think that the Hall might have found a prodigy?”

“A prodigy? Where?”

“That young man over there, look Elder!”

The old man looked to where this so-called prodigy was supposed to be and spotted the trial disciple that he previously saw. At first, he thought that he might be looking at the wrong person and the real genius was somewhere behind this youth but then he noticed it.

“That sword… that’s some good craftsmanship… Did that young man really make it?”

“Yes Elder, I’ve seen it with my very own two eyes! You couldn’t make a finer sword for a Martial Master even if you tried! A Martial Grandmaster wouldn’t feel ashamed when using one either!”

The secondary elder that was left to watch over the young men and women here looked ecstatic. His eyes were sparkling while looking at the youth that had finished the sword.

This experienced elder here could hardly believe it. Almost all of these young smiths here had trouble making a mortal grade item. The youth before him was able to fashion a higher grade one than some of the blacksmiths that were already working for years.

“You there…”

“Me, Elder?”

“Yes you, what’s your name, disciple?”

“It’s Dai Rong, Elder.”

The old dwarf-looking man walked up to this youth and grabbed the sword that he was making. After looking over the item it was hard for him to believe that it was a weapon made by a disciple, it was just too perfect.

It was as if someone maximized a weapon to be just a millimeter from reaching the Martial Grandmaster level. It was as if this young man was just half a step from reaching a point of a grandmaster-level blacksmith.

“Disciple… show me your crafting process!”

“You want me to craft another sword, was this one not good enough?”

The young man looked at the man with a somewhat annoyed look in his eyes but it quickly changed to one of neutrality.

“Not good? It’s more than good, it's great! This old man just wishes to see how this disciple crafts, if you show me this I will announce you the winner!”

“Can it be something smaller… like a dagger?”

“A dagger? That will be enough!”

The old man just wanted to see the young man’s hammering techniques. He missed the show and he would not have a chance to see this young man’s talent if he let him go now.

“You there, being over enough spirit metals for a dagger. It will be enough if you just make the blade young man.”

Dai Rong just nodded while grabbing the provided metal. The theme of this crafting competition was making swords and there was a limited amount of resources provided. With the metal in hand, Dai Rong got to work.

The old man started watching, from the process of heating up the metal all the way to the precise blows and till the sharp knife blade started taking shape, he didn’t miss a thing. Even some of the other elders and disciples that were taking part in this competition looked.

“T-this… how can one be so precise… the hammer blows… the Qi control… not even one wasted movement…”

The old man looked baffled, where did this young man come from, I must make him my disciple were the thoughts running through his head.

“Young man… where do you come from…”

“I’m a member of the White Tiger clan… will this be enough Elder?”

Dai Rong stood with a short blade that only needed a proper handle. Even without the handle, it was clear that this weapon would be deadly and could be sold for a big profit.

“Enough… yes… Listen here disciple would you like to become my…”

Before the man could finish Dai Rong spoke up.

“That’s great elder, does that make me the winner of the competition?”

The old man looked around and to the other blacksmiths that were keeping watch over the other disciples. They all shook their heads around to indicate that there was no one even close to this young man’s skill level. The old elder here also could not feel any strong Qi from all the other weapons.

“It does seem that you are the winner young disciple but wouldn’t you want to become my dis…”

“That’s great Elder! Now if you’ll excuse me, I need to go to the Pill Forging Hall!”

“Pill Forging Hall? What do you want with those old coots”

“I’m going to participate in their pill-making competition, Elder.”

“Pill-making competition? Disciple knows how to create pills?”

“Yes Elder, I don’t have much time so I should be leaving, could I take the bead as the winner?”

The old man was shocked that this smithing prodigy was on the way to the pill making elders. The blacksmiths and apothecaries didn’t like each other here. They were in a constant battle for more donations from the main sect. Each one wanted to prove themselves as the one that was more worthy than the other.

“Ah yes here you go…”

The old man took out a round bead with a character on it that proved that he was the winner of this competition. The other disciples after seeing how well this young man could craft could not even complain.

“Is that man also this good at crafting pills?”

Another elder asked while talking to this dwarfish-looking man that glanced towards his way.

“It can’t be, maybe the young man just wants to give it a try? It would be better if such a talented smith focused on one main craft!”

The elder started rambling a bit before turning back to the young man.

“Now then, young man, would you like to become my disciple?”

“Ah, he left already, Elder…”

“Huh?”

The old man’s eyes went wide as the young man slipped away while he was busy talking to one of the other elders. He didn’t even notice him leaving; it was as if the young man was able to hide his presence.

“Blast it, I must make him my disciple! What if he is good at pill-making as well! One of those old bastards could snatch him away! Everyone from the Blacksmithing Hall follow me, we must get that young man into our Hall!”

…

Zhang Dong slipped away from the third competition with now three beads in his spatial ring. He snatched the sword and the dagger he made as well, these items would aid his body refining later.

He made sure to produce an item that was at the limits of his recognized cultivation level. He could have easily made something a Martial Grandmaster could use but that would make it look a bit more suspicious.

The old elder made him somewhat mad as he left the spot, then he even had the gall to ask him for another item. Now there were two competitions left, the pill making one and then the battle.

Already he could tell that he was gaining attention. During his third competition, he noticed some people mentioning his previous wins at the appraisal competition and the formation competition.

Even now he could tell that some people were following him. He didn’t blame them, he was an unknown person that was showing a lot of promise. Now with a small crowd with him in tow he made his way towards the fourth competition, there he would try to stick out like a sore thumb.

Even as he moved through the sect, he could hear people whispering. People were surely using their communication jades to give others information. A young genius was spotted in the sect and all of the elders probably wanted to have him.

‘Good, the more popular I become the better chance of getting a good spot at the inner sect…’

The inner sect was locked away behind a separate formation and required a key to pass through. His chances of cracking this key and sneaking in were high but why would he put himself in danger? He could just walk in there as a proper inner sect disciple.

The plan was easy: get attention, make it inside the inner sect, and then find a way to access one of those lightning rods. After that, he would drain the whole mountain of its power.

From what he could tell, the stormy clouds above were formed due to this place's special location. Even if he sucked away all of the current lightning it had, the energy would reform itself later.

He was planning on offering some treasures to the sect elders in the form of pills or weapons that he crafted as an apology. After achieving core formation he didn’t feel like he would need to fear any of them. He felt bad about draining this place of its resources but he also needed to get home.

‘This is the place… wonder what pill they will want me to make…’

The pill hall was before him, even before entering he could already smell the herbs. With long steps, he entered with a large crowd following his footsteps. With now many people interested in his true abilities they were hoping to see a fourth win of this unknown prodigy.

Chapter 349

"What are all of these people doing here? Did a star elder grace us with their presence?"

A person asked after arriving at the pill-making competition. This sect member was just interested in seeing the disciples compete.

For some reason, there were a lot more people here this year. The pill hall had a large building and the competition would be taking place inside.

There were two parts to this competition. One would be picking out the right materials while the second one would be pill creation. Both were important processes that a pill maker needed to know. They had to have the ability to distinguish the materials while also knowing how to put them together.

"You don't know brother?"

"No, what happened?"

"Well listen well, a new genius has appeared."

"A genius?"

The person nodded while explaining about the new rising star called Dai Rong.

"Won three competitions already? Even the blacksmithing one?"

"Yes, everyone is taking bets if he can win the fourth one!"

While the two were talking a chime sounded which caused everyone to quiet down.

"The pill-making competition will commence now, we from the pill hall wish for everyone to be silent."

The pill hall was one of the greater established places in this sect. No one would be willing to offend them as that meant being banned from getting any pills in the future.

Zhang Dong found himself being stared at. The place they were doing this competition was another large hall building.

It was quite spacious but also somewhat stuffy. There were about a hundred participants. There were many tables in this hall, on them large piles of dried herbs. He instantly knew what this was about. Even before being given the pill to make, they would be tested on their knowledge of materials.

"Welcome to this year's pill-making competition, this year we will be making the Crystal mountain establishment pill!"

The people around started whispering while the young alchemists looked down. This pill was quite hard to make as it allowed a person to push through a large realm. It was a mortal grade pill but a tricky one to make for these new pill masters.

"When the chime sounds, you will have an incense stick time to pick the herbs. If you don't know the recipe you will be asked to leave!"

Even before it started a few people let themselves out with heads lowered. This was quite shameful so they were greeted with laughs and smirks.

Zhang Dong was well aware of the crafting process and what herbs he needed to get. This was all thanks to raiding the two libraries.

'This pill requires a small lesser mortal grade beast core and then various herbs...'

He looked at the piled-up herbs and other materials. For a normal person, it would be hard to pick up the right item. Even an experienced master could make a blunder.

A normal person most of the time needed to take the herb into their hands and check it with their senses. The smell and texture could reveal if the given herb was the right age depending on the pill.

Not every herb increased in quality over time. Some matured early while other ones could take millennia to mature for a few minutes before withering away. A master would need to then be ready to fashion something out of this material before it was wasted.

Zhang Dong on the other hand could just scan the items with his system’s identification skill that he bought all these years before. He was sure to level it up to the maximum, with this he would be able to find any hidden gems in this pile of greenery.

‘After I get the materials I need a pill furnace…’

In this competition to keep it fair, the pill furnaces were provided by the sect. Due to the number of participants, the pill furnaces were rather lacking in quality. This meant that if the pill maker made too many blunders they risked the furnace exploding or ruining the pill.

An important part of these furnaces was the fire. It was a treasure in itself and depending on the rarity the heat varied. These flame tongues could be kept in special spatial rings that kept them suspended in time. Depending on the rarity they could even burn for centuries.

There were various pill forging techniques that worked like magic. The pill maker would push their spiritual energy into this pill furnace and mix the ingredients inside. The special flames would also need to be controlled by their Qi. Infusing more would cause these flames to burn faster but also use up its limited usage.

Just as the furnaces the flames would be provided by the sect. These flames were quite lacking in quality and would not last for long. With this, the pill makers needed to create a pill while the time ticked against them.

While waiting for the elder to finish making his speech Zhang Dong continued looking around. He could tell that there were some Martial Grandmaster realm elders around watching him. This was a bit disheartening as he hoped to get a Martial Saint interested.

With someone of that caliber, it would be guaranteed that he would make it into the inner sect as a disciple. Regretfully there weren’t any Martial Saints in the outer sect. All of those elders were experts that didn’t need to attend such events. From what he knew only at the battle competition one of them would be forced to attend.

That would be his best chance to gain the attention of the inner sect. There would be other inner sect seniors there but mostly at the Martial Grandmaster level. He could probably safely get in with one of them but he would be in a lesser position than if he was noticed by a Martial Saint that was close to a core formation expert in power.

“You are getting ahead of yourself.”

While waiting he heard someone’s voice next to him. It was a thin youth in a pure white robe and long dark hair. He looked quite handsome but a bit thin.

“Are you talking to me?”

“Yes you, I don’t know who you are but don’t think an amateur like you can win over this Jin Ming!?”

Zhang Dong didn’t answer, instead, he just turned around. He had trouble remembering the names of these young masters he had already met that they just blended with each other. This guy was probably some pill-making prodigy that somehow heard about Dai Rong’s rise. No proper young master would be able to tolerate competition, they always needed to stay in the limelight.

“You dare ignore me? Who do you think you are!”

The elder stopped talking and walked back towards his seat, soon the chime would be sounded. The young lord here continued to berate him while Zhang Dong could only try to ignore him.

The lanky man’s face went red while others looked from the side. Some chuckled while others were surprised that the trial disciple wasn’t showing any respect to his seniors.

The chime sounded and the competition began. It was quite chaotic and every young man and woman was pushing towards the tables with resources. With one exception of the trial disciple that moved to the side and leaned against one of the columns.

While the others were busy fighting with each other like old ladies for products with reduced prices, Zhang Dong just rested. Instead, he just looked at the pill furnace section along with the spatial rings that held the flames in them.

This didn’t go unnoticed as the people that had followed him from the other competitions pointed with their fingers. Even the pill-making judges were furrowing their brows, it looked like he had given up.

“What an imbecile, did you already give up before it started?”

The lanky youth passed him with a whole tray of ingredients while scoffing. Only when most of the contestants were finished with picking up their resources did he move to them.

Now with no one here to bother him he reached with both his hands towards the pile of the herbs. He held up a large pile of them before throwing them high into the air. While the herbs were at the apex of their ascension he started to quickly scan them with his eyes.

“This one… and that one… also this one…”

While making a strange scene he started plucking the falling herbs onto his own tray. The people looking from the side were shocked by his picking process. It seemed as if he was just taking out random items but if someone looked closely they would see that he was going for the highest quality parts each time.

Even though he started after everyone else, his tray was full of items within a minute's time. Some of the other contestants that weren’t so sure about their choices looked at him in shock as he headed towards a free pill furnace.

“Huh?”

The young master that previously egged him on found himself to his left. He was clearly surprised to spot his nemesis with a full tray of herbs.

“You think you can win with those randomly picked herbs? Are you taking the pill-making profession lightly?”

Some of the judges in the distance nodded their heads as they agreed. Zhang Dong could see that he came off as a haughty young master himself now. This was all fine as he was about to shatter these people's worldview.

“Watch and learn!”

He replied while trying to sound somewhat condescending. Without a reason to hide he could play up a young master’s persona.

With a smack to the side of the furnace, the lid flew up into the air. He then gathered spiritual energy into his hand and gave it a twirl. A mini-tornado was created that circled around all the ingredients. The material started sticking to each other while the mini cyclone rumbled with lightning energy.

“Is that the Tempest pill forging technique? How could a young disciple like that be so proficient in it!”

The judges started staring after hearing the sounds of thunder coming from a particular spot. Zhang Dong had many such techniques but this one was one of the more eye-catching and also studied at this sect.

The mini twister started combining the ingredients even before they entered the pill furnace. Within the massive gust of air, the almost finished pill entered the container which he then closed.

With this technique, he could save on time while also conserving the pill furnace’s durability as part of the pill creation was done outside of it.

Now with another tap of his finger, the fire to the pill furnace was released. It was normally red in coloring but after coming in contact with Zhang Dong’s Qi it turned blue and started radiating electrical energies.

The whole large hall with many pill makers and their students went silent. Anyone with an ounce of knowledge about making pills knew that they were witnessing something special.

“What is this… I’ve never seen a forging technique like this...will that low-grade pill furnace be able to take all that spiritual energy?”

The lid started rumbling and more sounds of thunder escaped. The whole furnace started glowing brightly and soon the whole large hall was consumed by a flash of light.

As the furnace opened an illusory dragon shot up into the air and coiled itself around the furnace it came from. It gave out a menacing roar before its body started to fade away.

“T-the thunderous roar of a lightning pill dragon… a-a Master!”

‘Well… that got their attention alright…’

The finished product landed in the palm of his hand. The pill was radiating quite the strong energy, whoever ate this would surely reach the Martial Master level without any problems.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 350

“Join my family and marry my daughter!”

“No, marry my daughter instead! Also, become my disciple!”

“Stop it you lot, this disciple is mine! I can offer you a thousand low grade spirit stones!”

Zhang Dong stood surrounded by a group of old men that were involved in a shouting match. After he made a miraculous pill from the ingredients that the sect provided the old fogies went wild.

Not only were the elders from the Pill Hall here but also from the Blacksmithing Hall, the Formation Hall, and even from the Appraisal Guild. The last one didn’t really have that much pull here so they had to make way for the top three halls.

He had to commend them on how much a good disciple was worth. They even started offering him their daughters, more than one at a time. If he was looking to maximize his profits he would probably end up with a large harem and a house of his own here.

Still, these people were only outer sect elders and seniors. None of them could guarantee him entrance to the inner sect. Before a fight between these old farts could break out, he needed to stop it.

He wouldn’t be surprised if they made some kind of competition between each other. One where he could not refuse after the victor was chosen.

“Please Seniors and Elders, this Dai Rong is truly not worth your time. I’m but a trial disciple, I just wished to pit myself against the other seniors from the sect to see how far I could go. I will not decide on a master before finishing the competition!”

He needed to state his terms, the oldies knew what he was implying and they clearly didn’t like it. From their perspective the young man was foolhardy, the last competition was not a cakewalk and a person could get injured.

There were many young masters that fell during the last competition. Anything could happen during a fight, even a maddened elder could jump in to deliver a critical blow to a disciple that was not taken yet. Without the proper protection, this youngster was putting himself in a heap of trouble while not having proper backing. After speaking his mind, it would be a loss to their face to beg and make more offers.

“Is the sect junior resolute in his decision?”

One of the high ranking pill masters asked.

“The junior is, I wish to compete with the other seniors in the last competition.”

The old man shook his head before throwing a bead towards Zhang Dong.

“Is that so, I wish you luck. I hope you can be victorious and hope that junior’s greed doesn’t get the best of him.”

Zhang Dong was a bit surprised by this elder who was this pill hall’s master. He did not even try to offer him anything to be his disciple. It seemed that even this sect had some people with character. The rest after noticing this old man’s speech started clearing out.

The disciples that were in the process of making pills mostly gave up as there was no way of winning this anymore. The lanky youth that made him his rival shrunk back after being blown away by his pill-making technique.

Four down and only one left to go. It was time to take a break as the battling competition would be taking place in the morning of the next day. Even then he had quite the hard time slipping away.

The pill-making elders started asking him about some insights. The same thing happened with the blacksmiths and the formation masters. All of them wished to know how such a youth was this knowledgeable in their arts that they spent their whole life in.

It was strange to see all these old men and women asking him for tips. He looked like a youth that was not even at the age of twenty. Knowledge was power in this world, even the old seniors threw away dignity and asked a junior for help. Advancing in their given skill was more important to some, even more than face.

For some, it was the other way around. Part of the seniors and elders were looking at him with rage. It was clear that Zhang Dong needed to get out of here otherwise, some of them could do something drastic.

‘I’ll go back to the cultivation cave for now…’

“Excuse me, elders. I need to go to the little cultivator's room…”

He excused himself while some of them had questions. Some of the elders and seniors tried to stop him but he used an evasive technique that made his body move like paper in the wind.

“Please wait disciple…!”

They chased after him but when they got outside he was nowhere to be seen. Zhang Dong lowered his presence and faded into the shadows and made his way back to the cultivation cave. He greeted the person that was stuck looking over the cultivation caves and returned inside.

While trying to prepare a strategy for the coming battles he heard a knock on the large door to this cave.

“Disciple Dai… are you there?”

“Elder Yusheng? Yes, I’m here.”

Zhang Dong replied while wondering what the guy wanted. He was not supposed to come back this early.

“Did you leave the cultivation cave? I’ve been hearing rumors of a particular disciple winning some competitions…”

‘I guess he knows…’

Information spread fast here apparently, he thought that this elder was a bit denser but apparently he had some informants. This could throw a wrench into his plans but also not mean much. With the man knowing that he had already been active outside there was no reason to lie.

“Ah yes, I was a bit hungry so I decided to visit the sect and would you know it, there was a competition taking place so I just had to sign up!”

“Junior had enough spirit stones to sign up on his own?”

The sum of spirit stones required for taking part in the competitions as a trial disciple was quite steep. A hundred low grade spirit stones for each competition and two hundred for the main one, this was not something a trial disciple like him should have been able to afford.

“Ah yes, my clan had left me quite a sum but now I’ve spent it…”

This was a half-truth as most of the spirit stones were absorbed by him to push his cultivation forward.

“Are you planning to take part in tomorrow's competition?”

“Yes I am elder, I wish to see how I will fare against the sect seniors!”

“Is that so…”

After mumbling some words Elder Yusheng went quiet. This was followed by some strange clicking sounds and the use of some kind of Qi technique.

“I think that would be a bad idea, you should rest for a few days disciple, I’ll come to pick you up in a couple of days…”

With that message, he could feel the elder moving away from this location. When Zhang Dong approached the door he knew that the man had locked him inside. With a little knock on the hardwood, he knew that it was reinforced with a formation.

‘A late stage Martial Master would probably not be able to leave this place now…’

It was clear that this elder wanted to keep him here. He was probably thinking that if the prodigy vanishes then he could force him to be his disciple.

‘The inner sect elders are probably too lazy to look into some rumors about a trial disciple winning outer sect competitions…’

High-ranking elders and seniors tended to not care for what happened in the outer sect. Even if they got the information that there was a promising disciple they would not care. They were in a position that didn’t require them to care, it was the disciples that were supposed to fight for their attention and not the other way around.

“I guess this would work on a regular disciple…”

Zhang Dong could easily remove this formation lock that was placed here. It was quite rudimentary and even accessible from this side. He would even be able to force his way out as his true strength was above that of a Martial Master.

‘Let me reorganize my thoughts till then.’

While his escape was already assured he moved to the middle of the cultivation cave. He sat down and started doing some breathing exercises to calm himself.

From the outside, he looked calm and collected but in reality, he was a bundle of worries. There was no way to know how long he would be stuck here. His plan could also backfire even before he reached the inner sect.

This all depended on him being able to absorb all that lightning energy. With it, he would be probably able to access the core formation realm. All those years ago he entered this world at that stage and already then he was able to compete with late-stage core formation cultivators.

Now he was many times more experienced and also his cultivation technique was far superior. With that in mind, he hoped on achieving the strength level of someone around the great circle of core formation.

“That magical world did give me quite the boost to my cultivation, maybe with this I will be able to contend with one of those watchers if they appear…”

This was the biggest bump in the road. He feared that if he was found by one of the people that were part of the system, they might see him as an anomaly and attack. The demon lord was far stronger than the hero party and anyone that lived in that world. Here that could mean that they could even be on the immortal stage or somewhere between it and the nascent soul realm.

‘Well, It doesn’t seem like these watchers will care if I don’t overstep the boundaries…’

The watcher that was disguised as the human king only came out when he started causing imbalances in that world. Probably unless he started going out of his way to cause havoc these watchers would not show themselves.

This also posed the question of what the endgame in this world was. There was no obvious demon lord to defeat, only sects and the emperors at the top. Was he supposed to become the new emperor of one of the empires? Or maybe he was supposed to reach the immortal realm and ascend to some other realm?

The immortal realm was quite illusory here. There were secret grounds built by long-dead immortals but there was not really any information about how a person could push into it. With the original version of the system, he would probably be able to achieve it by combat.

After eradicating the top sects and clans he might have had enough points to unlock that level of power. Then after reaching that level a new questline would be unlocked.

‘Or… it could be the end of the line…’

There was also the possibility that after achieving the immortal realm something life-threatening could happen. A fight with the watcher? Moving to another realm and meeting the person that created this all? Maybe even a return to his original world?

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh as he didn’t really care. He would not even be inclined to reach the immortal realm to check. His family was more important, if it meant to remain at the nascent soul level and to never ascend past it, then it was fine with him.

‘If everything goes well tomorrow, I’ll be at the inner sect… just wait a bit longer, daddy will return soon...’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 351

With a little click, the lock on the cultivation cave came undone. The large door swung open while a certain someone escaped outside.

“Huh?”

The person responsible for watching these cultivation caves turned his head up but he could not see anything there. The door seemed to be closed but he could spot a bit of snow falling down.

“Must have been my imagination…”

The man shrugged and turned back to the other side. A certain elder had given him some spirit stones to watch one cultivation cave in particular. It seemed that he was interested in keeping a certain disciple locked inside. The man agreed as it was easy money and he just needed to contact the elder if he saw the youth leaving.

‘Those days as the demon hunter sure came in handy…’

Zhang Dong’s figure was coated in a translucent filament which allowed him to blend with the scenery. If he held his breath and didn’t move a muscle it was impossible to be spotted. This and a few other techniques he picked up for when he was out adventuring. It was much easier to go around as a sword for hire than a sect leader so he had to brush up on the assassination skills.

After the guard turned his head some more snow started falling but this time around there really would be no one for him to look at. Zhang Dong descended from the mountain while keeping to the shadows, he arrived at the outer sect just as the sun started to go up which turned the scenery red.

The scenery was quite breathtaking but Zhang Dong was preoccupied with the mission before him. He had already been noticed by many outer sect elders, he could join the outer sect at any moment. The problem was the inner sect elders which he needed to prove his worth to.

‘Will those other old farts try to stop me as well?’

He stopped before a large outer sect building. Inside of this one the last competition would take place. While being a trial disciple he would not be able to refuse any of the outer sect elders. If one decided to walk up to him, they could even take him by force to wherever they wanted.

Some of the pill makers and blacksmiths after seeing his crafting techniques had that look in their eyes. Each one of these old fogies was focused on face and status. Making him not be noticed by any inner sect elders was a silly plan but when face was involved, rationality went out the window.

Thus why he decided to hide his presence and watch for the time being. Even though it was four hours away from the start of the competition the disciples were already gathering.

Just as he had predicted he saw people that followed him from the other four competitions. He didn’t even need to remember their faces as their behavior was a giveaway.

There was only one star disciple but many hungry elders. They all started glaring at each other, it seemed that a brawl could happen at any moment.

The crowds gathered Zhang Dong was sure to take a good look at one of the young competitors. With a quick face change, he made his way inside. With a new appearance, the elders that were looking for Dai Rong had no idea that he just passed them. There was only one entrance so it was impossible for him to sneak in from another side, not with so many people standing on guard.

The first checkpoint consisted of some guards but they weren’t checking the permits for taking part in the competition. After sleeping through this part he turned back into Dai Rong once again.

With his infiltration now being successful, he blended in with the crowd of other disciples. Along with them, he made it through the second checkpoint which would allow them to go into the side of the competitors. Time continued to pass and finally, everyone had gathered.

‘So that’s the inner sect elder?’

Even though this was not an arena building there were many people looking in from an elevated point. There was one large tower in which all of the important elders were sitting in. They could overlook the disciples that could battle on many solid rock-slab-covered platforms.

“Let us get this over with...”

Zhang Dong looked up to the large tower and he could hear a bored voice calling out to everyone. From his vantage point he could barely make out his features, it seemed to be the same elder that greeted the new disciples by the name of Jingyi. The characteristic well-kept red beard and hair made this clear.

If someone looked at the ground from the vantage point of Elder Jingyi, they would see a checkerboard pattern down below. These were actually battle stages on which the disciples would be fighting on.

Each mini stage was quite large with thirty meters in diameter. Without the disciples having the capability to fly there was no need to make them any bigger.

The rules were easy, each of the disciples would be given several tokens. Everyone had three challenge tokens with which they could challenge anyone with a higher number in the ranking.

These ranking numbers were decided by various factors throughout the year of the outer sect. Zhang Dong was a trial disciple that just paid with spirit stones to get in, with this his ranking was dead last. Which meant that no one would ask him to do battle with them as there was nothing to gain.

There were a thousand people here, each one with three tokens but this wouldn’t translate to three thousand fights. Anything above the top hundred didn’t matter to anyone and the bottom 900 would be only challenging the top 100.

This competition was good for the challengers but not so good for the ones being challenged. Some people strategically waited till the competition was almost done before they used their token.

The disciples were only given five minutes to rest before being forced to fight again. There weren’t that many that could last through the continued battles before retiring. If a disciple was crafty enough they would be able to get rid of their competition and do it while everyone watched.

The young masters would use their goons to repeatedly attack their target until this target either lost or was tired. Then they would swoop in for the win while also causing harm to this person.

If the other person didn’t have enough backing to use the same tactic it was seen as a weakness. Having other people to help them was seen as just another tool from their toolbox.

‘Hm… should just go for it?’

Zhang Dong rubbed his chin while hesitating. His old way of thinking was still ingrained in his very being. He was not a person that liked to stand out but he was forced into a leadership position by the people around him.

If he challenged the number one disciple and beat him it would cause an uproar among the others. He would probably have to go through many more to prove that he was truly strong.

On the other hand, if he waited for too long he could be accused of battling a weakened opponent. This competition wasn’t really here to remain in the best spot but to show off to the elders.

While Zhang Dong was deep in thought about his next move the competition was slowly underway.

“I challenge you Xuan Fen! Face me.”

The first challenger appeared, he pointed at quite the brutish-looking disciple. Thanks to the comments of the people around him, Zhang Dong was able to figure out that Xuan Fen was ranked number three.

“Mo Huang is really daring, he is only ranked twenty and he already wants into the top three, so insolent!”

“He has no chance!”

Xuan Fen ranked three, Meng Meixiu ranked second and Feng Shi ranked first. These were the top three disciples but only one of them was being challenged for now. This didn't mean that other people in the top 100 weren't being asked for a spar.

‘Let’s see what these youths have to offer.’

The disciples started to throw their tokens and everyone moved to the stages to do battle. Zhang Dong was greeted to a nice bout of the youthful generation. If he compared them to his own sect members then these Thunderbolt hall disciples weren't anything special. But if he compared them to the old Zhang Clan then they would be slightly superior.

It was clear to him that due to the variation in their cultivation the people here edged out the common cultivator from his own empire. There were fewer in numbers but made up with the quality of their foundation and combate skills.

The sect here also didn’t get involved with the common people. None of the sects built their forces inside of large cities like they did in the Azure Dragon Empire. This saved a lot of time on politics and managing.

The resources like herbs and treasures were about the same. This left more cultivators able to get items like pills to boost their cultivation level. Thus their cultivation increased faster than their Azure Empire counterparts.

‘Well then… I should probably make my appearance, best to make a splash from the beginning.’

The top disciples didn’t take long to win their fights. The youth that was ranked 20th fell to the one ranked 3rd just in five blows which showed how much of a gap there was between the two.

Even with those five blows that he managed to utilize the people were surprised that he lasted that long. It seemed that if this youth was smart, he might have been able to raise his rank.

Regretfully he was beaten to a pulp and had to retire fast. Not being able to judge your own strength was also a skill that some people did not have. This young man reminded him of his old friend Huo Qiang, if this worked out he hoped to see the big idiot soon.

“Pathetic, does someone with skill dare to face this Xuan Fen? If not then maybe I should ask you for a bout, Feng Shi!”

Xuan Fen was quite the large young man, he looked like a hairy bear and his body was covered with many scars. Feng Shi on the other hand looked more like your scholar type, it was clear that one trained his body refining skill to the maximum while the other focused mostly on Qi refining.

“You can try but I would rather compete with junior sister Meixiu instead.”

The scholar replied while looking at the second-ranked woman cultivator. She was your typical jade-like beauty that just scoffed at the proposition.

“Xuan Fen? Sure, I’ll challenge you.”

Suddenly an unknown disciple moved forward, most of the people here squinted at his appearance as they had no idea who it was.

“Hey isn’t that… It is!”

But, soon Dai Rong’s name was spread through the whispers as people recognized him as the winner of four competitions. Everyone suddenly leaned forward to see if the new prodigy was a capable fighter.

If he managed to beat the number three disciple then his legend would be cemented. If he failed, on the other hand, his wings could be cut as Xuan Fen was known for crippling his opponents before they had the chance to blossom.

Chapter 352

“You wish to face me?”

The bear-looking youth laughed while nodding.

“Come then, I’ll show everyone what happens to nobodies that challenge me!”

Zhang Dong advanced towards the stage while looking at the smug-looking youth. His opponent was puffing out his chest while smirking. It was clear that the Xuan Fen that he was facing wasn’t taking him seriously at all.

The young man was quite large, even if he was in his original form he would be dwarfed by this muscle brain.

“Whose lackey is this?”

Xuan Fen asked while Zhang Dong hopped onto the stage. The young man was thinking that this Dai Rong here was someone’s follower. It was more believable that he was one of the many people sent to tire him out.

“I didn’t think there would be idiots like you around, whoever put you up to this must have offered you a lot of spirit stones!”

Xuan Fen continued to talk while Zhang Dong just stood there with his hands behind his back. His face was neutral and he didn’t look like he had a care in the world.

“Are those trial disciple robes?”

“Is that junior crazy? Doesn’t he know of senior Xuan Fen’s bad temper?”

From the conversations that the people were having here, Zhang Dong came to a conclusion. Probably the tactic of sending waves of foot soldiers for the top disciples didn’t always pan out. Not when people like this Xuan Fen crippled them or beat them down to a pulp.

The young man that battled him was taken away on a stretcher and his arms and legs were in awkward positions. It was clear that no one here was stupid enough to give away their future to offend this monster.

‘I guess word hasn’t spread yet… maybe the people from the other professions are still looking for me outside.’

This was a large open area but it was set up in such a way that only the elders in those lookout towers could see the fights. The disciples were on the ground, shoulder to shoulder, and looking at the checkerboard combat platforms for a worse angle.

“Begin!”

A judge sounded a large gong which indicated that the battles would start.

“I’ll end this quick, if you don’t resist I’ll be merciful and only break your arms!”

Xuan Fen charged forward with large strides, each time he took a step the ground beneath his feet cracked. His cultivation level was at the middle stage of the Martial Master level and he clearly specialized in body refinement.

Zhang Dong saw it all in slow motion, the young man’s body started being surrounded by small arcs of grayish lightning. His body hair began to be charged as he raised his fist and motioned it forward while still being about two meters away from his target.

“Thunder wave fist!”

The moment he swung this large fist a shockwave with tiny lightning bolts was sent Zhang Dong’s way. While everyone expected him to either get hit or try to dodge he did the exact opposite.

He took a small step forward while also moving his palm to meet this electrical attack. The moment the shockwave collided with this hand it was pushed back by an even greater force. Another shockwave appeared with a more bluish hue to its lightning element.

“What!?”

Xuan Fen’s eyes shot open as his attack was deflected right back. There was no time to evade it so he moved his forearms up to protect his head. The electrical attack collided with his body and pushed him back. He remained standing while blocking, his legs formed skid marks on the hard ground.

“What was that… he managed to push senior Xuan Fen back!”

“Yeah… his clothes are also ruined…”

Xuan Fen’s upper body was revealed to the public as his robes burst from this palm strike. Even now Zhang Dong could see Fen’s body contending with the invading lightning Qi.

‘Great, he didn’t blow up… I’m getting the hang of holding back!’

Zhang Dong wanted to pat himself on the back as he managed to analyze the strike that came his way. He then used that to measure his opponent's strength accurately.

With this knowledge, he just needed to use a technique with a little bit more power to cause some damage while also not killing the poor youth in one shot. This left his opponent with some residual damage but allowed the battle to continue further.

“You… you’re not all talk.”

Xuan Fen roared in a beastly fashion and with a burst of his own Qi managed to remove Zhang Dong’s attack in its entirety. Soon the young man’s body started to change, it expanded in size along with a coat of fur. At the end of this transformation, he looked like a cross between a bear and a werewolf.

“Senior Xuan Fen is having trouble, who is that junior?”

Soon the fight continued, Zhang Dong made sure to dodge each claw swipe and bite that Xuan Fen sent his way. While exchanging blows he chipped away at his opponent's stamina and health. With this approach, he seemed to be just slightly stronger than his opponent.

“Stop moving around and face me like a man!”

Xuan Fen panted with blood streaming out of his bear-like nose.

“You wish to put body against body? Are you sure about that?”

Xuan Fen didn’t respond but just charged forward, Zhang Dong did the same and the two used their fists. A strange ‘peng’ sound was heard by the disciples that sounded like a fist hitting solid metal. This was followed by Xuan Fen’s knuckle being broken after the exchange.

“ARGHhhh”

The large youth cried out in pain before another fist descended towards his face. He flew in an arc out of the battle stage that he and Zhang Dong were fighting. Out cold he flopped on the ground and the match was over.

“Don’t you have to announce the winner?”

Silence washed over the people and even the judge that needed to be reminded of his duties.

“Ah yes, the winner and new holder of the number 3 ranking spot is… uh…”

“Dai Rong, Elder.”

“Dai Rong!”

His name was announced and the people burst out in cheers. He could even see some people pointing and laughing at Xuan Fen that was down for the count. It was clear that a person that lived his life breaking peoples limbs was not liked.

“Well then… the next one would be Meng Meixiu? Is Meng Meixiu here?”

Zhang Dong shouted out loud to bring everyone’s attention to him. He previously saw the jade-like beauty moving around but it didn’t seem that she had been challenged yet.

“This Dai Rong is too ferocious, he wants to challenge senior sister Meng Meixiu even before he has time to recover?”

Previously the disciples were clapping but it changed to booing soon. This time around it seemed that the woman he was facing had a sort of following. Luckily she heard his loud shouting and decided to show her face.

“Brazen, you might have defeated that idiot but don’t get ahead of yourself, junior!”

The crowd of simps cheered out loudly the moment this beauty descended onto the stage. At the same time, they started with a vengeance at him.

It was clear who the favorite here was. It would be strange that when he was victorious that he would be spammed by many challengers that wanted to show off in front of this beauty.

“I’m getting ahead of myself?”

That is if he allowed this to happen, this was no time to hide his power. With a burst of energy, his body started radiating electrical energies. Small arcs of bluish lightning started shooting from his body in random directions before turning into a more golden coloring in the end.

“Hoh… who is that young man…”

Above in the tower, this outburst of energy was noticed by the elder generation. Some of them glanced during the bout with the bear-like Fen but only now did Zhang Dong garner the attention of the almost asleep Elder Jingyi.

“Elder Jingyi… that is the second-ranked Meng Meixiu, she will probably be moving to the inner sect of Yin-hall…”

“Not her, the other one…”

“The other? That young man is… I don’t know… I have never seen him before…”

Elder Jingyi stretched out while leaning forward in his chair. He was jolted awake by a strange energy signature in this young man’s electric Qi. It felt somewhat pure and even above his own and even though it was just for a moment it seemed like the young man had a lot of potential.

“Well, what are you waiting for? Find me his name!”

“Ah, of course elder!”

The man panicked and quickly moved to the side while Elder Jingyi continued to watch. Little did he know that he was playing along to Zhang Dong’s little game. He made sure to release some of his true Qi into the surroundings.

These cultivators were easy to read, if they thought that they could gain something they would act on it. While posting as a still unrefined disciple he could not just show off his superior lightning Dao. That would be too suspicious and just a ticket to getting thrown into a dungeon.
Instead, he started off with the regular version that was in a more pale blue color. It was the lightning that he came into this world with. This was already enough to make all of the peoples mouths water here.

‘I see that the old fart is finally looking at me now, I guess I should give him a good show…’

Meng Meixiu went quiet after the outburst of his Qi. It was clear that she started to take him very seriously.

“Shall we then?”

The young woman was holding a weapon that he was very familiar with. It was a weapon that his wife also used, a set of battle fans. It was also a bit surprising how similar this girl was to Zhang Liena.

The moment she utilized the fans a torrent of green energy gathered in front of her. She created a miniaturized twister filled with arcs of green lightning energy.

“Wind energy with lightning… not bad…”

Zhang Dong had to make this a bit more flashy this time around. He clasped his palms together in one strong move which also produced the sound of a thunderclap. His hands started glowing in a pale blue light that quickly turned into electrical energy.

“That technique… isn’t that the lesser thunder dragon palm?”

The lightning energy that looked chaotic at the start started taking shape. It looked like two small eastern dragons coiled themselves around Zhang Dong’s forearms. They remained floating around while clinging to them tightly while sometimes giving out thunderous shouts.

“Well then, shall we?”

He plunged himself into the battle, one of his palms stretched forward while the other was closer to his body in a defensive position. Some people burst out in cheers while others remained silent, it seemed that this would be a battle that they would remember for ages to come.

Chapter 353

The young disciples cheered as they surrounded the stage where the new trial disciple appeared. They even forgot about offering their challenge tokens for their own contest while gawking at the display of skill.

Everyone was more interested in gaining some insight into the battle techniques this young man was using. With one glance they could see that he had trained them to a very high level. He moved thunder and delivered devastating blows that his opponent had trouble defending.

“Junior sister is losing? How can this be?”

The fans of Meng Meixiu both male and female were looking with eyes wide open. Her opponent was quite brazen but he had a lot of skill to back up that claim.

‘Getting the hang of this…’

Zhang Dong thought to himself while moving his palm forward. A dragon made from lightning shot forward and bit into Meng Meixiu’s battle fan. The girl in panic had to let her weapon go while jumping as far away as she could.

The dragon made from electric energy chomped down on this weapon and made quick work of it. With this, the young lady cultivator was disarmed and would need to use her body to defend herself.

“Senior sister, you may surrender if you wish.”

Zhang Dong smiled while standing upright. This young woman seemed a bit stuck up but this didn’t mean that she needed a good beatdown. She also reminded him of his wife slightly so he was willing to let her quit if she wished for.

“You want this Meixiu to surrender? You must be taking me for a fool!”

It didn’t seem that she was willing to, the only thing he could do was to shrug. While the woman continued to gather her Qi into her body he advanced slowly.

Green energy with a bit of lightning mixed into it started circling around that voluptuous body. Zhang Dong had to wonder if it was something in the food or if it was caused by cultivation. For some reason, the women in this world tended to be on the bouncier side. This one was nothing compared to his own wife but she wasn’t a slouch either.

‘Damn… I should stop thinking like this or I’ll end up as that perverted gramps.’

While remembering his lecherous grandfather he took a step forward. The woman’s attack activated as she swung her hands forward. A gust of wind flew his way, this looked like a ranged attack that turned the wind into blades with an added shocking effect.

Even if the wind blades missed the target, the electricity would shock the target. This is if someone didn’t have some kind of lightning resistance or a helpful skill.

Zhang Dong held his palm out while making a grasping motion. The moment he did the lightning dragon that was coiling around his forearm shot forward while opening its mouth. The wind blades that were approaching him were promptly absorbed along with that meager amount of lightning energy that they carried.

“Impossible how could you…”

Before the young woman could finish the sentence Zhang Dong’s body blurred. He activated his old moving technique that produced an electric afterimage in his old spot.

“Ugh…”

A foot collided with Meixiu’s abdomen before she had time to react. At the exact moment as Zhang Dong’s kick connected with the girl’s stomach a tremendous thunderclap filled the stage. The girl flew far and wide and finally ended up outside of the ring.

She didn’t collide with the rough ground though as she was caught by an old woman with light gray hair. This old lady looked at the person that sent this woman flying.

‘Hm?’

Zhang Dong could feel killing intent pressing down on him. The old woman was clearly trying to suppress.

‘Bullying juniors with no backing is it?’

It was clear that this old woman was either this Meng Meixiu’s master, family member, or maybe even a bodyguard. She was at the level of a Martial Grandmaster so it wasn’t something that he couldn’t handle. The problem was that his persona that he was using couldn’t.

‘This calls for some acting…’

The old woman continued to glare at the young man while other disciples looked. They all knew what was happening but they couldn’t offend an elder. What was surprising is that the person that was getting his cultivation suppressed was still standing upright.

Dai Rong was seen standing upright while his body trembled slightly. After a few moments, the people could see his eyes getting bloodshot and some blood flowing from his nose. It looked like the young man was unwilling to kneel down before this elder.

“That’s enough!”

The booming voice of Elder Jingyi filled the whole competition area and the old woman was forced to back away. The woman looked up to this Elder Jingyi while bowing in apology, soon she moved to the side with the jade-like beauty that had the wind knocked out of her.

‘That guy took his time, it’s not that easy to fake bleed.’

This was of course just an act, he did force his body to bleed for a moment but it was nothing but a scratch. There were no internal injuries or cultivation damage that mostly came with Qi attacks like that.

To play it up he stumbled forward after the pressure attack was removed. He was sure to look like a thick-headed disciple that didn’t know his place yet. Even though most people didn’t like when the juniors were impolite to the elder generation, they also had to commend them for their high pride. It was a sign of willpower that could not be easily broken.

“Junior sister lost… this can’t be happening…”

“This only leaves brother Feng Shi, will he also challenge him?”

“Not possible, after the elder intervened this Dai Rong must be in a world of pain, he is probably on his last breath.”

“Yeah, isn’t this a chance?”

The young disciples looked at Dai Rong that just went through the number three and then number two ranked disciples. He had taken out their competition which meant that it would be possible for them to get into the top 3.

Meng Meixiu might have been able to return later but Xuan Fen was out for the whole competition. The second spot that Dai Rong was occupying might have been temporary but the third was a possibility.

“You think that I am weakened?”

Like thunder, Dai Rong’s voice spread through the area. Even though the voice only carried the might of a Martial Master there was something in it. The elders that were in their tower overlooking the competition even flinched after the thunderclap sounded.

“Be my guest, come and challenge me and see if you return in one piece!”

Zhang Dong played it up by making his eyes crackle with lightning energy to make him appear like a wounded tiger. Everyone knew that injured beasts were very dangerous and they all quickly shrunk back.

“Feng Shi, you are last and I have only one challenge token left, face me!”

It was time for the climax of this storyline, the number one student was a Martial Master that had already reached the late stage. No one was seriously trying to get his spot as it was not theirs to take.

Feng Shi was apparently someone that took his time to build up his foundation. When he came out of seclusion this year he soared towards the very top. His age was close to the other top disciples which made him an obvious choice to enter the inner sect.

Everyone here knew that even if this senior brother didn’t participate he would be taken under the wing of some inner sect master. This was more something he did out of tradition.

Feng Shi as a proper young master that was at the very top of the food chain looked bored. He was sitting to the side under an umbrella with two busty jade-like beauties. It looked like he was here for a picnic instead of the competition.

“You wish to challenge me, junior brother? Won’t you reconsider, you’ve already achieved so much, you need to learn some piety in this long life that we live.”

“Senior Feng Shi is so composed!”

“He is right, this Dai Rong is too childish, he needs a few more years before challenging senior brother Shi!”

The people laughed while Feng Shi ignored Zhang Dong’s hollering. He on the other hand just smiled while remaining up on the stage.

“It’s fine to be scared, senior brother, you can just give me your number one spot if you don’t think that you can keep it.”

Feng Shi stopped sipping his green tea while hearing Zhang Dong’s taunts. His facial expression that was previously relaxed changed into one of rage. He was quick to hide this moment of emotion before putting the teacup to the side.

“Afraid? This Feng Shi would be afraid of a junior disciple?”

“This Dai Rong has no shame, he is barely standing and wants to challenge brother Shi.”

“Brother Shi, show that junior that the seniors deserve respect!”

As expected the place got loud. The elders in their tower kept quiet while the juniors down below got into a shouting match. It seemed that they would let them clear this up among themselves.

“Ah, if I must, then I shall teach you some respect.”

Feng Shi finally raised his posterior from his spot and made his way towards Zhang Dong. Even though the others couldn’t see it, he knew that this was seething with rage.

He was not much different than any other young master. They looked composed and majestic on the outside but turned to cranky little kids whenever their authority was questioned. Even if he thought he would lose here, he would not be able to refuse the challenge, the loss to face would be astronomical if he did.

Feng Shi was greeted on the stage to the applause of men and women alike. It seemed that he had gained a following of some kind. From Zhang Dong’s perspective, it looked like a bunch of ass kissers trying to weasel their way into the good graces of someone that was going to the inner sect.

‘They don’t realize how these young master’s act, it would be a miracle if they kept their old promises after gaining power.”

“Your fighting technique is refined junior but you still lack cultivation.”

“Show me then.”

Zhang Dong replied while taking on a battle stance. He produced the exact same technique that he used against the second-ranked jade-like beauty.

It didn’t seem that anyone was thinking that he would win. From their standpoint, he looked like a junior that was just an early stage Martial Master. One that made up for his lower realm with high-quality skills and techniques.

The person that he was facing now was two small realms above him. This was not a gap that could be closed with superior techniques. This is something that Zhang Dong knew well and thus he was planning something special for such an occasion.

The gong sounded again and the two charged at each other. Even though no one believed that Dai Rong could win it, his young age caused the elders here to look at him as a prospect. Someone that could be nurtured to become a true powerhouse for this sect.

Chapter 354

“Is this all?”

Feng Shi scoffed while gracefully evading a small dragon made from blue electrical energy. For most of the outer sect disciples, it was an astonishing feat of agility. They could see that this opponent called Dai Rong was no slouch.

The attacks were quick and deadly. Each time those dragon heads chomped down a loud booming sound of thunder riverbed through the whole large field. This only showed how strong Feng Shi actually was as he was managing and doing it with little effort.

“Senior brother Feng Shi was this strong?”

“No wonder sister Meng Meixiu and brother Xuan Fen never challenged him to an open fight…”

To everyone here, it felt that this senior brother of theirs was far above what a Martial Master should be, even more, experienced elders that were at the late stage of that realm would fall before him.

“Submit junior, you have no way of winning!”

A ferocious palm strike that was thrown by Dai Rong was quickly kicked to the side. Feng Shi kick carried his own Qi and caused the dragon made from electricity to quickly dissipate.

“Submit? This fight has only begun!”

Dai Rong replied while using his other palm. The dragon on it combined with it as he fired off a somewhat cone-shaped electrical attack at Feng Shi.

The weapon of choice for this senior brother looked to be a battle umbrella. The moment the palm strike descended in his direction this umbrella was opened up. It started glowing with white light, the palm strike was quickly absorbed into this umbrella that was spinning around.

“I’ll return this to you!”

This peculiar weapon continued to spin until it formed a torrent of white energy. It looked like a blade storm that was bathed in electricity. Dai Rong retreated, his feet shuffled on the stage as he left many lightning charges after images.

The electrically charged storm didn’t stop, it connected with each after image and started getting bigger. It looked to be absorbing all of the electrical energy from those after images and only getting more powerful.

Dai Rong found himself at the edge of the battle stage. He had no way to run, if he was removed from this stage he would be disqualified. Thus the only thing he could do was to turn around and take the hit.

Everyone looked in horror at the giant cyclone that was composed of sharp wind blades and electricity connected with Dai Rong’s body. The young man moved his forearms above his head as he turtled up.

“Senior Feng Shi so brutal…”

“That junior had it coming, how dare he talk like he was senior brother’s equal!”

The peanut gallery commented as Dai Rong’s body vanished behind the white storm energy. They didn’t think that he would be able to survive this unscathed.

Feng Shi’s umbrella stopped spinning around and he pulled it back. The young man gave out a sigh while turning around. He looked to his old spot where he was sitting and the girls smiled at him. It seemed that the battle was over and he could return to his original place.

“I must apologize to everyone, I seemed to have lost my temper.”

“Senior brother is so humble!”

“Yes, senior Shi did nothing wrong!”

The young disciples cheered while the young master smirked slightly. Before he could make his way back though, he heard a voice call out from behind him.

“Where do you think you are going, this isn’t over yet.”

Dai Rong’s voice was heard by everyone. After the storm was cleared his injured body appeared before everyone. The upper part of his robe had been cut up into tiny fragments. His body looked like it was put through a shredder.

“How can he still be standing…”

“So many cuts…”

To everyone standing here, it seemed that the young man was holding onto his dear life with willpower alone. Feng Shi just started with an empty look in his eyes and quickly laughed.

“It’s not over? You can barely stand. This Feng Shi commends you on your bravery and willpower but you should know when to give up. There is no shame in losing to me.”

The young lord smiled while speaking and everyone here nodded. It was clear who had won this battle and if it continued then Dai Rong would shorten his cultivation life. Unless a person surrendered the fight would continue, not even the elders would stop it.

“Shame in losing? Who is losing, I just need a moment…”

The people laughed while Feng Shi shook his head in disapproval.

“Even if I gave you a year, you would not be able to best me... ?”

Feng Shi trailed off at the end of the sentence as he felt something strange happening. Soon after, the people could see a certain glow surrounding Dai Rong’s whole body.

“What is he doing…”

“His cultivation… it’s getting stronger?”

Dai Rong’s muscles started twitching and contracting. His long dark hair started floating up while electricity continued to gather in a small area around his already glowing body.

“If this isn’t enough for me to win, then I just need to go further… further beyond!”

“How is this possible… is he really advancing his realm in the middle of the match? Is he crazy!”

Someone from the audience shouted while Dai Rong’s body continued to go through some kind of change. Feng Shi was stunned by this turn of events, unable to comprehend what his opponent was doing.

Going through a small realm during a fight and while being injured was unwise. This was something that only someone that has prepared accordingly should attempt. Otherwise, they risked failing and crippling themselves for the future. For everyone here, it looked like the young man would just ruin his future and fall.

“Alas he was a fool, such is youth. Let us hope he won’t suffer cultivation deviation”

Elder Jingyi commented while other elders looked down to the stage the number one and two prospects were fighting. It didn’t seem like anyone here would go and stop the change. It was far more dangerous to go in, the young man’s chances of bursting through the realm would go down if any elder attempted to move in.

“Elder Jingyi… look... “

“What? Impossible!”

Everyone expected him to fail but instead of his body bursting with more blood it seemed that the wounds were subsiding. His muscles got larger and his figure filled up while his aura increased in power.

Soon a giant thunder strike was heard by everyone here. Dai Rong’s body crackled with thunderous electrical might and it looked that he had achieved the breakthrough that he had hoped for.

“How could this be… Martial Master… middle stage? Just like that?”

Elder Jingyi rubbed his chin while looking down at the young man. He started examining him from head to toe with his spiritual sense and he could feel the powerful golden crystal palace hidden within this youth. When he compared it to the young man this Dai Rong was facing, it was like comparing a grand castle to an old moldy shack.

“Unfathomable…”

….

‘Did you take a good look?’

Zhang Dong chuckled to himself as he faked a breakthrough in the middle of the fight. He had decided that this would be a better way to show off his might. If he beat someone that was at the late stage while being still at the early stage it would look somewhat fishy. Like this, he would look like a genius but he would still be grounded in reality.

His strength was already over the Martial Master level. The young man that he was fighting was talented but not that much more than your average sect prodigy. It was time to play it up for the crowd, he struck a nice pose and pointed out with his finger.

“Surrender now and I will be lenient!”

He could see Feng Shi’s forehead vein becoming very prominent at this moment. It was clear that this young man was just acting the good senior brother part. In reality, he would probably tear him limb from limb if there was no one looking.

“I have been too easy on you junior, if you don’t want to listen to reason I must show you the truth with my fists! So what if you achieved the middle stage, you are still below this senior!”

“I don’t need to be at the late stage to defeat the likes of you!”

Zhang Dong taunted the young man. He could see Feng Shi’s eyes going bloodshot from rage, it was clear that he was not used to such behavior from his peers.

Feng Shi was the first one to charge forward along with that strange umbrella weapon of his. At the end, there was a spike that would probably be able to pierce through anything it touched.

Regretfully Zhang Dong was done playing around and he would give the audience a nice show. It was the exact reverse of the start of this battle. This time around Dai Rong was dodging everything with no effort while Feng Shi charged at him like a mad bull.

“How could this be…”

“I have never seen such a display of agility, can he predict all of those movements?”

People had noticed that Zhang Dong was evading almost too well. This could be attributed to either ability or experience. Being that the young man was still a realm below Feng Shi, most attributed it to ability.

“That junior must have an innate talent for prediction!”

“Guh”

A palm landed on Feng Shi’s chest and he flew back a couple of meters. The umbrella was used as a crutch as he stood up with shaky hands. During the exchange, Zhang Dong had used a counterattack at a perfect moment.

“I told you, surrender now!”

“Y-you…”

Feng Shi’s face contorted to look like that of a devil. He was clearly not enjoying this fight, no one that was similar in age had ever been able to compete with him at an equal footing. Unable to cope with his emotions he turned into a madman.

Zhang Dong found himself deflecting and evading all kinds of electrical attacks and techniques. The longer this fight lasted the angried the young master he was fighting was acting.

‘Time to end this…’

With a well-placed kick to that umbrella weapon, he managed to disarm his opponent. The weapon landed outside the ring which meant that Feng Shi would need to fight without it.

“You dare?”

“Ha ha, yes indeed, but do you dare?”

Feng Shi looked a bit confused at the answer and another clash between the two occurred. This time Zhang Dong was sure to ram his palm in the young master’s solar plexus. With some Qi added to it, Feng Shi turned into an electrified puppet that soon flopped on the cold ground.

“W-winner… Dai Rong!”

He held his fist up in the air as if he owned the place. It was clear that he was showboating but everyone here knew it, he had skills to back it up.

“I am number one!”

‘This should be enough… I know you are drooling up there, come down and let us get this over with…’

Zhang Dong looked up to where Elder Jingyi was sitting. He clasped his hands in a proper manner before getting down from the ring. Now he just needed to wait and his path towards the inner sect should open up.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 356

“Elder Jingyi, glad to have you with us. How was the competition?”

“Boring as always but there was one promising disciple. On any other occasion, this would be a joyous moment but how things stand…”

Elder Jingyi that was used as a ticket into the inner sect walked into a closed-off room. In it, there were many elders and seniors from the Thunderball hall. It seemed that all the leaders from each of the halls had gathered here and this probably without the knowledge of the outer sect.

“Yes, the future is shaky…”

“How is the Patriarch?”

“Not good, his cultivation is slowly declining and we have discovered new evidence of a spy.”

“A spy? So it really someone from our sect that had poisoned the Patriarch during his ascension?”

“Yes, the evidence points to… Zheng Ting!”

“Zheng Ting? How could that be? She is the Patriarch’s granddaughter…”

“Yes, she vanished the moment we discovered that there was foul play involved. She is also trusted by the Patriarch, it would be easy for her to slip in the poison into his food…”

“But why would she do it? What would she gain from weakening the sect?”

Elder Jingyi asked as he was clearly out of the loop. Due to the outer sect competition, he was forced to remain in that part for a whole day.

“We fear that the Blood Poison Cult is involved, the poison that was used is also one that they are famous for…”

“The Blood Poison Cult?”

“Yes, our brothers found letters coming from that cult hidden away in Zheng Ting’s quarters. It would seem that she was romantically involved with one of their members which might have caused this…”

“Romantically involved? Does this mean that the Blood Poison Cult could attack us?”

“Yes, we fear for the worst. Normally our patriarch would be able to combat their cult leader but in his weakened state he will not be his match… this might also not be the only problem…”

“There is more?”

Elder Jingyi’s face went pale as the people started listing other problems. Apparently, their spies detected movement in other evil sects and cults that were situated close to their Thunderball hall.

The spot this Thunderball hall occupied was quite sought after. The concentration of lightning energies was not the only profitable resource. Deep inside the mountain range, there was a pocket of dark crystals. These crystals could be used by demonic cultivators to hasten their progress.

This was of course a big secret that the sect was hiding away from the other powers. With the betrayal of Zheng Ting, who was part of the inner circle, the secret might have been found out. It would not be strange if the demonic sects united to take care of them and to take away these dark crystals.

“This… Did our spies find out more?”

“No, It seems that our spies have been silenced.”

“This doesn’t bode well, can the patriarch recover in time? Should we contact the other righteous sects in the area and ask for help?”

“The other sects…”

The gathering of the elders continued into the night. While everyone was busy scrambling around, a certain sect leader was making his way towards the large tower of lightning.

‘Hm, this place doesn’t look that well-protected. Are they that sure that no one will attack them or are their forces somewhere else?’

Unbeknownst to him all the strongest elders and their disciples were gathered at one location all the way up the tower. While they were busy going through the sect's existential crisis Zhang Dong slipped past everyone.

‘This thing looks a lot bigger from close up…’

He had to strain his neck to look at the giant blocky tower. The lightning storm was circling around this building and discharging lightning bolts into it. If he had the ability to fly he could just charge into the eye of this storm and absorb all of this energy.

His current cultivation realm was that of foundation establishment middle stage. With the help of this energy, he was hoping to enter the core formation level. Maybe if he was lucky enough he could even push it to the middle stage. There was quite the amount of lightning elements here that possibly could boost him further.

‘There are some guards.’

He could see five men being stationed in front of one of the doors that led into this large tower. One of them was clearly the commander while the other four were just part of his unit.

‘It would be better if I didn’t just charge through here like a maniac…’

Zhang Dong felt that these five would not be a problem to beat but this would just put everyone inside on alert. Five guards just vanishing from their post would be quickly seen through. He at least wanted to give himself some time before they figured out that he invaded their tower.

‘This calls for the honey pot trap approach.’

His appearance started to change, from a young and handsome young master to something paler. Two large lumps of flesh started protruding from his chest as his body shrunk down. His hips started getting wider and his highs were now pleasantly plump. His skin was white as a jade as he took the appearance of a once-in-a-lifetime beauty.

‘This disguising technique is scary, at least it doesn’t make my little guy vanish along with it.’

Zhang Dong changed into some short fairy-like robes that showed off his legs and chest area the most. He had to pick a robe on the more flowy side, as from close up his large little brother would be clearly bulging it out.

“Who goes there!”

One of the guards noticed some movement and was shocked to see a beauty coming out from behind a building. The five guards started drooling instantly while checking out all the good parts. Zhang Dong had to hold himself back from cringing and scoffing at the looks that these men were giving him.

“Oh no, I’ve seemed to have lost my way… I just arrived in the inner sect, could one of you senior brothers help a lady in distress out?”

Lucky for Zhang Dong the competition for the outer sect disciples had ended. It wouldn’t be suspicious for some new faces to appear in the inner sect area. This was also what the guards here were thinking but due to the beauty they were seeing here, their perception was skewed. They abandoned all reason while devouring her with their eyes.

“Dear junior sister, you should not wander alone through the night, what if you catch a cold. Let this senior brother escort you back home!”

“What are you talking about? I will be the one to escort this junior sister back home!”

“No, it’s going to be me!”

Soon the group of guards started fighting with each other while Zhang Dong stood there. He took on a strange uncomfortable pose that made his posterior and chest stick out at the same time.

‘How do girls do this stuff…’

“Be quiet all of you and get back to your post!”

Soon the captain of the group of four shouted out. His aura was enough to make the four weaker guards shrink back in fright.

“Show some decorum!”

The man was slightly older than the rest and seemed a bit more composed. This quickly changed as he gave Zhang Dong one of the most lecherous smiles that he had ever seen.

“Little lady, you should not be wandering around at this hour, if one of the elders spots you, you will be reprimanded.”

He started approaching Zhang Dong while the other four guards scoffed. They knew that they could not go against their captain and that he was just as attracted to the woman as they were.

“Oh no, could you show me the right way back senior brother? I seem to have lost my way.”

“Certainly junior sister, let this big brother show you the way…’

The man grinned and the two started walking away. Zhang Dong had to doge a hand going towards his hip. The four guards then looked on in despair as their captain went away with the beauty that was shaking her wide hips side to side like a professional dancer.

“Damn, it should have been me…”

“Hah, why would that fairy even look at an ugly bastard like you!”

“What did you say?”

Two of the guards started shouting at each other but soon they quieted down after they heard a strange scream. It came from the direction that their captain and the beauty vanished into. They all looked at each other with wide eyes, was their captain more of a leech than they had thought?

“Captain?”

Soon the man returned. His clothes were slightly ruffled up and he had a red handprint on his cheek. The group of men started sniggering as they knew what had happened.

“What are you looking at, get back to your post!”

“Yes sir!”

They all nodded while retreating into formation, still their faces were filled with smiles. The captain soon entered the tower while grasping the side of his face. The moment he left the remaining men burst out in laughter.

‘Well, that was easier than I expected, only my pride as a man was damaged...’

Of course, the man that returned was not the guard captain, it was Zhang Dong in disguise. He had made short work of the lecherous man and with a quick zap, he was out. After taking his face and clothes he returned.

He looked around and could see that most of this place was empty. The space was wide open and he could see stairs going up.

‘That’s a lot of stairs…’

It looked like the impossible staircase phenomenon with many of those stairs moving at an angle. It also seemed that there was some kind of illusory formation working here that would make it hard for anyone to ascend.

This only applied to normal cultivators and not to someone like Zhang Dong. With a quick glance, he already knew the correct path to ascend.

‘I don’t see any rooms, they must be up higher…’

Soon he ascended up, his plan was to get as far as he could. The closer he was to that storm the better it was for his cultivation.

While Zhang Dong made his way up towards his destination, there was trouble brewing. Far away from the Thunderball Hall, there was a group of cultivators in shadowy robes.

“You have served me well Zheng Ting, when we crush this Thunderball Hall you will be granted the position of high elder!”

“Thank you, my lord, I just wish to be useful to the Blood Poison Cult!”

The man looked to be in his mid-thirties. He was quite handsome but also quite powerful. Behind him was a swarm of flying boats along with many cultivators.

“Tonight, we shall bathe in our enemy's blood!”

He raised his fist high up while the other men cheered. Soon all of them faded away into the shadows, the approach would be slow and only when it was too late they would strike.

Chapter 357

“Darn why is it so dusty in here? Do these sect people never clean their precious lightning tower?”

Zhang Dong complained while trying not to get too much dust on himself. Thankfully he was powerful enough to create a little dust shield around his body that would also protect him from getting stuck in cobwebs.

At this point in time, he was making his way through this lightning tower. He had seen through all of the protective formations that were keeping all the secret entrances from him.

‘I have to give it to them, these illusory formations are quite good. I’m not sure anyone that isn’t at least a formation grandmaster would be able to get past this.’

It was a little bit odd that this room that he entered was so well protected. To get here he was forced into a secret passage that was barely large enough for him to fit through.

The moment he entered he noticed that the mechanism was quite old. It was as if it hadn't been operated in many years. On the inside, it also looked quite old and unused.

The only reason for this place being so unkept and unused was that it was probably some kind of old secret evacuation passage. Maybe it led all the way up to the most important parts of the tower but never found its use.

‘Even if that’s true, they could clean it up every year or something…’

The further he went the worse everything looked, finally after walking for about an hour he finally arrived at what looked to be the end.

‘What is this?’

He scanned this place with his spiritual sense but could not feel any living being. Luck was on his side though as when he looked up he could see a large cristal.

This cristal would periodically give out a burst of light followed by a crackle of thunder. It was actually quite loud but a formation around this room was keeping all the noise from reaching outside.

‘That was easier than I expected…’

Zhang Dong was convinced that on his way through this tower he would need to knock out a few guards. Maybe turn into them to sneak in further before he was discovered. Now on the other hand he was looking at a source of great lightning power.

This crystal was clearly absorbing energy from the storm and radiating power. It was then discharging the residual energy into the walls of this chamber. Each time it did the whole room glowed in a dim blue light.

This chamber looked like a crypt. In the middle, there was some kind of large coffin. Each time the room lit up strange runes on the ground would glow. After a few glances, Zhang Dong already had a theory about what this place was.

“The room seems to be purifying the lightning energy that the crystal is giving off. It’s then injecting it into that coffin for some reason, is there someone in it?”

With another jolt of his spiritual sense, he tried focusing on the object in the middle of the room. Even when he tried he could not feel anything, the inside of this thing had no living being.

“Hm…”

Zhang Dong looked around, without seeing any traps he finally approached the large rectangular coffin. The room around it had some columns and on the walls, he could see some faded pictures with faces that were unrecognizable.

‘Has no one been here for hundreds or thousands of years?’

He wasn’t sure but he was still wary of the inside of this coffin. This world clearly had demonic beings in it. There was always a possibility of some kind of undead creature being in there. He did not feel the presence of any shielding formations but that didn’t mean that there was nothing there. If something exceeded his current cultivation or his old one, he would not be able to detect it.

‘Here goes nothing…’

It needed to be done, trying to cultivate with this unopened box of pandora would be dangerous. What if a bag of bones popped up and tried biting his nape or some kind of evil spirit tried to take over his body when he wasn’t paying attention?

With a swift kick, the large slab of the coffin was removed. Zhang Dong jumped back while in a battle stance.

“Hm?”

He quickly dropped his guard as the only thing that was inside of this coffin were rocks.

“Wait… doesn’t that look like a head?”

He approached and after looking everything over again he noticed that the rocky bits were shaped as a person. It looked like an old statue made from stone was there. It was clearly broken and crumbling. The moment he picked up what looked to be the head, it just crumbled into dust.

“Why would they put this in here…”

It was a big unknown, it looked like someone just placed a stone statue in here and locked it. Was someone trying to fake their death a thousand years ago or was there more to it?

“Hm?”

This wasn’t all, on a part that used to be the right hand he noticed something shining. After looking this up he found a storage ring, it was quite old but still in working order. It was locked but for someone that studied craftsmanship, this was nothing. After a few minutes, he managed to unlock it and peeked inside.

In the spatial ring, he found a lot of old texts. There were various lightning techniques that were of a higher grade and belonged to this empire. One, in particular, seemed interesting but it was not complete.

‘If someone used this thing they would suffer a large cultivation backlash, it's easy to fix though.’

With a quick scan, he had taken in all of the cultivation knowledge that was inside this ring. It didn’t say much about the original owner though.

“Good sword.”

After going through everything there was one weapon of note. A white sword, it was radiating lightning energy and was actually a heaven graded item. With it being far above his current cultivation level he couldn’t really use it but when he recovered it would be a nice replacement for his old one.

“This robe isn’t bad either…”

Zhang Dong changed into his original appearance. The dark hair of Dai Rong that he used changed into snow-white as his body expanded into a more handsome and muscular man.

The robe that he found had the colors that he liked to use, it was mostly white. On the back of it, there were some characters that translated into ‘Lightning Lord’. It was not quite the Lightning Emperor or Monarch title but would do nicely for now.

The robe was very similar to his old one as it was not one of the flowy ones, clearly more meant for hand-to-hand combat. There were even leg guards and armguards on it that were made from a shiny white spirit metal.

“Finally some luck, now it’s time to cultivate.”

The only thing that was missing from this spatial ring was a flying sword on which he could escape after he reached the core formation level.

After going through this chamber a few times he did not find anything else. Whatever this old statue was was unknown to him. There was no spirit in it and he could not find any traps that would turn on when he was concentrating.

With some muscle strength, he removed the coffin from the middle of the chamber. He also needed to alter the formation in this room. With a few alterations, he was now making it focus all of the energy into one point. That point was him.

While already dressed in his new robe he sat down. He was now in the traditional lotus position with his palms open. It didn’t take long for the crystal above him to charge up and fire a concentrated lightning bolt towards Zhang Dong’s forehead.

The moment the lightning bolt connected with his body he could feel the energies seeping into his foundation pillars. It was working, he could feel himself advancing further. The lightning strikes continued to descend and each time they hit they were swiftly absorbed.

One, two, three, ten, twenty, and then thirty. He took on all of the powerful lightning bolts before being able to fashion another perfect golden foundation pillar. His power churned and he could feel the electrical energy rising.

“Not enough, I need more!”

He looked up towards the lightning crystal above him. This treasure was somehow storing the lightning bolts but also hindering them from descending. It was like a small dam that only let a certain amount of energy through. For him to advance faster, it needed to go away.

From his eyes, a golden beam of light escaped and connected with this lightning crystal. The crystal unable to contend with this might soon burst into many tiny particles. The light from Zhang Dong’s eyes didn’t vanish but instead of the light being exuded it was now drawn in.

A giant suction force was created that was now continuously sucking all of the lightning energies from outside. Zhang Dong could feel the process being sped up tenfold and it was speeding up.

More and more foundation pillars were created. Five, six, seven, eight… and they continued with no end in sight. After he went through the fifteenth he realized that something was wrong.

There were far too many foundation pillars, they were exceeding what should be possible for a cultivator in this world.

‘I just reached the late stage and I already have this much… how many will I get?’

His cultivation was reaching new before seen heights. The foundation pillars kept being created as he absorbed a massive amount of energy from outside. The whole room began to rumble as the walls were being strained by all of this might.

With this amount of noise, he also believed that he would be found out soon. This is also why he could not stop. Along with his opened eyes, he also opened his mouth and started to absorb everything.

He was not sure what was happening outside but he would not be surprised if the whole lightning storm wasn’t being forced into this room. With another resounding boom, he reached the great circle stage of foundation establishment.

His whole body was now surrounded by a giant golden pillar of light. This pillar shot up and drilled through the ceiling. If they didn’t spot him before, they would certainly be aware that he was here now. The pillar of light reached all up to the sky and he could feel all of the lightning energy being sucked in by him.

‘Hey Bob what’s happening, I should have broken through already...’

There were already over sixty foundation pillars and he had reached the great circle realm but it was still continuing. Without knowing what to do he finally asked his AI companion for some help.

“User’s increased soul capacity has caused a unique cultivation variation… warning… user will die if he doesn’t break through…”

‘Well, thanks a lot…”

Zhang Dong concentrated, the pillars kept increasing and it looked like he would have to wing it. Finally, when the pillars started to approach seventy they started to slow down. Sixty-eight, sixty-nine, and then seventy.

Finally, as that seventieth pillar was formed he felt a jolt in his very being. He could feel something changing in his dantian and also in his soul. This was also followed by a bout of pain, pain that he had never felt before. It felt like his insides were being ripped apart by these energies.

He screamed out in pain as everything started collapsing around him. The whole place exploded and he shot up into the sky as a rocket. But even while in pain, he could feel it. He could feel his core being created and it looked like there was more than one…

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 358

“What’s happening?”

Elder Jingyi asked after feeling the whole place trembling, soon a person burst through the entrance to this meeting chamber.

“Elders! We are being attacked!”

“What!?”

All the people in this room were the heads of the Thunderball hall. All of them were gathered in this room and no one was able to notice any enemies getting closer.

“How could this be? Why wasn’t the alarm sounded?”

“They appeared out of the mist, we only detected the enemies after they started attacking the protective barrier.”

“Who are the enemies, who dare attack the Thunderball Hall?”

All the people looked at the sect member that burst through the door, the man quickly replied.

“It’s the Blood Poison Cult! They have the whole sect surrounded, they must have sneaked in during the night!”

“The Blood Poison Cult? Then it must be true, she really did betray us…”

One of the high elders commented as he recalled the Sect Leader’s granddaughter being rumored to have betrayed them. With their sudden attack right after their strongest member was poisoned this was too much of a coincidence.

“It doesn’t matter now, everyone protect the disciples, we must protect the sect, someone go inform the Sect Leader! Contact the other righteous sects, see if they will aid us in this time of need!”

The elders soon scrambled, this was a life or death situation. Everyone knew that this Evil sect of poison users would not stop until everyone was dead. Fleeing was not an option as they would just be hunted down to the end of the world.

On the outside, everyone was woken up by a blaring alarm. The outer sect elders and disciples were forced to defend themselves as they were the closest. The protective shield that was surrounding the whole mountain started cracking each time it was hit by the enemy's powerful attacks.

“That’s it, break it down, kill everyone, don’t let anyone survive, no prisoners!”

An elder from the Blood Poison Cult shouted. He was wearing a dark red robe that was surrounded by a purple haze of poisonous energy.

This was a coordinated attack. This sect came to eradicate the Thunderball hall and take their resources. Siege weapons were firing off large boulders filled with poison.

Many demonic cultivators were already in their battle formations and taking the appearances of ghastly demonic creatures. They pounded on the protective barrier with their massive claws and tendril-like appendages until it broke down.

The bloodbath soon started, the outer sect members were no match for the elite army of this sect. The disciples were quickly evacuated towards the inner sect while the elders and seniors tried to stall.

Even though this was the Thunderball Hall’s territory the protective formations and weapons didn’t slow down the approach of the enemy sect. It looked like the plans of the defenses that this sect was keeping a secret were also stolen.

It seemed that they knew where all the traps were placed and where all of the weak points were. With a lack of defensive measures the Outer Sect was quickly collapsing and people were forced to quickly evacuate into the inner sect where there was a stronger protective barrier.

“Hah, run you little roaches, you will not escape your fate!”

A large booming voice was heard by everyone, in the sky, three people were seen floating around. They were not using any treasures to float around as they didn’t have to. Each of these three had a cultivation level of a Late Stage Supreme Saint.

“Brother Ying, your Blood Poison Cult looks ferocious today, it does seem that we won’t be needed.”

The man that previously shouted was wearing a Blood Poison Cult’s robe that showed off that he was the leader. The two people that were floating next to him had other robes and were clearly not from this sect.

“I thank you brother for your words but we must stay vigilant, that Zheng Tengfei might still be alive.”

The other two men nodded. They were two sect leaders from allied demonic sects. Zheng Ting was put under a demonic bond with the Blood Poison Cult’s leader. She was brainwashed into loving him and revealed to be his perfect spy.

The cult was forced to act after they got news that this Thunderball Hall leader was close to ascending into the Saint Emperor realm. If that happened they would be surely eradicated by this righteous sect's new might.

Before that would happen they planned this out, the two Supreme Saints here were just the backup plan if the old Hall leader proved to be stronger than expected.

“You dare steal away my granddaughter!”

Soon the fight was brought over to the inner sect barrier and the Patriarch was forced to show himself. He was clearly not doing great as he was forced to stand on a floating platform.

“If it isn’t old man Tengfei, you’re not looking so good, is something wrong?”

The cult leader laughed out while the two men to his sides chuckled with him.

“Do you think you can leave here unscathed? Do you think my sect won’t put up a fight? You forget where you are!”

The old man held out a trident in front of himself and raised it up into the sky. When he did the whole lightning tower began to churn with power. The lightning bolts started being absorbed into the tower’s lightning rods as the whole tower started bursting with energy.

“Even in my weakened state, I can still operate the ancestral tower!”

“Hah, are you sure about that?”

The cult leader brought out a strange pendant and while the patriarch was ready to deliver judgment upon the enemies he activated it. The pendant glowed in red and with it, a strange tattoo appeared on Tengfei's neck.

The old man started vomiting purple smoke and quickly lost focus. The tower that was glowing brightly quickly lost its power and the lightning bolts started firing off in random directions even causing damage to the inner sect.

“Did you really think I would come here to be killed by that treasure? You forget that I’m a master of poison!”

The cult leader knew that Tengfei was the only one able to operate this huge tower of lightning. With the sect leader now down on the ground and vomiting blood, there was nothing to stop them from eradicating this sect.

“Everyone attack! That protective formation will run out of power soon, they lost their trump card!”

But while some of the lesser elders from the Thunderball Hall were trying to activate the patriarch’s trident something strange started to happen. The whole tower started rumbling and the lightning storm above became rowdy.

For a moment the cult was still outside, still attacking the protective barrier. The people only noticed a bit later that all of the lightning was being absorbed by one lightning rod on the tower. This rod soon started melting as it could not contain all of the energy and a large hole was blown from the inside.

At exactly the same moment of the protective barrier giving out the top of the tower exploded. The terrified Thunderball Hall members looked up and could see a massive pillar of bright light shooting out into the sky.

“What is that…”

“Oh no, the tower is no more and the protective formation is done for, we are all going to die!”

While the Hall members cried out in panic the cult members stopped with their approach as their leader shouted.

“Brother Ying, was this also one of your plans?”

The two Supreme Saints next to the cult leader asked as it didn’t look to be so.

“No… did you also notice?”

“Yes, there is a person in that pillar of light… the power is immense…”

“Let us attack!”

The three Supreme Saints nodded at each other as they didn’t like how this looked. It seemed that this Thunderball Hall had another secret that they didn’t know about. They all combined their attacks and fired them into the sky at the person inside of the storm.

This person was, of course, Zhang Dong. He was in a world of pain as he flew up into the sky. He ended up busting his way through this tower of electricity and entering the lightning storm himself. All of the lightning that was in the vicinity was promptly absorbed into him.

“GAHHHhhhh”

A massive shout was heard by everyone and prompted them to look up. What they saw there was a giant ball of deep blue lightning energy that looked like a sun. As this energy came to be it lit up the night. The whole place was illuminated and it looked like it was daytime.

The dark energy attack that were fired off by the Supreme Saints collided with this large ball of lightning energy but could not pierce through it. It seemed that Zhang Dong’s ascension was not going to be stopped by external factors.

He could feel it, his lightning core was being formed. It was much larger than the one that he had before and it crackled with deep blue lightning energy. This wasn’t all, there were still more foundation pillars to go as this was only a third.

A second core that was pure gold and radiated the holiest of energies was created soon after. With its creation, the deep blue ball of lightning that he was surrounded with turned to gold and gave out a burst or repulsion.

The demonic cultivators and poison users were pushed back by these holy energies. Some of them were instantly knocked out cold while others started vomiting pitch-black blood.

This was not over yet as Zhang Dong had to focus more. There was one more core to go and soon the rest of the foundation pillars started to melt and be absorbed into a new core. This one didn’t really have a color as it was translucent in nature, it was the soul core.

With one last shout, the ball of electricity turned white and everything was engulfed in it. The people had to avert their gazes while some that didn’t would be temporarily blinded.

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh of relief as the massive pain that took him over was quickly subsiding. The bright light that surrounded his body was also vanishing and he could smell the fresh air outside.

He focused on the cores that he had created. It seemed that they were the three aspects of his cultivation that were the strongest, lightning, holy element, and then his soul power. The three cores floated around each other as if they were harmonizing.

When he was ascending into the core formation realm he had momentarily lost his senses. The first thing that he noticed is his ability to fly, this was not something a core formation cultivator should be able to do.

When he checked, he could feel that his all-around power level was about half of what it was when he was a nascent soul early stage cultivator. Maybe after he digested this unique realm change, he would get even stronger.

Finally, he started glancing around and he noticed that he was surrounded from all sides. Below him were the Hall members while everywhere else there were evil-looking cultivators dressed in black robes.

Before he could ask about what was happening he heard an old man that seemed to be poisoned call out to him.

“T-that robe… that ring... is it possible… is it the great ancestor? Did you manage to survive the dreaded petrification curse?”

‘The what now?’

When petrification was mentioned he could only think back to the coffin that he found a crumbled stone statue with a spatial ring. The same ring he had around his finger as it was of a much higher caliber than the rest.

‘Does this mean that that was a person in there… but what is this situation…’

He started looking around, it seemed that he was right in the middle of a good old-fashioned sect cleansing. Apparently, he was now the ancestor of the losing side.

‘Oh boy, here we go again.’

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 359

Zhang Dong looked at his spatial ring and the new white robe that he apparently lifted off a dead man’s coffin. If he was in a game he would probably have gotten the grave robber achievement.

He expected to be met with strange gazes after he appeared but there were far too many people here. Not only was the whole Thunderball Hall out here but also some other sect.

This other sect was quite evil-looking. He could see many monsters that looked like centipedes and spiders standing along with these cultivators. Their attacking formations were radiating poisonous and demonic energies as well.

It was clear that while he was busy cultivating this righteous sect had been attacked but the other side. He was far too busy with his cultivation to notice anything that was happening outside. The room he was in was also sealed off so no one noticed him either until he blasted off into the sky.

After reaching that sealed-off room he had hoped to silently breakthrough. The plan was quickly discarded after his cultivation effort became a bit chaotic. To not go crazy from the pain he also hastened his ascension by directly jumping into the eye of the storm.

Now the sky above him was devoid of any lightning energies as he had swallowed it up. It would probably take a while till this area recharges itself and years to get back to the previous levels.

“Ancestor? Was there an ancestor like that? How could one still be alive?”

Suddenly the people started talking. With his appearance, the Thunderball Hall members became chatty while the enemies backed away. Zhang Dong was now radiating energies similar to a powerful Supreme Saint. His cultivation was of his own empire so the people were not quite sure where he stood.

“T-there was one… one of the old ones, the long lost ancestor that suffered a curse of petrification…”

The old man that was talking wiped his mouth from the blood that he had vomited out. It was the Hall Patriarch that was affected by the poison. During Zhang Dong’s appearance, he had regained some strength as the Poison Cult leader had stopped using his poison treasure.

“There was a legend the previous Patriarch passed on to me, of our ancestor that gave his life to protect the Hall. The legend stated that he was still somewhere on the sect grounds but the knowledge of where exactly was lost to time…”

Zhang Dong listened to this story and was able to come to a conclusion. This ancestor had died a long time ago but the room he was placed in was probably designed to keep him alive.

Through the ages, it was forgotten and probably the formations hiding his chamber were above the current sect’s knowledge. Only legends remained that no one really took seriously, even the ancestor's true name was lost.

“So this is their trump card? An ancestor? Do they think that we were born yesterday? He is only a Supreme Saint at the late stage.”

“You are right brother Ying, he is trying to mask his cultivation but it’s easy to see through it!”

“Their whole tower was now destroyed, Tengfei is in my grasp. Aid me, brothers. Let us kill that fake ancestor and reap the rewards!”

Zhang Dong could clearly hear what the trio of gloomy cultivators was talking about. His presence was not strong enough for them to just back away. It looked like he would be fighting his way out of it.

There was also an option of running away. These three might not be able to chase after him or even try. That was not something that he would do, he still felt bad about absorbing the lightning storm that belonged to this sect. He would also not leave so many people to just be slaughtered.

“Hold your foul tongue you bastard, you dare offend the great ancestor?”

The Thunderball Hall Patriarch got really feisty after hearing the enemies belittle his so-called ‘ancestor’. He was quickly put in his place by the cult leader that activated the treasure. It made the old man vomit up more blood and poison, which was quite a sight.

“Be quiet old man, your deaths are already assured, now my brothers and sisters att…”

“You sure have been talking a lot of shit for someone in slapping distance.”

Before the cult leader could finish his speech a booming voice spread out through the whole sect grounds. Zhang Dong finally spoke out which caused all of the demonic and poisonous beasts that this sect brought over to cower in fear.

“What?”

Zhang Dong quickly vanished from his spot in the clouds and appeared before the old man. Tengfei looked like he was close to withering away. His face was purple and he looked very skinny, it was a miracle that he was able to hold on for so long.

“A-ancestor?”

The Hall Patriarch was surrounded by other elders from his sect that were unsure what to do. But they were not even able to react as with one step he appeared right before the dying man.

“Don’t talk and let me heal you.”

He touched the old man’s forehead with his finger that gave out a golden glow. He activated his healing energies that caused his golden core to churn with energy.

The old man’s body began glowing in a radiant golden light. This light uncovered many purple-colored spots in his body and forced them outside. He could see this purple miasma being quickly expelled in the form of smoke out of the man’s body as he was nourished back to health almost instantly.

“Impossible… my poison…”

The cult leader was taken aback after seeing Zhang Dong cure the old man of his affliction. The whole process of healing was far too fast for a high grade poison.

“What?”

There was also more, the pendant that he used to activate the poison started glowing as well. Soon he found himself throwing it into the air before it burst into tiny fragments, destroyed before his eyes.

“My nine hydra poison pendant, how could it be affected from this far away!”

While the cult leader was shouting out from behind, Zhang Dong inspected the old man in front of him.

“You should be fine now, how do you feel?”

“I feel… I feel great, my hip pain has also gone away…”

The old man stood up on his own two feet and his face looked quite rosy. Zhang Dong was a bit surprised at the potency of his own healing arts. Previously he needed to use needles to insert his holy energies into the correct acupuncture spots but now it seemed that he wouldn’t need to do that anymore.

The golden core that he made had all of his healing Dao inside of it. Thanks to it being a whole separate core it wasn’t as limited. Then there was his lightning core which looked more similar to the one that he had before he ascended to the nascent soul realm.

It could be just regular lightning as well as golden. There was no drop in power whatsoever and using both at once was also not a problem. Then there was the translucent soul core which was the biggest mystery.

From what he could tell, he could also add it to his lightning attacks. He needed to test it first but he was sure that when he added the soul core he would be able to damage the soul directly.

This would prove quite good against any nascent soul cultivator. They would probably not be able to use their nascent divinity to escape any fights as his attacks would damage it directly. Then there were the phantom and ghost-type enemies that would also not pose a threat.

“Great, then stay here.”

Zhang Dong nodded as he could see the patient had recovered. He turned around and looked to the three Supreme Saints in the distance.

“Great Ancestor, let this Tengfei help you!”

With his health being recovered the old man was now also at the level of these three. From what Zhang Dong could tell the was a little bit stronger.

“No need, just protect your sect members, leave the punching bags to me.”

“Punching bags, great ancestor?”

Zhang Dong nodded while strutting forward. His body flew forward at a great spread which caused the three cultivators to take out defensive positions.

“Hey you three stooges, let's take this somewhere less populated.”

He shouted out while charging forward, the three cultivators reacted by putting up a barrier which was quickly broken by Zhang Dong’s charge.

The closest old man was promptly kicked in the stomach and sent flying into the distance. The other two were grasped by the necks and yanked. Soon the three vanished from the area in a matter of seconds leaving both sides stunned. The leftover silence was then broken by the Hall Patriarch.

“What are you doing? Don’t you see that we have the Great Ancestor on our side! Defend the sect, their beasts are weakened, their formations are nothing, defend the Hall!”

The old man’s shout invigorated the large gathering of lightning cultivators. They just witnessed a powerful ally easily removing the three strongest combatants from the board. This was the best moment for a counterattack.

Everyone nodded and soon they also charged into battle. The charge was led by the Hall Patriarch that now with the disappearance of the sect leaders was the strongest person here. He quickly picked up the trident that he had dropped, even if it was unable to use the tower’s might it was still a powerful weapon.

Zhang Dong could hear the shouts behind him and wanted to give out a sigh. He wished to minimize the bloodshed but it seemed that his new friends were still battle-happy cultivators. Even though he would be fine if they just turtled up until he returned they were going on the offensive.

“This should be far enough.”

With another kick the middle stooge found himself forming a crater in the ground. The two men that he was holding up by the neck were also thrown to the ground and bounced around it like stringless puppets.

“Hm, maybe I expected a bit more from you three…”

At first, he thought that he was just a little bit stronger than these three but this didn’t seem like it was the case. He was still only an early stage core formation cultivator but his might was approaching the nascent soul level.

“You cur, how dare you do this to me… I will eat your soul.”

The man that he had kicked repeatedly while flying here finally floated back up into the sky. Previously he was wearing some kind of mask but now it had fallen off and was showing his ghoulish features.

“You sure you don’t mean sole? You were eating it quite a bit back there.”

“Ying never told me anything about this, if we survive you better pay up.”

“I apologize brothers, I did not expect someone like that to be in that sect but together we can kill him!”

The three finally recovered enough to float up around him. They surrounded him in a triangle formation. The ugly demonic cultivators burst forth with evil energies while chanting, it was finally time

Chapter 360

Zhang Dong hovered in the air while looking down at his opponents. One of them was quite handsome for his age but he could tell that the man was using a disguising technique. Below it he could see a face that only a mother could love.

Behind him, there were the shouts of many people. The battle had reached its focal point and to end it he would need to end these three old farts.

“If you surrender, I promise to only cripple your cultivations and you may live the rest of your lives atoning for your sins.”

“Surrender? It’s you who should surrender, I don’t know who you are but you can not defeat all of us. Now brothers, let us destroy this man and claim what is ours!”

The man that looked younger than the rest proclaimed while the other two just nodded. He knew that there was no use trying to bargain with these types but he liked to give people an option.

“Is that so, well then…”

Zhang Dong pointed out with his finger and behind him, a circle of magic appeared. It was followed by many more such circles which riddled the sky behind him in a mass of bright lights.

“Mass Lightning Arrow.”

From the magic circles, a scorn of magical lightning arrows was produced. This was one of the many magical techniques he had learned from the other world. It could very well be used with Qi as a replacement for mana and actually required less energy while still packing a lot of damage.

The three stooges were in the process of chanting a strange ritualistic spell as well. The moment the swarm of bright blue lightning bolts descended on them a dark purple shield appeared before them.

This shield looked to be holding out fine but this soon changed as the onslaught of lightning bolts descended onto them.

“How could he attack for so long…”

The arrow rain was without mercy and the magical circles remained in place. Soon the three men inside the barrier started sweating. It was clear to them that they might not be able to outlast this enemy and drastic measures needed to be taken.

Zhang Dong just looked at them while being calm. This was mostly a test of his new cultivation realm that he had achieved. He was still not used to the three cores inside of him and how they could work independently from each other.

While he was contemplating his move the three demonic cultivators acted. They chose to overload their protective shield and cause it to explode. This caused a massive burst of evil energies to be exuded into the surrounding area.

Plants and insects that were in the close vicinity all died instantly. The whole place was covered by a strange greenish mist that even enveloped Zhang Dong’s body.

Even then he remained calm. It was clear that this was something akin to a smokescreen that these cultivators used to surprise their opponents. Any regular cultivator would be forced to retreat in fear of being poisoned by this miasma.

Zhang Dong on the other hand instead of running he activated his golden core. A radiant glow of holy energy covered his entire body. There was a certain lack of lightning energies surrounding his body.

Now with his golden core being separated, he did not need to use lightning along with his holy energies. This would save him much energy which could be better attuned to his needs.

“Oh no, not the dark mist, what will I do now…”

He chuckled a bit as the poison and evil energies could not penetrate through this thin layer of holy energy. It would be easy to just remove it almost instantly but if he did that, then the enemies would not come to him by their own volition.

Soon the first took the bait as he raised his hand up and added some lightning energies to his palm. With this raised palm a bladed weapon connected, this weapon looked to be a pitch-black battle scythe.

“You demonic types sure like those scythes of yours… wouldn’t a spear or halberd be much more proficient?”

“How did you…”

The cultivator’s eyes went wide as his sneak attack was blocked by Zhang Dong’s palm. Even though his bodily cultivation was still at the silver body level he could block attacks like these by surrounding his body parts with concentrated Qi instead.

This was one of the more basic protective techniques but also one of the hardest to do during the heat of the battle. The cultivator needed to focus on the direct moment of impact. If they timed it badly they would suffer dearly for it.

“I guess you will be the first one.”

The other two cultivators were not far away, one was below while the other one was above him. Before they could finish their combination attack, Zhang Dong grasped the scythe with his hand.

His eyes started glowing with lightning energy which he then quickly discharged everywhere. Most of it went into the metallic item he was holding. The old man that was grasping it was quickly shocked by a mix of lightning and holy energies.

Both him and the evil cultivator lit up like a bright star and caused all of the mist to be consumed by the light. The two men that were trying to attack him from two sides were forced back and had to use defensive trinkets to protect themselves.

“One down, two to go…”

“What!?”

After the bright light subsided they could see their ally’s charred body. It soon started crumbling into dust as it was incinerated by the lightning energies.

“Blast you Ying! This was not part of the deal, I did not come here to die!”

The ones that remained were the Poison Cult master and one of his friends. This friend was clearly not too keen on remaining here anymore. This was one of the most common traits of these types of people.

They were strong against weak people but their confidence quickly crumbled at any sign of resistance. They would not put themselves in harm's way to help their allies, sooner they would plunge a dagger in their back so that they would have more time to flee.

“No brother, we must fight together if we don’t…”

“Screw you, you are no brother of mine!”

Zhang Dong looked at the two men fighting in front of him. They were quick to blame each other and clearly none of them was concerned about their other allies' death.

Ying was unable to convince this man who tossed out some items towards Zhang Dong. Some turned into strange creatures that flew towards his way, while others created more poisonous smoke.

“I might have overestimated your strength or I might be stronger than I originally thought.”

He gave out a sigh and released a new aspect of his aura into the surrounding area. It wasn’t very flashy as there was a certain lack of a golden aura around him. Instead, his body was covered by a dim transparent glow.

The creatures that were attacking him found themselves dropping down from the sky as if a mountain was weighing down on them.

“Wh-what is this…”

“How could someone like this have been hidden away in the Thunderball Hall?”

“Please, senior, I didn’t have anything to do with this. It was all that Ying, he made me do it! Show mercy!”

After the dust was cleared both of the cultivators were seen down on the ground. They were grasping their chest in the spot where their heart was. They could not move and breathing came hard as they were being successfully suppressed by Zhang Dong’s soul core.

This core in particular allowed Zhang Dong to affect other people's souls. Soul arts were a forgotten art and very few texts existed on how to harness the power of the soul. Thus for him, that had this soul core it was easy to directly attack his opponent's immortal souls.

With no knowledge as to how to protect themselves, he could disable people that were even at his level. Only much stronger opponents could ever hope to protect themselves from such attacks. It was more or less an advanced version of a suppression attack that would allow him to never have to bother with weaker opponents.

“Your types are quick to change your tune at the drop of the hat, I gave you a chance to surrender.”

His opponents were now defenseless and before him. They were unable to fight back as he was successfully suppressing their souls. If this was the old Zhang Dong then he might have been merciful but after years of struggles, he was not so kind.

“You have killed many and you would kill more if you were left amongst the living, I shall give you a quick death.”

He began concentrating and thought back to one of the techniques he discovered in the spatial ring. It was very similar to one of his old moves that he was unable to do because of the lack of a nascent soul.

Zhang Dong clasped his hands together and his body was surrounded by a deep blue light. This light soon expanded while being followed by crackling thunder and lightning.

It started as a small circle but soon turned to a hundred meters in diameter. Then with a burst of lightning, a draconic head emerged from within. On this head, Zhang Dong was standing proudly.

Soon a huge lightning dragon could be spotted by everyone in the vicinity, its howls filling everyone with fear.

“N-no, I can not die here…”

“No please, what do you want? Spirit stones? Virgins? I can give you all, I will pledge my life to you senior, just let me live.”

Zhang Dong didn’t answer while the man pleaded. The time for talking was over as the dragon opened his mouth. A large ball of electricity formed in front of its maw and continued to increase in size.

“I hope you can find solace in your next life…”

The lightning dragon’s breath descended on the ground and the two disabled cultivators. The massive burst of energy almost instantly disintegrated both of them into atoms while producing a giant explosion.

The fight between the sects came to a stop as none of them were able to move a muscle while under this lightning dragon’s aura.

“Well then.”

Zhang Dong looked down to the giant hole that he blasted with the help of this lightning dragon. It was not quite the same as his soul beast but could be used during his core formation days.

He finally turned back to the Thunderball Sect, it was time to clear things out with the locals and then finally try going back home. With the increase in his cultivation, his system was revitalized, maybe now he could teleport back and see his family...

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 361

Silence fell upon the entire mountain range. The previous thunderous region that was covered by storms was now devoid of it. The sunlight started to rise on the horizon and gave birth to a new day bringing an end to the slaughter.

Zhang Dong was hovering above a large crowd of people. His body was radiating an oppressive aura which was causing both sides to remain quiet.

After the three Supreme Saints were vanquished by him in a very flashy matter the fighting had stopped. The evil sect members were down on the ground cowering in fear.

When the top elders fell in battle the juniors knew that there was no way of surviving. Zhang Dong was also already on a level where he could single-handedly dispose of the rest of them. The only way of survival would be to scatter and hope that he would not be able to kill them all too fast.

‘Hm… some parts of the system seem to be back in working order but the most important one…’

Zhang Dong’s eyebrows furrowed as he went through his system window. The part involving his sect was the most important one and he was now looking at it. He hoped to see the information about his family there. They were part of his faction so the information should be there.

‘It’s all grayed out… Bob, do you know something?’

‘The system update was successful, some functions have a distance limit.’

‘I’m too far away from the sect?’

‘Affirmative.’

‘Could you update my map to show me how close I have to get?’

Soon Zhang Dong was looking at a holographic image of the world. He was on the other side of this empire and it would take quite some time to get back. His hopes of at least seeing the passage of time was also denied.

His faction-building part of the system showed him the ages of his followers. If he was able to see their age he would know if more than a year had passed as his memory of them was still strong.

‘Damn, I have to get all the way to the border… useless shitty system.’

Zhang Dong cursed out which caused a thunderous noise to escape from the heavens. The people below were looking cowered in fear and started to bow.

“Please senior, show mercy. We could not go against the wishes of the patriarch!”

“How dare you speak!”

Tengfei the sect Patriarch shouted out soon after. His trident was stained with the blood of his enemies, his bloodlust still not satiated. With the three strongest cultivators being busy with Zhang Dong he had killed most of the other Supreme Saints that were below the late stage all by himself. The man that was pleading for his life was the only one left alive now.

“Ah right, I forgot about you guys…”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh, the most important functions of his system were not working. The teleportation option was also something that was activated when he was at the nascent soul level. Even if he got it now, he felt that it would also be out of range.

When he was in the Azure Dragon empire he did not find any limitations but that was only because he could not travel beyond it in the first place. His disciple window was also not working; everything had a range limit.

“Didn’t have a choice? There is always a choice.”

Zhang Dong finally started speaking, his body started shining as he descended from the heavens.

He was not a naive person, he knew very well that these people had blood on their hands. Even with that some of them were probably victims of their circumstances.

These demonic cults and evil sects had a way that they operated. Most of the time they would go pillaging through the villages stealing the young men and women away. They would sometimes use them for their strange experiments and the ones that proved themselves would be taken in as disciples.

Even with that, it was probably too late to save them. Their characters have been tempered by bloody battles and carnage. Taking such a person and trying to bring them back into the light would be quite the hard task, one that Zhang Dong didn’t feel like he would be able to go through with.

“Your lives may be spared…”

The pleading man’s eyes lit up at the motion of spearing their lives but soon they went wide after Zhang Dong continued.

“You all will give up your lives as cultivators and become mortals, you can continue living as servants.”

The cult members cried out in shock at this proposition. For a lot of people in this world losing one's cultivation was something worse than death. Living with no power in a world ruled by power was a sentence most cruel.

“But senior I implore you to reconsider, we could form a soul contract you may still have use for our cults powers!”

“A soul contract?”

There was that, it would force people to do your biddings. They would still have their cultivation but would be not able to go against the person hanging on to part of their soul. They would be nothing more than slaves but they would still be able to cultivate.

It was funny that the people here would rather become mindless slaves just to keep their small amount of power. Living as a farmer or a baker seemed like a worse deal to them.

Even the Patriarch from the Thunderball Hall seemed to be considering this proposition. It would be quite a boon to their sect if they could enslave thousands of cultivators. They would have a battle-hardened unit of cultivators that they could order to die for them.

It seemed like a good deal for everyone but Zhang Dong felt otherwise. There was no way of keeping tabs on all of these evil cultivators. How many people would they kill without getting an order to do so? What if they got aid from another sect and somehow regained their freedom? It was hard to do, but there were ways to counter these types of contracts.

It was far too dangerous to let them at large and Zhang Dong did not want to have more deaths on his conscience.

“No, you will become mortals. There is no need for your types to possess this amount of power.”

After saying that he pointed out with his finger. A thick ray of golden lightning energy shot out and at the halfway point down it split into many more rays of energy. All of these rays traveled towards their targets and connected with their dantians.

The people that were hit by these beams cried out in pain as they got hit. He was not able to just cripple everyone here, his power was not quite there yet. What he did was aim for the people that were around the Martial Saint and Supreme Saint realm. By holding them back with his soul core they weren’t resisting much.

“Cripple the rest, you come with me.”

He pointed out towards the Hall Patriarch while everyone was too afraid to raise their heads. With the strongest fighters now out of commission, this elder here was not needed.

“What do you need, great ancestor?”

The old man bowed his head and clasped his hands as he was beckoned over. Zhang Dong could tell that after healing this old man he was quite grateful. It was time for him to start his journey through the empire but for that, he needed more information.

“Yes, show me a detailed map of the empire and also take me to the sect’s treasury.”

It would be unwise for him to go unprepared. He had already burned through most of his spirit stones. Those he could recover after getting into this sect's treasury. He felt that after saving all of their lives a reward was in order.

He would not just drain the sect of all of their riches, only the items that would aid him in recovering his cultivation. Luckily this sect was concentrated in the lightning element, thus he had reason to believe that there would be many treasures involving his favorite element.

“Yes Great Ancestor, follow this junior.”

The Patriarch didn’t even react at the mention of the treasury. It seemed that he was fast to switch into the junior’s position after seeing Zhang Dong’s might. Clearly, he believed him to be the man that died inside that coffin.

The proof that this was untrue had been destroyed during Zhang Dong’s cultivation as the room he was in had exploded. The huge hole at the top of the tower was proof.

The Patriarch quickly guided Zhang Dong to the tower, the old man could also fly so he was the perfect guide. The inside of the tower looked a bit different as all of the illusory formations inside had been deactivated. Luckily the treasure room that was in the middle section was still there and well protected.

“I will bring the map of the empire promptly!”

“Mhm.”

Zhang Dong nodded as he was left in the treasure room. Compared to the White Tiger Clan that he had robbed, this place had much more. The spirit stones were of middle grade quality as well as of high quality. There were many earth grade weapons and even armor that he could use to quickly improve his body’s cultivation.

‘I should be able to reach the golden body easily with all of these, the spirit stones should help me boost my cultivation directly.”

He could also spot the thunder stones that he saw powering some of the buildings stored here. They were all promptly sucked into his new spatial ring that was quite spacious. Soon most of the high quality treasures and items made their way into it, when the Thunderball Hall Patriarch returned with the map he found a mostly empty treasure chamber.

“A..ancestor I have brought the map…”

It was clear that the old man was against this daylight robbery. He could not say or do anything about it, from his point of view the ancestor was the sect. Zhang Dong was someone above the Patriarch.

“Good, show me where those three sects are located that attacked us…”

“Ancestor… Do you intend to go there?”

Zhang Dong just nodded. He was not stupid enough to just start his journey when there was much more to be gained here. The strongest fighters from these three were now dead, the resistance that would be offered were minimal.

His plan was to clear out the three evil sects from their treasures and only then make his way back towards his empire. Even when he recovered his ability to fly it was slower than his nascent soul realm spread.

It would take him a month to reach the border, before that he could clear out these sects which would also protect this one from any more deaths.

“I will make it so that they won’t be able to retaliate but then I must set off on my own journey, I will leave the sect in your care.”

“B-but Ancestor…”

“This is my decision and this is what will happen.”

He replied in a stern voice which caused this Patriarch to shrink back in fright. It was time to finally set off and time to begin his journey back home.

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 362

“Where did you hide your treasure?”

“I’ll never tell a righteous sect scum… ARGBLARGh…”

A dark cultivator in a robe was seen being electrocuted, his body lit up like a dark sky during a firework show. Soon he dropped down to the ground while slightly twitching, his cultivation clearly ruined.

“Damn, word spreads fast here…”

Zhang Dong glanced over to some other cowering evil cultivators. He had arrived at the third and last sect that had attacked the Thunderball Hall. His plan was to go through the sects one by one and take away all of their most precious treasures but he had miscalculated.

When he arrived at the first sect, there was still a lot of treasures around but already a large chunk of the sect members had scattered. At the second one there were even fewer people around while on the third one, there were only some old farts left behind that probably didn’t have any worth to their sects.

It was clear that the information of his arrival spread fast and they evacuated. What was left behind were only items for beginner disciples that no one cared about. The items like high-grade spirit stones that he wanted were all gone.

If he decided to give chase he could probably gain some of those riches back. The biggest problem was that there were just too many variables. It was easy to stash everything in the spatial rings among many people. With this world being this big he could spend a month looking for everyone and still not get it all.

“Slaves…”

Zhang Dong took a glance at one of the cowering cultivators. It was clear to him that they were all compelled to stay here by some kind of occult contract. While they stalled him the true masters would run away and hide.

‘I don’t have time to play hide and seek but it would be better to gain more strength.’

While thinking he started glancing at the people here. He was in the middle of a large hall that was the main chamber for the big wigs in this evil sect. There he found a small group of people that had the stench of death on them.

“You there, come here.”

He did a grasping motion towards one of the old men that was here. This one had the largest cultivation realm from them all and seemed to have been the leader. After grasping him by the neck he started scanning.

“Hm… I wonder… this might hurt…”

“W-what?”

The man asked before a strange shadowy aura descended onto him. Zhang Dong used his soul core to poke and prod at the curse that was keeping this man as a slave. All of these contracts were based on soul arts so in theory, he could be able to overpower it.

These contracts were easily produced as they only required the person affected to accept them. This could be done in many ways but most of the time it was done by a simple death threat. The evil cultivators were famous for doing this mostly out of fear of betrayal.

The man landed on the ground while grasping his chest. He convulsed for a moment before settling, the other cultivators were aghast by the presentation of torture. They thought they would be next in line but surprisingly their fellow sect member opened his eyes and stood up soon after.

“The soulbond is broken… how could this be… who are you?”

Zhang Dong just smirked a bit before crossing his arms over one another and puffing out his chest.

“It doesn't matter who I am, now tell me, where did your strongest elder escape to. I already slew your Patriarch, the one next in line is the one I am looking for.”

Zhang Dong knew that there should be some kind of number two in the sect. If he was lucky it would be one person and not a whole group. If there was a second strongest then he would probably take the bulk of the items.

“Next in line? That would probably be Elder Yuan, he was the Patriarch’s younger brother…”

“That will do, tell me where he went, you are not bound to him anymore.”

Zhang Dong proclaimed while exuding a menacing aura. The man was clearly confused, living a life as a slave did change one's outlook on life. It was hard to get rid of old habits of following orders out of fear.

“I… I will tell you senior, just swear to me that the bastard will suffer a painful death!”

Surprisingly the man did a fast 180-degree turn and turned his hate to the people that enslaved him here. Years of rage bottled up due to being stripped of their freedom. The man was unable to hold it in anymore as he started shouting as if finally he could voice his opinion.

“He will be dealt with, that I can promise you, now tell me where he went.”

After the man calmed himself down Zhang Dong received the coordinates. Apparently, they headed in the direction of something called the shadowlands. It was a place filled with shadow beasts that were hard to deal with.

“Good, this will do.”

Zhang Dong started taking off from the ground after he got his information. The sect that he had invaded was a strange one. It was deep inside the forest with many flesh-eating venus fly trap-looking monsters. The eastern-looking buildings were wrapped up in vines that were clearly alive and moving.

“I’m getting proficient at this, it's nice to have most of my power back.”

With a few motions of his hand, he produced a round sphere of energy. At each side of the sphere, there were spell circles that were slowly circling around it.

After pointing at this orb it activated. The magical circles started shooting out thin beams of light that started connecting with the cultivators that were still left alive here. Just as during his other sect attacks he robbed people of their cultivation.

They would be left alive to live out their lives as mortals. He knew how the people in this world thought but that was just a mindset born from ignorance. There was nothing wrong in living a simple fulfilling life. Everyone here could very well build up a family and start anew.

‘I hope this is the right thing…’

The only problem that he saw with this would be the people's character. He did not know if a bunch of demonic cultivators could turn over a new leaf. Would they just cause more death and destruction while harming others in hopes of regaining some of that lost power?

Would they follow the law of the land out of fright instead and live simple lives? He did not know but he was unwilling to stain his hands even more than this. There were enough people that were now dead because of him and it looked like the count would only continue to increase.

‘Shadowlands huh? There are always some shadowlands…”

Zhang Dong turned to the sky and bolted towards his destination. His system map was updated with the help of the detailed one that he received from the Thunderball Hall. That one showed him all of the points of interest like sect location and distribution of the lands.

Luckily they were in the direction that he would be heading anyway. While chasing after this sect's treasure trove he needed to go through this map. The way he would be traveling was very important as there was an easy way and a hard way.

With the map and the help of the Thunderball Hall’s Patriarch, he was given a couple of choices.

If he headed in a straight line he would be pushing it. On the way, there were many dangerous places that could not be approached by anyone below the nascent soul level. He was already there but still lagged behind his old early stage cultivation.

There were too many unknowns to try going in this fashion. He would be going through sect areas that had elders that were rumored to be Saint Emperor level. There were also a few spots with strong monsters and beasts that would also give him a run for his money.

This option was taken to the side, unless he received some information of his sect being in immediate danger he needed to look out for himself. It would not do anyone any good if he was dead or crippled during his journey back.

The best way that also took the least amount of time took him through some cities and points of interest instead. As before he still needed to cultivate, areas with lightning energies would bolster his cultivation but now a little problem arose.

Due to the fact that he now had three cores, they all needed to be nourished at about the same rate. He could not exclusively absorb lightning energy and use it as a power source. The golden core required holy energies and the soul core required ethereal energies.

He found it out the hard way after trying to absorb the thunder stones that he nabbed from the Hall. When only his lightning core started increasing in power it was quite noticeable. It was fine to absorb it for now but unless he managed a golden ratio of one-third for every core he would not be able to progress.

Luckily for him, he still had his system which would aid him in this process. Even though it did lose a lot of its functions there was something it could do for him. By absorbing spirit stones he could use the points towards the core that was missing out. This process was not very cost-effective but it was the only thing that could help him further his power level.

‘Lightning is quite easy to find, the problem will be with the two others…’

Soon he arrived at the shadowlands that were in some kind of desolate area. Thanks to his soul core he could clearly see the shadowy phantoms lurking behind every corner.

“Hm… aren’t these phantoms just decrepit souls of the dead? They should be enough to nourish my soul core…”

He rubbed his chin while glancing at some of the dark shades, one, in particular, was hiding in a tree stump.

“Come here, little guy…”

With a thump, he landed next to that tree stump and reached into it. The creature of the shades had elongated appendages which it started flailing around but the moment he utilized his soul core the shade found itself unable to move.

With some prodding here and there Zhang Dong managed to figure out the process. He opened up his mouth and a strange suction force was produced. When this force hit the shade it started siphoning away its essence.

The creature cried out in shock but soon faded away into nothingness. Zhang Dong gave out a burp before covering his mouth.

“Excuse me.”

His soul core started radiating some light as it absorbed the soul energy that this creature possessed. There was not much of it there but he could feel that he was making progress.

“I guess the shadowlands will soon just be called the lands…”

Chapter 363

“Elder Xiong we have locked the exits as you have instructed, the phantoms won’t be able to enter.”

“What did you call me?”

“El… I mean Patriarch!”

“Yes, that’s better.”

A smaller group of about a hundred shadowy cultivators were in a large spacious cavern. The glowing moss on the walls was illuminating this place with a greenish light.

“Listen to me, my brothers and sisters. Our old sect might have been destroyed but that doesn’t matter, we shall rebuild and create a new one. We will rise from the ashes and become more powerful than ever!”

The group of cultivators that were here were the remnants of one of the evil sects that had previously attacked the Thunderball Hall. They weren’t fully involved as their previous patriarch had just gone with an old friend to aid him.

“I must apologize to all of you, my idiot brother brought this upon us.”

“It’s not Patriarch’s fault, no one knew that such a monster was hiding in that righteous sect.”

Everyone nodded as they were informed of one of the other sects going down in only an hour. This white-haired devil was seen destroying everything in his paths and not even the great formations could stop them.

“We will be safe here, we will send a party out to search for a new sect location for us.”

“How about we go to the lower reaches and take over one of the lesser sects? With our dark arts, we could easily make their weak cultivators do our biddings.”

“Not a bad plan brother, it would save us from having to hide in this place but for now we need to… What was that?”

While the people were discussing their plans they heard something rumbling. Dirt and small rocks started drooping from the ceiling which made the people here a bit nervous.

They were an evil sect that somewhat knew how to evade the evil phantoms outside. This didn’t mean that they would be able to contend with the stronger ones.

The only thing that was protecting them were a few old treasures and this safe house that had been built by their ancestors. Most of the people here didn’t know how to repair the formations that kept the evil souls away. If they suffered a massive earthquake and this place collapsed they would be doomed.

“Don’t worry, this is normal, the shadowlands are surrounded by a storm of death. That’s probably what’s making a ruckus outside.”

The people from the evil sect made their way into this place through a set of tunnels even before they reached the shadowlands. They had collapsed the exit for now out of fear but there were other pathways that they could use after everything had settled.

“What is that thumping? Is it getting closer?”

The rumbling stopped for a moment but then they started hearing a strange sound coming from one of the walls. It was as if someone was hitting it with a sledgehammer while being quite far away.

“No it’s impossible… could someone really be outside?”

The wall started to shake and the cultivators that were gathered here took out their weapons. The Patriarch moved forward as he was the strongest master here, in his hand a special medallion that had a purple shine to it.

“It might be one of the death beasts, get ready even if it enters here it will be weakened by the formation, it should not break just from this.”

The man said while sweating as he was not really sure if what he was saying was even the truth. Even though he was standing strong he was already eyeing the side exit. He brought the people over here and was the only one that knew all of the secrets.

There were several hiding spots that he could use while the phantoms were busy devouring his sect members. He knew well that if the walls were destroyed the formation would start weakening and the only thing he should do was to flee.

Then finally with one last hit, a small hole was blasted through the thick wall. He was ready to use the item in his hand to try to stall the evil spirits and then to flee. Instead of evil spirits, there was something else that greeted his eyes. It was the face of an unknown cultivator with snow-white hair.

“Ah, there you are. You know that you really shouldn’t place a spirit protection array in the middle of nowhere, it’s quite easy to sense with nothing else around.”

“T-the Thunderball Hall ancestor? But how!?”

“Oh, I almost forgot that they are calling me that? Well, this will make things easy, give me all of your spirit stones and treasures and you might still live to the next day.”

Zhang Dong forced his way into the inside of this cave and his radiant aura filled it with light. Inside the group of ghoulish-looking cultivators started feeling dizzy the moment they felt the overwhelming aura of good.

“W-what is this…”

The new sect Patriarch was only a Supreme Saint at the middle stage which made him far weaker than this man here. The evil medallion that he was holding out shattered almost instantly as it was pushed back by the holy powers.

With nothing else to do, he tossed this item at the overpowering presence and started running away. Before he could duck away into one of the hidden rooms he felt a pulling sensation. He could not resist it as he was yanked towards the invader.

“Listen here, I don’t have time for this, just give me your spiritual rings.”

The evil cultivator felt his body go limp as he was held by the neck. The man jabbed his finger into his dantian and promptly crippled him. With this, the man's dreams of finally walking out of his brother’s shadow went under.

“Doesn’t look too bad…”

Zhang Dong peeked inside of the spatial rings that this man had on his fingers. Inside of them, he saw many treasures but most unusable to him as they were of demonic nature.

“Now, give me the rest.”

He tossed away the old foggy that looked to be the strongest here. The rest could not budge a muscle due to his overpowering aura. Thanks to his half-step nascent soul powers there were now certain things he could do with his spiritual energy. One of them was to have all the spatial rings in the vicinity to float towards himself.

It only took him a moment to take away all the loo that these cultivators had. Most of it was not great but all of the spirit stones would add up. To top it off he crippled everyone here to the last person.

“Well, hope you can live simple lives from now non.

He commented while making his way out of the cavern.

“Simple lives? You jest, the phantoms outside will eat our flesh and devour our souls, you have sentenced us to a fate worse than death.”

The old man that he crippled first spoke out while panting.

“Oh, the phantoms? I took care of them, the place doesn’t look that bad if you take care of all the evil energy…”

Zhang Dong shrugged and then quickly floated out through the cave opening that he created. On the outside what used to be a barren wasteland covered by grim shadowy energy turned into a more lush environment.

The death trees that were possessed by evil spirits were slowly regaining their life energy. The streams of water that were pure poison to anyone that drank it, was now pure as they could ever get.

Zhang Dong had used his soul core to absorb all of the decrepit soul energy that had gathered here. There was even a big bad phantom king that he had to go through. With the combination of his soul core and golden core, it was nothing more than a mob.

After his holy energies touched this place the plants and animals had turned back to normal. With time this place could be populated by humans with no threat of evil spirits taking hold of them. With the death of the phantom king, the place was cleansed.

“My soul core can’t absorb more energy, now I only need to power up the other two before the next breakthrough.”

Zhang Dong now knew of a good way to increase his cultivation. Such places with evil spirits were uncommon but still existed without ever being exorcised. He could just use the map to find such places as they would clearly be marked as dangerous zones.

The only problem that remained was his golden core. He needed divine or holy energy for absorption to further his cultivation. This core was a bit strange as it also received a boost to energy whenever he did a good deed. Even showing mercy to this group of evil cultivators and clearing up an area filled with demonic energy was making it stronger.

“It’s a bit out of balance, if I absorb more evil phantoms my soul core could go berserk, if I don’t clear up those evil places my golden core won’t progress though…”

It was a bit of a waste as he could get rid of the phantoms without absorbing their energy. The only other option was his system that might be able to equalize things out.

“This will have to be enough, I might be able to advance a bit now..”

Zhang Dong looked out into the distance and he finally took off. After flying for an hour he finally decided on a safe spot. It was deep inside of a stormy mountain range that was also surrounded by some strong beasts. Unless a Supreme Saint arrived he would probably not get any unwelcome guests.

Before passing through he had a little glaring match with the ‘Beast King’ here. The strongest beast here was some kind of glowing green stag. It’s horns were quite intricate and large, it was weaker than him so it could only move its head down in capitulation without even trying to defend itself. The beast could also feel that Zhang Dong was not dangerous.

Thus he drilled into the mountain range and when he came out he found himself in an underground cave. To the side he could spot an underground river of sorts which was probably why there was some space for him to sit on the side.

“Let’s see what I am working with.”

Like before he started taking out all the usable items. All the weapons and treasures that could help him bolster his body refinement were placed on one pile while spirit stones were placed on another pile. Then came all the thunderstones that he had obtained from the Hall.

“Great, with this I should at least be safe when traveling through these lands, it will still take a while to reach the border, better start now…”

While thinking about his family and friends he quickly grasped one of the weapons. It started glowing red and quickly turning to liquid which was then promptly absorbed into his body.

“Not much progress, this will take a while…”

He gave out a sigh while looking at the massive pile of swords and spears. It was time to absorb them all and maybe soon he would have his golden body once again.

Chapter 364

Name :

|

Zhang Dong

Affiliation :

|

Zhang Clan, United Element Sect

Spirit Points :

|

2891

Cultivation Base Qi :

|

Core Formation [ Middle Stage 5 %] [ Divine Spectral Lightning Trinity ]

Cultivation Base Body :

|

Core Formation [ Middle Stage 6 %] ( Ascended Golden Body )

Techniques :

|

True Divine Lightning Path Cultivation Art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...

Dao :

|

Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting...

Other :

|

Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes...

“Whew…”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh after looking at his cultivation realm. He managed to balance out his cores before achieving a breakthrough into the middle realm. Now after reinforcing it for an hour he could finally move on.

Going from one small realm into another wasn’t that hard, he only needed to gather enough energy for all the three cores. This would probably be the same for all the other small realms; the only thing that he needed to worry about would be what was after that.

His step into this new core formation realm was quite painful already. Would he need to go through another body-altering change? The first time he ascended into the nascent soul realm he did it himself with minimal help from the system.

This time around it would be much harder but would also put him on a stage of his own. This was due to how strong he was now and how much a breakthrough into a larger realm raised one's power.

“Early stage nascent soul…”

Zhang Dong gathered some energy into his hand and the cave that he was occupying started to tremble. Bringing himself into the middle stage of core formation put him at around the early stage of his old nascent soul realm.

This could indicate that if he reached the great circle of core formation he would be back at his previous strength level. Then if he pushed himself even further beyond that he could very well shatter the limitations of this world.

“It would be nice if I knew the multiplier…”

He had asked Bob about it but his AI companion didn’t really know the answers. It was quite strange how useless he was in this original world while he could offer some precious insights into the other one.

His body refinement had also progressed into the core formation stage and even had a nice name change. While his old silver body had a plus sign next to it, this golden body was now an ascendent golden body.

With it now being in the golden body stage he could also use the old abilities that he once had. The acceleration of his brain function that it came with was quite nice as it allowed him to be even better during close fights. His senses would be enhanced during activation and everything would seem slower but in actuality, his brain would just be functioning much faster.

“This thing still isn’t showing anything, guess it’s time to leave. At least my crafting abode is back.”

Zhang Dong had access to his old crafting pocket dimension. There was a problem with it as Bob had burned through all of the upgrades that he made to it. Without any time on his hand, he could not waste it on getting it back up to the old condition.

With a thunderclap, he rocketed out of this cave. He had burned through all the weapons and spirit stones and was mostly left with useless junk. The occult items could be placed in the crafting abode for now. When he upgraded some of the features those items could be desynthesized into resources.

At least as a storage space, it was far better than the spatial rings he had. If he was ever searched by some other cultivators they would not find anything worthwhile in his possessions. The only thing he kept with him was the sword he got from the Thunderball Hall ancestor, his robes, and some spirit stones.

Back on the outside he looked at his minimap and flew forward to his next destination. He had mapped out a couple of dangerous spots that could have decrepit souls or some shadowy monsters. The stronger he got, the faster he would return home.

So he flew and time passed. The scenery unfolded before him and he could tell that this empire was not that much different than the one that he hailed from. There were pockets of people living everywhere and there were always a lot of them.

Villages with thousands of people and cities with hundreds of thousands. It was hard to find a settlement that did not have at least a thousand people living in it. The large size of this world was the only reason that it was not suffering from overpopulation.

The only big difference was that the sects in this empire didn’t create large territories that could be their own countries. They kept to their spots and let the lesser clans and smaller sects operate in the cities without getting involved that much.

They still possessed sites like spirit stone mines and large treasure troves with herbs and the like. Some of these places Zhang Dong was set on visiting, he would not feel bad about taking what he needed as he was choosing the evil sects as his victims.

Maybe in the future, the legend of a lone cultivator ravaging the lands would be told to the new generation. He didn’t care much as he was not intending to stay here for long. Luckily due to how the sects operated most of the treasures would be concentrated in a few areas. If he chose his targets wisely he would come up unscathed.

Two days after his travels he came to the first point of interest. When he looked into the distance he could see a thunderous mountain range filled with elements of the wind and lightning alike.

He was quick to dive into it, with his current cultivation level hurricanes and cyclones was nothing more than a summer breeze. The storm was promptly absorbed entirely into his lightning core. When he left he could see some people poking their eyes out from afar.

They were clearly cultivators coming over to see what was wrong. The moment they saw him up in the cloudless sky they bowed in fear. Not wanting to stick around to explain himself he moved on to the next area.

This area was another two days of flight away. This time it was a gloomy-looking forest covered with shadowy miasma and poisonous mists.

He could feel that right in the center of it there was some kind of soul-based creature. Before moving in though he spotted a group of people quickly walking out of the forests. They had pained expressions on their faces and some of them were constantly looking over their shoulders and back into the spooky forest.

Soon he would realize why they were doing this. After entering he was met with the usual rabble. Angry spirits that tried to possess his body and animated corpses that tried to devour it instead.

None of them could survive his soul core’s effect. Any type of undead creature had some kind of spiritual essence attached to it. Without it, they would not be able to move its reanimated body. What Zhang Only needed to do was to absorb this essence.

While moving towards the largest source of this energy he needed to take a lot of creatures out in the process. This felt like he was playing an old dungeon on an overleveled character. None of these creatures could do any damage to him and would dissolve after a flick of his finger.

“Ah, good old human sacrifice…”

He finally found why the people that were leaving had painful expressions on their faces. Before the evil creature, he spotted a young girl of about sixteen years of age. She was probably a virgin which these types of creatures loved to snack on.

She was bound to some kind of ritualistic altar and left for dead. The most powerful creature that took the shape of a large lich. It was wearing a golden crown and its body was adorned with a lot of golden trinkets with jewels. The being looked like some kind of old king, probably was one that was buried here before.

Now his vengeful spirit was snacking on the people in the area. The most probable cause of this sacrifice was to appease this menacing being. If the humans that were living outside continued to give sacrifices it left them to their own devices.

“Idiots, they don’t realize that feeding this thing people only makes it stronger, for now, it is contained to its own domain. When it grows strong enough it will be able to leave this forest and will devour them all.”

Zhang Dong shook his head as he knew how these evil creatures operated. It probably fooled the people into believing that this was their own option. It probably lent its power to one of the people living there that was doing its bidding and allowing it to grow stronger with time.

“Excuse me, I’m just passing through.”

Just at the moment when the monster was about to devour the poor girl’s soul, it felt something tugging it from behind. It found its very essence being sucked away by some kind of enemy.

When it turned around it saw a smiling Zhang Dong that was sucking away all of the phantom’s soul energy. There was a translucent sphere in the middle of his chest and the monster was slowly being absorbed into it. The monster screamed and used every ounce of its being to get away.

“Oh be quiet, the neighbors will hear you!”

It didn’t take long for the monster to vanish and with it the miasma that was accumulated in this place started to fade away. The lesser ghost started to fade away as they could not sustain themselves without their leader giving them parts of his power.
“Hey there.”

“W-what…”

“Here, I think this one belongs to you.”

Zhang Dong flew back and easily caught up with the group of people. Since they heard the monsters scream and how the forest started to clear up they remained here.

“You should really stop making pacts with these kinds of beings, if you kept giving it people to feed it would only grow stronger and devour you all.”

When he handed them the young girl the group of adults started to cry and thank him. They clearly realized that he was a powerful cultivator that managed to slay the monster that was plaguing their village.

Just to have a clear conscience Zhang Dong took the group of people back to their village. There he found the man responsible twitching down on the ground. After the monster was slain the high priest had lost his connection to it. He would still be too strong for the mortals to handle so he took care of him before going on his merry way.

“Okay, on to the next one!”

Chapter 365

“We have come as you ordered Patriarch.”

“Greetings Elders.”

A small group of old men were bowing before a certain individual. This man was writing something onto a scroll with impeccable penmanship.

“This will do, bring this scroll to our allies.”

The parchment was promptly sealed and given to one of the men here. The man that received this letter could see the intricate dragon design that was stamped onto the seal of this scroll.

“It shall be done.”

“Is everything ready? I don’t think that I have to remind you that we must not fail, if something goes wrong then we will have to suffer the wrath of an enraged Azure Emperor.”

The man that was named the Patriarch commented while taking a seat. The others followed suit as everyone sat down together around a table.

“There is one problem…”

“What is it? Spit it out!”

The man that commented swallowed hard and then continued.

“It’s about the Patriarch's Grandson…”

The old Patriarch’s brows shot up high and he promptly slammed down his fist on the table.

“What did he do now, tell me.”

“It’s not much, more of the same. He has heard rumors of a beauty from one of the middle-sized sects and he wishes to take her into his harem…”

The old Patriarch gave out a sigh before leaning back.

“Is it just that? I thought that part of his character would mature just as his cultivation did. Is there a problem with this particular sect?”

“Yes, the woman in question is their Patriarch’s wife, this individual, in particular, is revered as one of the rising stars in the region. Normally it would not be a concern but we might suffer casualties if we engage in battle. It would be better to wait till after our plan is carried out but the esteemed junior doesn’t want to see reason, he is blinded by lust. Maybe Patriarch could talk some sense into him?”

The Patriarch listened while tapping his fingers on the now cracked table.

“Aye, the boy’s hobby is hard to satiate but even I am having trouble controlling him. He has grown strong, so strong that I can’t even foretell what heights he might reach… it is as if he is our ancestor reborn, we need him for the plan to work…”

Soon the old man nodded with his head as the decision was made.

“Lend him some of the supreme elders and go take care of it, it’s just a middle-sized sect even if their Patriarch is at the epitome of the nascent soul, he will not pose a problem, take care of it! We still have some time left.”

“As you wish, Patriarch, it will be carried out swiftly.”

Soon the meeting ended and the old man that brought up the Patriarch’s grandson was approached by some other people.

“Elder Tong, how did it go?”

“Not well, the old Patriarch favors his grandson, we must appease his urges once again, send word to the supreme elders we will move out, as always…”

The man that approached this elder also gave out a sigh while shaking his head.

“I will do as Elder Tong commands, the elders will be ready by tomorrow. What about the esteemed junior?”

“Don’t worry, I’ll talk to him…”

The two men nodded at each other and they parted ways. The man named Tong then floated out of the meeting place that was taking place in a large tower-like structure. He glanced back at this tower which had a giant dragon coiling around it.

Right at the top was the dragon’s head that was open. Right there was a giant radiant orb, this orb was producing massive spiritual fluctuations that fused into the sect's protective barrier.

If someone would fly out beyond the barrier they would quickly notice the true meaning behind this treasure. The whole sect was floating off the ground, the barrier covered the whole set of mountain peaks that made all of it up.

Tong quickly soared towards one of these mountain peaks. The moment he arrived he could tell the changes that were done to it by its newest master. The scantily clad female disciples and lack of male disciples was a dead giveaway. Even the servants were all of the female variety. Unless a person was an established elder they were barred from entering this place.

Tong here was one of these supreme elders that could not be stopped even by the new peak master that resided here.

“Greetings elder, should I deliver a message to the Peak Lord?”

“That won’t be needed, I would request a meeting with the peak lord, free of others.”

The beauty that approached this old man lowered her head for a moment before speaking out.

“T-the peak lord does not like to be disturbed, is this an order?”

“Yes, it comes from the Patriarch, don't waste my time!”

The woman bowed her head and quickly apologized before removing herself and moving towards the peak lord's estate. The old man was asked to wait for the time being while she fetched the man in question.

Thirty minutes later Elder Tong found himself tapping his fingers on the table himself as he was made to wait in the guest house.

“Every damn time, that young sprout has no respect for his elders, what will become of this sect if he is meant to be the future of it…”

After another ten minutes passing elder Tong was finally able to hear someone approaching. The bamboo door slid to the side and then he saw him.

The man was about six feet tall with long jet black hair. His stature was not too muscular but also not too skinny at about that golden middle ratio. His apparel was revealing and his hairless chest was showing of that pale skin and pectoral muscles.

“What do you want you old fart, I said that I didn’t want to be bothered.”

Elder Tong’s brows furrowed and he started frowning at how the young man looked. There were two vixens wrapped around each of his arms, their large breasts pushing into his arms as they smiled.

“You smell of alcohol, this is not how the young master of the Wang family should behave!”

“Yeah yeah, what do you want, old man, I hope you brought up what I requested with ol’ gramps?”

The young master that he came to deliver the message to slowly walked in and plopped on the nearby sofa. One of the ladies quickly made her way into his lap while the young man’s hand started grasping onto her hip.

“Yes, the Patriarch has agreed. Some of the Supreme elders will join us tomorrow.”

“Great, I knew ol’ gramps would see it my way.”

The young man laughed out loud while still getting handsy with the two girls by his side. Elder Tong on the other side could see that there was something wrong with those women. Their smiles felt empty and their eyes were somewhat glossed over.

He did not know what happened behind closed doors but he knew that there was something affecting them. With a combination of herbs and certain techniques, it was easy to break someone’s mind. The women the young lord fancied were known to change with time.

Even when they were returned to where they came from they were never the same as before. Stories of them ending their life afterwards were quite common.

“If it was this much, you could have just told it to one of my attendants.”

Tong’s intent was to keep the clan young master’s name out of the dirt. If the regular disciples knew that he periodically captured women from other sects the good Wang name would go through the dirt. The young master on the other hand didn’t seem to care and bad rumors were already spreading.

“There is also another issue, the Patriarch requires you to participate in the future mission, I don’t think I have to explain how grave the situation is, all of the peak lords must participate!”

“Ah, the new quest? Yeah sure, after we are done with the side gig it won’t be a problem, It will be a great moment to get more points.”

Elder Tong wasn’t sure what the young man was talking about. Even after all these years, he could not get used to the way he spoke. Even though he was an oddball the results were there.

The more enemies he slew the stronger he became. To this day he was the youngest ever nascent soul cultivator that this sect had created, rivaling only the old ancestor with his speed of progress.

His path was riddled with corpses as all of the previous young masters that stood before him were now six feet under. There didn’t seem to be any remorse behind his actions and whenever a new opponent was slain the mention of some strange spirit points was given.

Then when the Azure Emperor was mentioned strange words like ‘last boss’ or ‘raid’ were mentioned. The Patriarch doted on this young man though so no one could say anything, the crazy words could only be attributed to this young man’s eccentric nature.

“Fine, we shall leave in the morning, that babe will be a fine addition to my collection, not enough light-haired and tanned beauties in this world, everyone is just so pale.”

The young master started laughing while Elder Tong removed himself from this place before he could lose even more brain cells. He did not even bother to mention the husband as he knew that it would only rile the young master up.

One of his favorite pastimes was taking women away from their spouses. Then he would quickly toss the women away while enjoying the show. It was as if the young man had his woman taken away from him and now he was trying to get back at any happy couple that he could see.

…..

“My gratitude, Senior, how could we ever repay you?”

“No need, I was just passing by on my journey, just be careful next time.”

Zhang Dong floated up while a group of merchants prostrated themselves before him. They were almost robbed and killed by a group of bandits but then he came along. The bandits were promptly taken care of and any spirit stones that they had were taken away.

“This won’t do, such an act must be rewarded!”

“Well, if you say it like that… I could use some spirit stones…”

Zhang Dong nodded and was quick to relieve the merchants of some of their spirit stones. As he was leaving he could see the man that offered him the reward being beaten up by all the other merchants that were now without any spirit stones.

“I should stop making so many stops, for some reason I have a bad feeling about this…”

Chapter 366

“I’m glad that you have stayed with us for so long, we will present tonight's last item!”

A well-dressed man with a soothing voice pointed to the stage. Onto it a jade beauty dressed in lavish clothing was walking. In her hands, she was holding a pillow and on it was an orb. The beauty placed this orb on center stage where everyone could see it and the small crowd of people erupted.

“Isn’t that the fabled beast core of a divine spirit beast?”

“It’s certainly the real deal, I can feel the divine power!”

Where the people were sitting was a large auction house. They were wearing various robes as they belonged to various sects from around the land.

“Yes, Seniors have a keen eye. This item belonged to a late Divine Beast! But not just any beast, it was one on the level of a Saint Emperor!”

“It couldn’t be…”

“Saint Emperor? If that’s true then it could be used to fashion a deadly weapon indeed…”

The murmurs continued until the auction started. It took a while for the cultivators here to quiet down and finally, it began.

“We will start at ten high grade spirit stones.”

Some of the people in the room swallowed hard after they heard the price point. One high grade spirit stone was worth ten thousand middle grade stones. Then one middle grade spirit stone was worth a thousand lower grade spirit stones.

This brought the starting price up to a staggering amount. If someone tried paying it in low grade spirit stones they would have to dump a whole truck of them here on the stage. Even with this steep price a paddle with a name of a sect on it was raised.

“It’s the Saint Dragon sect, they even have a Saint Emperor as a Patriarch…”

They weren’t the only ones bidding though as another sect raised the price even further.

“It’s the Blade Demon Sect… aren’t they in competition with the Saint Dragon sect?”

Even though this beast core was of the divine element it didn’t mean that only righteous sects could use it. There were ways to corrupt such cores as well as cleanse evil ones of their energies to produce a similar ranked product.

There were other large sects and powerful seniors that bid at first but soon everything devolved into a competition between these two powerhouses.

“What is your intention here Blade Demon’s, you can’t fully utilize this beast core are you just trying to hike the price up for us!”

A man with a long beard that reached all the way up to his waist spit out in anger at a decrepit-looking man in a black robe.

“Ha, if you don’t have the spirit stones then why even come here? Is the Saint Dragon Sect so poor that it can’t afford a little divine beast core?”

The people from the Blade Demon Sect started laughing while the cultivators from the righteous one fumed with anger. This was nothing new as the two parties were in a dispute with each other for generations and there was no end in sight.

“One hundred high grade spirit stones…”

Soon the price was raised to tenfold of the original price. The old man from the demonic sect grinned, his yellow teeth clearly visible. On the other hand, the old man from the righteous sect could just grit his teeth as he knew that he could not spend more.

“Hundred spirit stones, is anyone willing to match the price?”

“Going once… going twice… going, Ah I see a palm raised there!”

The two sects looked at each other and could not see anyone raising a hand from their camps. This prompted them to look down to the main stage and down from the VIP booths that they were in. There a hooded person was raising his hand as if he wanted to bid more than a hundred spirit stones.

“Who is that man? He doesn’t look like he even has a hundred low grade spirit stones… is this some kind of joke?”

As this was something unprecedented the people got loud. The seats that were down below the VIP booths were intended for the poorer demographic from the cultivator world. All the powerful elders would be inclined to pay a bonus to keep face and not look like a country bumpkin with the other poor sobs there.

“Sir, I must implore you to not raise your hand if you can’t afford the item…”

The person responsible for the action let out a sigh as he looked at the man that raised his hand.

“Afford it? I think I can but would you be up for a trade instead?”

“A trade?”

“Yes, I’m low on spirit stones right now but would you be willing to trade that beast core for something of equal or higher value?”

“Equal or higher value to a Saint Emperor beast core?”

“Someone remove that man, he has clearly lost his mind!”

One of the people from the Blade Demon Sect called out from up in the VIP booth. The others were of similar mind as the man looked like some scammer that was trying to steal the divine beast core from their sect.

“Hah, why don’t we hear the man out?”

On the other hand, the people from the righteous sect called out in favor of this turn of events. They didn’t have enough funds to get the item that they desired so if this man could snatch it away from the enemies instead it would be a win in their eyes.

“Okay, what would the gentleman like to trade for this divine beast core? I would advise sir to be careful about the choice of words.”

Even though the Auctioneer was fine with this continuing there were some guards ready to intervene. If it turned out that this person was wasting everyone's time here, he would be beaten and thrown out. They needed to show that there was no place for disturbances like this, otherwise, their establishment could be seen as a questionable investment.

“Nice. How about you give me that beast core for this cultivation manual, I think it would be a fair trade.”

The man pulled out a book that was quite large compared to other cultivation manuals. The Auctioneer was a bit surprised by the item in question but he nodded to one of his workers to go fetch the book and bring it over.

“A cultivation manual? What is this farce?”

The people began to whisper again as this was a strange trade. Cultivation manuals were a rare commodity in auction houses as they were something a cultivator would mostly not give up.

Most manuals that found their way here were taken from the defeated and were of low worth. The ones that were deemed usable were mostly kept by the person that found them. No one would actually sell a rare cultivation method unless they were either crazy or really desperate for spirit stones.

“Please my dear cultivators, I will quickly look over this item and we shall finish this auction then.”

Everyone expected the auctioneer to read the first page and then quickly toss it back to the person it belonged to. Instead, a minute passed, then two and three but the man was still reading this large tome-like book.

“Hey...hey!”

“Huh, what?”

The man that was reading the book snapped out of it after the old man from the Blade Demon Sect shouted out to him. The Auctioneer looked like he had seen a ghost as his eyes were wide open and his hands were trembling.

“What of the cultivation method? What is wrong with you?”

“Ah yes… t-the cultivation method…”

The man looked at the hooded figure that this book belonged to and asked a question.

“D-does Senior really wish to trade this in for that little divine core?”

“Hm… you are right, it is worth more than that core, do you perhaps have more of those cores lying around?”

The people were taken aback by the conversation that the two men were having. It looked like what was written in the book was not just empty scribbles, it was actually worth something.

“Ah! Quickly call over the owner, this is of great importance, not a decision someone like me can make! There will be a fifteen-minute recess.”

The Auctioneer was then seen calling out to one of the servants with bulging bloodshot eyes. This caused the sects that were gathered to look at the hooded man, it seemed that the item that he brought over was quite costly.

Some people that were near him started inching away as the constant glares from powerful cultivators started building up pressure that they couldn’t handle. It did not seem that the man in question was perturbed by it as he just sat there waiting while leaning back in his chair.

Within fifteen minutes, another old man appeared on the stage along with the previous person that was doing the auction. It was the owner of this establishment and in his hand was the large book that supposedly had a cultivation method in it.

“My friend, you put this old man in a bind, what would you like to trade for this item I could throw in two hundred high grade spirit stones along with the divine beast core, how would that be?”

“Wait! That beast core belongs to the Blade Demon Sect, explain yourself! How could that book be worth three hundred high grade spirit stones!”

The old man protested as it seemed that his bid was not even being taken into consideration anymore.

“I must apologize to our friends from the Blade Demon Sect but this is a matter between the Auction house and this senior here.”

He was quickly shut down by the owner of the auction house which brought more questions to what was being sold there.

“Only two hundred high grade spirit stones? You do realize that that manual contains a high grade cultivation method all the way up to the Supreme Saint realm right? It’s an all-in-one deal with the path laid out for anyone cultivating it! Wouldn’t a thousand high grade spirit stones be more like it?”

Everyone was taken aback by what the man in the robe just said. The beast core was in theory the higher graded item as it could be used by a Saint Emperor. This also limited its uses though as the amount of Saint Emperors that were in this empire was quite small.

On the other hand a full set of cultivation methods that could bring a person from the Inner Aura Realm all the way up to the Supreme Saint realm? That was something that sects would go to war with, this was something that could tip the balance. A cultivation road like that could very well be the backbone of any sect.

“G-good sir, please you didn’t have to…”

The moment the explanation was given the cultivators that were gathered here looked at the large book with hunger in their eyes. It looked like a pack of vultures that were looking at a tasty piece of meat. The strange way that the auction house owner was acting was proof enough that this book was worth a lot

It was clear that a lot of people were now contemplating on snatching that book away from the owner. Wars between sects started for lesser items and it was hard not to go for it when the prize was so close. Even this auction house with so many guards would not be able to contend with all the masters that we're here and they knew it.

“Oh, would you all shut up!”

Before they could dive in for the kill though, everyone found themselves on the ground clutching their chests in pain. The one responsible for this was the robed person that finally stood up, his aura powerful and unfathomable to everyone here.

“S-saint Emperor!”

Everyone shrunk back in fright the moment the cloaked figure revealed their cultivation level. Before they could even act they all were at his mercy.

“Now, could we strike a deal? Don’t waste my time more than you already did you bunch of murder hobos.”

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |

Chapter 367

Zhang Dong was looking at a group of bowing cultivators. One of them was handing him a spatial bag filled with high grade spirit stones along with an orb that came from a divine beast.

Traveling through these lands at his current strength level didn’t pose a problem. Even when he got in trouble and alerted Saint Emperors to his presence before they arrived he was long gone. The disguising skills that he leveled up proved their handiness on these occasions as his trail was unfollowable.

With time he arrived at this city where he heard of an auction house that would be selling a divine item. This he could use for furthering his holy core to get stronger along the way. The only real problem was the lack of spirit stones to buy it.

He absorbed them all into his system to also get stronger almost instantly as he received them. The only items that he could barter with were cultivation manuals.

Without wanting to spend days or weeks trying to sell them in the auction houses he decided to try an instant trade. When the maximum bid was raised he finally acted and now found himself with the prize in hand.

“Everything is accounted for, senior…”

Just as he had figured the cultivators valued the cultivation manual that he corrected a lot more than crafting materials. The auction house would probably make the spirit stones back quite fast after word spread of the manual they had acquired.

It would probably be quite lucrative for him to just sell manuals like these. The only problem was the lack of time. It would take time for the word to spread and to get the powerhouses to gather before he got his money's worth.

If he was just out adventuring without anything binding him in this world then he could very well do that. He could even visit various beast kings and battle them for their cores that he could then use to propel his cultivation forward.

There was a problem though, he had a strange feeling tugging him elsewhere. He had a very bad feeling that if he didn’t return in time something bad would happen. It was a bad premonition that made him quickly leave this auction house and bolt into the skies at full speed ahead.

The people there were left astonished by the speed that he was leaving which prompted them to believe that he was really a Saint Emperor. Knowing well that this was the limit of this empire’s cultivators they thought themselves fortunate to have survived this day.

While leaving he could hear them bickering over the cultivation manual that he had left behind. He hoped that they would be able to work it out between themselves without bloodshed but that was probably just wishful thinking.

Yet he didn’t have time to have a bad conscience. He has abandoned the thought of being able to take care of everyone here. He could not take responsibility for others people's actions even though he might have been the catalyst for them.

‘I need to find a safe spot and move on…’

After leaving the city he found himself a secluded mountain range that was protected by deadly wind and ice elementals. He quickly burrowed himself into the land to form a makeshift cultivation cave.

For one reason or another cultivation in his crafting abode was impossible. It would be the safest area for a breakthrough but alas he had to contend with a quick protective formation that would mask his aura.

The divine beast core was placed on the ground along with all the spirit stones he was able to gather. Zhang Dong was actually surprised at how fast he was progressing. After he was done here he would already enter the late stage of core formation.

There was no lack of shadowy places with evil phantoms floating about. Lightning storms that spread devastation through the lands were also promptly absorbed into his lightning core. It was a lot easier to progress than when he first came to this world.

He did not need to stop and slowly purify the lightning energies as he used to. This lightning core was quite efficient at doing this by itself. He just needed to find the correct power source and his cores would just take in the energies as if they were black holes consuming light.

Even now as he held the divine beast core in his hand his holy core was pulsating with joy. Soon the football ball-sized beast core crumbled into dust. With his holy core being enriched he followed it up with the high grade spirit stones that were used to equalize all of the other cores and bring them to the edge.

Soon he felt the cores bursting with unimaginable power. They were ready to go through their next enhancement and soon he would reach the late stage of core formation. This would still put him below his old middle stage nascent soul level but he would be quite close.

‘This will have to do, I’m not far away from the border.’

After reaching the late stage the plan was to make a last sprint for the edge of the empire. He knew that he needed to make it into the teleportation range of his sect. Only then could he finally reach his home, he also needed to save some of the spirit points for the jump.

Besides the high grade spirit stones that he received from the auction house, he had many more treasures here. Some were taken as gratitude from people that he saved while others were snatched from the less stellar cultivators.

He knew that remaining in this empire like this would also pose a large threat to his well-being. The news of a renegade cultivator flying around the empire unhinged from any responsibilities was slowly spreading through the lands. Even though he was able to hide his appearance it didn’t mean that he would remain unnoticed forever.

With a lot of pressure on his shoulders, he got to work. The cores started resonating with each other and circling around each other once more. Instead of creating more cores like with foundation pillars, he needed to refine them.

The process of refinement would actually compress the cores into smaller ones. The original ones were like large sponges that absorbed all kinds of energies. What he needed to do was to purify these energies and compact the cores.

This process required a lot of concentration and also a lot of energy. After it was all done the energy in the cores would become purer than before. It was as if he was reforging a blade from a lesser one to the highest graded one possible.

This process was quite volatile just as with the blades, one mistake, and the cores could shatter into tiny pieces. It was possible to lose one of the cores if something went wrong.

For someone with three cores, this was three times as difficult but would save him from losing all of his built-up power. The cores were like bonus lives which even if they faded he could probably push forward with only one. This would probably revert him to his old core formation stage which would be much weaker than what he had now.

‘It’s all or nothing now…’

The earth rumbled and the stormy weather outside was halted. It seemed as if time had stopped for this land as a massive burst of energy was produced. A pillar of light shot out from within the ground causing destruction in its wake.

This pillar intensified with time and continued to cast a glaring light throughout the land. It reached up into the sky and caused the storm above it to be absorbed into it.

Zhang Dong could not do anything about this, he knew that he had limited time. The longer he took to break through the more danger could come his way.

The beasts and animals that were here looked up into the sky. They did not flee or scatter, their senses told them that there was no enemy nearby. Once the storm was gone the soothing energies that came from within that pillar invigorated the land.

Long unmended injuries that any of these creatures possessed were healed while any demonic phantoms were eradicated in the process. Some of the more intelligent beasts that possessed a cultivation level lowered their heads in worship as they knew that a master was there.

With a thunderous boom, the pillar exploded and its energies rained down onto the ground. These rays of light did not bring death and destruction, instead where they landed the soil became invigorated with strange energies.

‘There we go…’

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh as he looked up. The cave that he burrowed into was long gone. Above his head was a fifty-meter-wide circular hole that he created after breaking through. He could see the clear blue sky and the sun shone its bright rays on his face.

‘Damn… there is someone there…’

He did not have much time to reinforce his cultivation as he felt someone approaching him from afar. There were multiple people and all of them seemed quite formidable.

“There you are, Renegade Cultivator, your days of terrorizing the lands will end here!”

After floating up into the air he found himself surrounded. There were six people around him and he could tell that they were all Saint Emperors.

‘Five early stage and one middle stage…’

He had a theory about his true power level but he didn’t really have an opportunity to test out his newfound cultivation. All of the enemies that he had faced were one or more steps behind him. They didn’t even make for good sparring partners.

“Renegade cultivator? I think you might have found the wrong person. I’m just ‘a cultivator’ I think that renegade flew that way, he had a really menacing look on his face.”

Zhang Dong pointed in the opposite direction where he was going while smiling.

“Well, I will excuse myself then while you go to apprehend that menace!”

He clasped his hands while slowly floating away but before he could leave two old men blocked his escape route. When he looked behind him there were two old women instead while below him was another old master.

“Do you think we were born yesterday?”

Above him was the most powerful member of them all. He looked quite imposing and didn’t actually look that old compared to the others. The salt and pepper hairstyle went well with his rough looks but the dark demonic-looking robes told Zhang Dong a tale.

“Can’t fault me for trying…”

He shrugged while smiling but soon his expression became stern and his cultivation was unleashed.

“Guess I’ll have to do this the hard way.”

Chapter 368

Zhang Dong looked at the six people that were floating around him. They were all on top of the food chain when this empire was concerned as they were all Saint Emperors.

It seemed that his money-grabbing ways have come back to haunt him. He had spent the last weeks ransacking spirit stone mines. Snatching away divine elemental herbs and even absorbing shadowy energies from evil sect grounds.

He was mostly sure to focus on the evil sects as those tended to be the less morally friendly bunch. Thus the people that witnessed his deeds attributed everything to him being from the more righteous paths.

It was clear that the people on top of their sects would not let this just go on. With the lack of time and a goal in mind which would bring him far away from this empire Zhang Dong didn’t erase his tracks well enough.

In his eyes, he would be long gone back in the Azure Dragon Empire before anyone could figure out where he went. His appearance in the auction house must have alerted some of these old fogies to his whereabouts.

Even then he would still evade their clutches if he just didn’t stop to cultivate. There were ways for him to hide yet this was not something he was planning on doing. With hiding, he would lose precious time. The old cultivators lived long and they could very well remain in close proximity while waiting for months on end.

There were two options left for him here, one was to run away. With his current flight capabilities, he could very well be able to reach the border and teleport out.

There were a couple of problems with that plan. For one he did not know how far these six would chase him and they could always call for their friends to meet him halfway. From six there quickly could become ten or twenty.

Then there would be protective barriers that could be activated to stop him in his tracks. There was a danger in getting caught in a trap from which he could not escape. While flying they could easily track his whereabouts while contacting their allies. He lacked the knowledge of key locations in the empire so he would not know how to evade pockets filled with cultivators.

“If you come with us and return what you have stolen we might show mercy, otherwise consider your life forfeit! Did you really think you could rob us of our belongings and see the light of day?”

The main man that possessed the highest cultivation level here started speaking out. His realm was of a Saint Emperor at the middle stage which would place him at around the nascent soul late stage level. His five comrades that were all at the early stage would be a bit below the middle stage of nascent soul.

In contrast to them, Zhang Dong was not sure where he stood. He was only a core formation expert at the late stage but after battling with people at the levels of half-step nascent soul masters he felt that he stood a chance here.

“I think I’ll go with option B. How about you retreat and you might still retain some of your dignity?”

He replied while his aura exploded, it didn’t seem that he could talk his way out of this. These six people clearly felt that they had the upper hand so he didn’t have anything to bargain with. The only way to prove otherwise would be to prove himself in battle against them.

After his reply, the five lesser Saint Emperors quickly pulled out their weapons and activated their cultivation. It was clear by their auras that they were all from fewer staller sects of the evil variety. It also didn’t seem that they were planning to give him much time to retaliate. Being all old experienced fighters they knew that it was best to strike their enemies down as fast as possible.

They charged but as they approached their target they were met with a strange feeling in their chests. There was a strange crushing feeling, it felt like their feet were stuck and that there was a giant weight upon their shoulders.

This was Zhang Dong’s soul core. He activated it at max power to see if he could just crush his enemies with soul pressure. Regretfully he could see that these Saint Emperors were different from all the other cultivators that he had faced. Even though his soul core was at full effect it didn’t fully disable them.

“What is this trickery?”

The strongest Saint Emperor that was there seemed mostly unaffected. With a hand gesture, he activated his own cultivation aura which started countering Zhang Dong’s soul core. While he was somewhat effective against the other five this man was able to dispel his soul attack.

“Watch out!”

Zhang Dong was not born yesterday as he knew that it was best to strike when there was confusion within the enemy's camp. While his soul attack was resisted it gave him enough time to charge at one of the disabled enemies. With one ferocious slice of his sword a cultivator fell.

One man’s head fell from his shoulders while another one was quick to move to the side. The slice was aimed at the two but the second one was nimble enough to only receive a grazing wound.

“Hey now, you’re not supposed to be dodging and I’ll be taking that.”

He raised his head while smirking. This was not quite the end of this attack, just like with nascent soul cultivators these Saint Emperors were able to utilize soul divinities. These soul forms could then be able to function to a lesser extent and with some techniques, it was even possible to recover one's body.

At least in theory that was possible but for Zhang Dong, this soul divinity was quite similar to the evil phantoms that he had faced off before. It was a fat juicy piece of soul energy that he could absorb with his soul core.

This was what this group of evil cultivators was seeing. Just as the soul form of their ally left its body to escape it was pulled back and absorbed by their enemy.

“What is this technique, he absorbed his source!”

Zhang Dong could feel the man's very essence being consumed by his soul core. Luckily he only consumed the underlying energy without any strange things like the man’s memories.

Some lesser techniques would burden cultivators with such things which then left them a mess if they consumed too many souls of the dead. His soul core would only go for the base energy while ignoring the rest which just faded away into oblivion.

“What are you doing, surround him, don’t let up!”

The strongest cultivator didn’t seem perturbed by his allies' demise. He was able to see the big picture as he threw his spear clad in demonic energies towards Zhang Dong. This spear burst forth with purple energy and turned into a serpent composed of this dastardly Qi.

Zhang Dong moved his sword to intercept this attack. Spear met sword and a resounding boom filled the area. He found himself retreating a few steps while the spear rebounded back to its master.

He was then met with a pincer attack from four sides which he evaded thanks to his moving technique. The spot that the four Saint Emperors struck now contained an afterimage that discharged a holy energy-charged jolt of electricity.

While the ones that dived in for the kill first were affected by this some of them continued their chase. The area around here began being filled with holes and bursts of energy as the fight continued.

The party of five found themselves unable to gain the upper hand even after several exchanges between the two occurred. Soon all five found themselves on one side while the white-haired Zhang Dong with his bloodied sword was on the other side.

While dodging he didn’t remain passive, his weapon delivering punishment to his enemies that were out of position. Their clothes told a tale of who was winning, while Zhang Dong’s white clothes were without a blemish his opponents found themselves with sliced-up robes.

“S-senior, this Renegade cultivator is formidable, we might have to retreat for now…”

The four Saint Emperors that were clearly used as cannon fodder by the one above them looked drained. Their wounds only increased while their opponent seemed to be able to see through their attacks.

“I have no quarrel with you, do you really want to die just for some poultry resources that you can just regain with time?”

Zhang Dong shouted out while glowing in his usual golden color. His aura was very confusing to these five cultivators as they had never met someone in the core formation realm.

It was clear to him that these people here didn’t come from one sect. Their robes were different and their fighting techniques also differed. There was no unity among them, facing a stronger opponent was only possible with good teamwork which they clearly lacked.

It seemed that the four lesser Saint Emperors were considering the proposition but their ‘leader’ just seemed more enraged by this proposal.

“Poultry resources? Do you even know how far back you set us back!”

“Is that so? How about this then, I’ll reimburse you for your losses.”

“Will you give us back the spirit stones you stole?”

“Well, I didn’t say that I would use spirit stones, I might have something even better…”

With that being said Zhang Dong pulled out a booklet that he promptly tossed over towards the five cultivators. They were quickly taken aback by this gesture and their leader used his aura to hold this booklet away from the group out of fear of it being some kind of trick.

“What is this? How will this make up for our lost resources?”

“Oh, you don’t want the Saint Emperor level Demonic Ashura palm? It’s just a pinnacle grade palm technique.”

“Pinnacle grade?”

While eyeballing Zhang Dong from afar the leader of the group opened up the booklet. Even from afar all of them could see what was written there and as they continued to read so did their eyes start to get bigger.

“T-this is…”

“It looks authentic… everything written there … how magnificent…”

To masters of this level, it was easy to see a gem like this cultivation method. After a few glances, they could tell that it was the real article. It didn’t take much to make these cultivator nuts look at things with hunger in their eyes.

“You see, could you even buy such a technique with those poultry spirit stones and treasures that I took?”

Zhang Dong gave out a grin while yanking the book back towards his own hand. The four old cultivators looked at the technique with hunger in their eyes. Then with a pristine pitching form, he threw the book into the stratosphere.

“If you want it, then go get it!”

With that, he bolted in the opposite direction leaving the group to decide on what was more important.

Chapter 369

“Greetings brother.”

A dashing young man nodded at the welcome he received from quite a lovely young woman. Both of them were wearing pure white robes reminiscent of their master. Their pure white hair was a clear indication of who that master was.

“The scouts have given their report, it seems that it is inevitable…”

“This does not make any sense, what would one of the great three powers want with us…”

Asked the young man that hailed by the name Zhang Liu. His younger sister was right next to him and they were standing before the hall of elders. Not that long ago word arrived that a large fleet of ships had crossed into the middle sect reaches.

Through the years they had created a vast network of informants that were planted in all of the large cities. Their communication technology was quite advanced for the times. The spies were there to inform the main sect of any suspicious movement from the other powers.

Not long ago such information had reached their ears. A couple of ships from a rather powerful sect have entered this side of the empire and their course was their sect. This was hard to confirm at first but now they were dangerously close and about a day remained until they reached their doorstep.

“What do you think that the elders will decide on?

Asked Liu while Xue, his younger sister, contemplated. She could only shrug and shake her head as this sort of thing was above her. Both of them were now core formation cultivators, which didn’t grant them access to the inner workings of their sect.

While their master was still around they would be informed about the decisions through him. Since he vanished on that fateful day, their standing in the sect had lessened. It was a slow progress but they could tell that some people were treating them differently.

They still had the support of the matriarch but she was also on thin footing without the support of the strongest. That title fell towards Huo Qiang and since his father was also one of the great elders some felt that he should take over while the Patriarch was away.

“We might have to ask your partner about the decision, the Matriarch might speak to her about it before announcing it to the rest of the sect.

Zhang Xiu flinched a bit at the mention of his ‘partner’. The girl in question was still Nuana who continued to strongarm him into a more permanent relationship. Now without his master's support, he was running out of options to refuse the girl.

“Let’s not talk about that…”

Zhang Xue chuckled to herself but soon her expression became solemn. She looked to the large gates that they were both standing at. These gates would only open for registered members of the great elders which they were not.

Past these doors was a large open chamber with seats around a middle platform. This platform had no one standing on it and the elders were sitting around it. It was similar to a lecture hall with the professor missing. The spot in the middle belonged to the Patriarch but since no new one had been unanimously announced it remained empty.

Above the spot where the Patriarch should be standing was a holographic image of the large ship. The image was of various shades of blue but it was quite clear to the people here to whom this ship belonged to.

“Do you recognize the ship?”

A woman with light pink hair and quite an exotic look asked one of the other people in the room.

“Yes, that crest belongs to the Soaring Dragon Sect.”

The group cultivators started murmuring among each other as they knew that this was one of the top three powers in this empire. If this sect wanted to go to war with any of the middle-sized sects they could easily wipe them from the face of the earth.

Someone like the Dark Palm sect that they barely beat with the help of their Patriarch would be nothing more than a speck.

“What do they want from us? Did they figure out our situation?”

“They could be after our technical advances, it's become hard to keep the flow of information hidden away from the other sects. Ever since the Patriarch disappeared it has become hard to handle the spies from other sects…”

The room wasn’t filled with many nascent soul elders. Ever since Zhang Dong’s disappearance, the progress of the elder generation was halted. He was the only one that could cleanse them from any impurities and offer them the correct advice to help them break through.

Even with their advanced knowledge that they received, passing into the nascent soul level was not an easy procedure. Only Huo Qiang was fortuitous enough to reach the middle stage of the nascent soul level. Zhang Liena, who was second in line, had not been able to progress.

This was mostly attributed to the demons that sprung up in her heart. The days of worry about her husband brought her cultivation to a stop and she couldn't bring herself to advance like Qiang who was more battle-focused.

“Do we really need to fear them? Their visit here might be unavoidable but it does not have to cause destruction for our sect!”

One of the older members that was not quite at the nascent soul level commented and some of the others agreed.

“That’s right, we know not of their true purpose we should hear them out before we make a decision.”

“We should hear them out? Did you lose your mind, why would they gather a whole fleet of flying vessels to come here? It’s obvious that they aren’t coming here to have tea with us!”

Another elder commented on the issue and a fight of words between the two parties commenced. One side was of the mind of raising the alarm and being prepared to fight to the bitter end. The other side was willing to welcome the guests with open arms and hear them out instead.

“Silence you old farts!”

The voice was raised by Zhang Liena which managed to quiet most of the people.

“What do you expect us to do then?”

The one that raised his voice was a tanned man with a muscular stature. Next to him was a man of similar build but hair that looked like it was on fire. He sat there looking bored with his hands crossed over one another as if he didn’t have a care in the world.

“Could I have a word?”

From the side a voice that a lot of people knew spoke out. A certain dashing young man was seen by everyone which made Zhang Liena scoff slightly.

“Stop using that technique when you are at the elder gathering you old leech.”

“Ha ha, excuse this old man.”

The man’s appearance started changing and soon he was back to his older looks. Zhang jin was his name and he was the late Patriarch’s grandfather. Next to him was Zhang Zhi that was also from the old Zhang Clan.

“What I wanted to inform the Matriarch about is that particular ship. It is quite famous around some of the circles and it does not bode anything good…”

“Is that so? Could you explain?”

“Certainly!”

Zhang Jin started talking. He explained that the ship belonged to a certain grandson of that sect’s Patriarch. He also explained that there were only bad rumors about this young man. His talents were second to none and he rose to peak lord status in just a few years.

It was quite astonishing but also very bloody. He apparently took his opponent's life without any remorse, if there was a chance to vanquish his opponents he would take it.

“You are saying that such a maniac is approaching our sect… What does he even want with us?”

“Ah yes, I’m afraid that this particular young man has a strong love for women… If he has moved here then he is probably after one thing and one thing only…”

Zhang Jin proclaimed in an elusive voice which brought everyone’s attention to him. After a brief silence and not getting a response Zhangn Liena slammed her fist down.

“Well, what is it?”

Zhang Jin finally licked his lips and gave a quick reply.

“Beauties.”

“Beauties?”

“Yes, beauties.”

“What do you mean old man?”

“I mean what I said, wherever that young man is seen women vanish. He is very well known around some circles, the women sometimes find their way back home but they are nothing but empty husks of their former self…”

“Then you mean to tell me, that they organized a whole fleet of battleships to take our women?”

This time Huo Qiang chimed in as he was a bit surprised as well. So were the others as they started asking questions about the person that this young man was after. Soon they came to a consensus on who the beauty in question was that he was after.

“Zhang Xue.”

“Yes, it must be Zhang Xue.”

She was the most sought-after beauty that this sect had to offer. There were a few others that came to mind but all paled in comparison to the late Patriarch’s disciple.

“Do you think that this peak lord will leave if we give them the disciple…”

One of the men here asked the question that was on everyone's tongue. It might seem cruel but offering one member as a tribute didn’t sound so bad if the whole sect was not affected. To some of the people here, it would actually be profitable to get rid of a potential thorn in their side.

There were two main camps in this current sect. One was composed of the people from the old Zhang and Feng clan while the others were of the Huo clan. The latter had abandoned the motion of ever finding Zhang Dong’s remains while the other still wanted to wait till they discovered more clues.

The Patriarch in question that they thought of being dead was at this moment speeding away from an encounter with five powerful cultivators. He could hear the explosions and screams behind him as they battled for possession of the palm technique that he threw far away.

“I should have enough time to get away from here before they discover the fault of this technique…”

While the palm was a powerful technique it had a certain downside of exploring a person’s nether regions if ever used. It could serve as a last-ditch effort for survival but one gave up on ever having children in the process.

‘They’ll need to read the whole thing until they realize I should be able to reach the border by then…’

His body soon vanished in a torrent of lightning energy as he made his way towards the teleportation range. The bad feeling in his stomach did not go away so he continued with utmost urgency.

Chapter 370

“Xue, you must leave, you can easily use one of the secret shelters that we created in these lands. Even if it’s the Soaring Dragon Sect they won’t be able to find you.”

“Brother, it’s fine…”

A confused Zhang Liu was yanked back as he was trying to pull his younger sister away. He was just informed by Zhang Jin of what the real reason for that sect’s arrival was. If it was true then his sister would be subjected to a life worse than death.

“What do you mean, you must escape, we can’t let that maniac desecrate you!”

While Zhang Liu continued yanking Xue finally managed to get her hand free. She grasped her wrist while looking down to the floor. Her shoulders were slumped forward but she seemed to have made up her mind.

“No brother, if I escape by myself many of our brothers and sisters could die…”

Zhang Jin that was here as well started frowning as he knew what his great-granddaughter was getting at. There was no telling what the young master of the Soaring Dragon Sect would do if the prize he came for was not here.

He knew of a few circumstances of this happening which always led to more deaths. This person clearly didn’t hold people up to high standards. When being denied what they thought was theirs they would lash out and if they did lives were at stake.

“It pains this old man to admit it but…”

“But what? You can’t seriously be thinking of just giving up Xue to those bastards!”

Zhang Jin didn’t know what to say, he could see the pain in Zhang Liu’s eyes. It seemed that he was taking it rather badly while his sister was somewhat composed. Zhang Jin wasn’t sure what was going through her head but she was clearly willing to make the sacrifice.

“Brother, stop shouting, it’s not grandfather's fault! If it means that I can save lives I will gladly sacrifice myself for the sect just like master did!”

Zhang Xue started shouting back while tears formed in her eyes. The moment she mentioned her master everyone was reminded of the times that Zhang Dong put himself in danger for the sect.

The first time was against the Dark Palm sect, he had almost lost his life during the expedition. Then he faced off against their elders in the final battle and finally came out victorious at the end with some help from the two other nascent soul elders.

Some of the sect members were against how the Patriarch acted. This was shown at the time where he agreed to help another sect out. No one really saw the merit of them facing off against that monstrosity. Some even blamed him to this day as his disappearance only weakened them.

“Have you set your mind to this?”

Zhang Liena walked out while being followed by two attendants.

“I did, matriarch.”

“Liu, you need to calm down. Nothing is set in stone, you might not be the reason for that young lord to come here.”

What Zhang Jin informed them about had been confirmed by some other sources. This didn’t mean that the man in question always went for the particular beauty in question.

“For the time being, remain hidden, if he doesn’t call for you directly we won’t have to reveal you to them.”

Zhang Liu let out a sigh of relief but his frowning face did not vanish. He would remain by his sister's side for the time being.

“The scouts say that they will be there within four hours. Please use this time to calm yourself down.

Soon everyone from here departed. The members from the Huo side of the sect were a bit less friendly as they left a few people to watch Zhang Xue and Liu’s movements. Everyone knew that the sect was at stake here and they would be willing to give up the late Patriarch’s niece to let it survive.

“This sect is changing…”

Zhang Xue returned to her room and looked out of the window. There he saw a magnificent set of buildings that were a wonder of modern architecture. Everything was built with the help of her master and even in his absence, the people living here were progressing at a rapid pace.

“Yes, it has not been the same since master vanished, wherever could he be… we couldn’t find anything, not even a flicker of his Qi or soul…”

Zhang Liu dropped down on a couch while sighting out some more. Both he and his sister noticed that after about a year of their master’s disappearance the people started to change.

Their master was not one to make public appearances often but he was regularly seen flying around the sect. At first, they told everyone that he was just cultivating, this was an excuse that worked most of the time.

It could take many years for a nascent soul cultivator to progress through a bottleneck. Thus it was not odd to not see them for years on end. Even then, everyone knew that something was off.

Whenever something happened only the grand elders were sent to clear up the problem. Some problems were resolved but others were not. The sect started clearly operating similarly to others and not as it used to when the Patriarch was at the helm.

Soon some started speculating that the Patriarch was either injured or dead. No longer did they see him clearing up demonic beasts or healing the injured. No more lectures were given, the techniques that he improved upon were also slowly getting withheld by the top brass.

With time a power struggle in the sect was seen to happen. With this most of the people could easily deduct that something had happened to the Patriarch. It was clear to them that if he was there no one would dare to go against the old rules.

Zhang Liena was also a big tell as the Matriarch had been seen acting strangely. The smile that she had on her face was replaced by a stern look. Even his closest students seemed vacant and uncharacteristic which caused everyone to speculate that Zhang Dong was no more.

Some saw this as a catastrophe while others saw this as a chance. Without the monolithic person on the top that could force everyone to act, there was now a chance to gain some power.

Even though the new recruits were handpicked for their morals this wasn’t the same for the old brass. Some members from the old clans took the chance to gain power and fatten their purses.

The sect was just too big to manage for the limited number of elders that was on the old Patriarch’s side. The next in line Huo Qiang also showed no desire to take over which left things up to others.

Zhang Liena still had a lot of say in everything but most of the nascent soul elders were still coming from the Huo side of the sect. They could not be denied and they often butted heads when it came to decision making.

After a few hours, all of the elders gathered outside.

“They aren’t taking us seriously, aren’t they?”

Huo Qiang was there, for once he looked quite ecstatic about the situation. It was clear that he was itching for a fight.

“Yes, they didn’t contact us until they already passed through our borders, if they were from any other sect we would have just attacked them…”

“This is normal, that’s how the strong operate. We can only hope that they leave quickly…”

Zhang Liena replied while looking at all the other elders that didn’t comment. All of them looked a bit ticked off about the blatant disrespect but they could only wait here for the ship to arrive.

Soon they saw it on the horizon. It was huge, bigger than the flagship that was produced by Zhang Dong. Behind it were several smaller flying ships and all of them carried strong auras with them.

It was clear from the start that there were several nascent soul cultivators in that armada. One of them was radiating astonishing might while the others trailed behind him slightly.

Without having made an appointment the elders from the United Element sect decided to not take out the red carpet. Instead, they activated the protective barrier that would be hard to pierce through from even a nascent soul grandmaster at the great circle level.

This caused the ship to halt before its approach and a certain person to appear in the front. Behind him was a group of nascent soul cultivators all in the late stages.

“People from the United Element Sect, listen well. We have not arrived to cause you harm, we will soon leave after we achieved our objective.”

The man’s booming voice filled the entire area. The people that lived in the city were previously informed about the danger and were already in the process of evacuating.

The sect had an extensive underground with long winding tunnels. They would lead everyone outside the sect grounds and into the forest area several kilometers away. The tunnels were lined with special materials that halted anyone from piercing them with their spiritual sense. Thus even now the people from the Soaring Dragon Sect would not know that people were escaping while being directly under their ships.

“We from the United Element Sect greet the great elders from the Soaring Dragon Sect. I apologize that we could not receive you respectfully but you did not inform us of your arrival…”

The one talking was Zhang Jin while the rest of the elders remained on standby.

“Yes, we have to apologize for this but we do not have much time on our hands. First, let me introduce myself, I am Rang Tong.”

The elders started discussing things with each other but soon another powerful aura washed over the area which was followed by an annoyed voice.

“Damn, I wish there was a dialogue skipping option in this shitty world, can you old farts shut up for a moment!”

This was followed by the appearance of a handsome-looking young man. Normally such a face would be envied by many other men and would cause the women to flock. The only problem was to who it belonged to. It was clear from one glance that this person was quite a quirky individual.

In his hand, there was a bottle of wine that even while talking he continued to sip from. When it was empty it was promptly tossed to the side and followed by a loud burp.

“Young lord please, let me perform the negotiations so we can return with haste.”

“Negotiations? Hah, let me show you how you negotiate!”

The young man appeared next to the most powerful elder and started looking around. Soon he spotted a certain woman from the elder group that was floating along with them.

“You there, yes you with the massive milkers. You will come with me and become my concubine!”

The young man pointed with his finger at Zhang Liena, who was taken aback by the revelation. The man was not here to take away Zhang Xue, no he was here for her instead!

A note from Kuropon

Thank you for reading!

Don't forget to follow, favorite, rate.

Donate | Discord |